And I saw a beast rising out of the sea, with ten horns and seven heads;
and on its horns were ten diadems, and on its heads were blasphemous names.
The dragon gave the beast his power and his throne and great authority.
They worshiped the dragon, for he had given authority to the beast,
and they worshiped the beast, saying,
"Who is like the beast,
and who can fight against it?"
Revelations 13:1-4
-That was amazing.
-You were great as usual.
That was such a difficult brain aneurysm,
but you did the clipping so speedily.
Yeah.
It was an excellent surgery.
Herr Dr. Tenma.
I'm glad I could once again witness
the genius of Kenzo Tenma.
No, I couldn't have done it
without everyone's help.
Thank you.
I can't believe it's so late in the day.
Yeah. It was a six-hour surgery.
We don't have any outpatients today.
Get some rest.
Where's Daddy?
What happened to him?
Herr Dr. Tenma
Düsseldorf
Germany
Come on. Get up.
Wake up, Dr. Tenma.
KENZO TENMA
Our roles are reversed, aren't they?
EVA HEINEMANN
I should be the one being woken
with kisses like a princess.
Eva. It's you.
Now in Düsseldorf. Mr. Lyman?
Kenzo, did you forget about our date?
No, I didn't forget.
Mr. Liebert, an adviser in the East German
Trade Bureau, has arrived to seek asylum.
He appeared in front of the reporters
with his family yesterday.
Mr. and Mrs. Liebert appeared to be well.
Their son and daughter,
a pair of fraternal twins,
looked happy as well.
They will be staying in Düsseldorf
for a while.
The government will be taking care
of their well-being.
I haven't slept a wink...
Hey!
-Wake up! It's your news!
-…the opera singer Mr. Rosenbach
was in a critical condition
due to a hemorrhage.
He is now in a stable condition
following surgery.
The operation was
at Eisler Memorial Hospital.
Earlier, the hospital's director
Dr. Heinemann held a press conference.
Mr. Rosenbach was diagnosed
with a ruptured brain aneurysm.
Dr. Heinemann
The surgery went smoothly,
and the clipping was very successful.
Can you tell us his chance of recovery
as he has many fans waiting for him?
We will give it our best to help him
get his voice back.
Dr. Heinemann's team has performed
numerous complex surgeries in the past.
This surgery has certainly confirmed
our country's status
in the medical community.
Isn't this great, Kenzo?
It's not about me.
It's news about your dad.
That's true,
but it's all because you did
the perfect surgery
as one of father's team members.
I'm sure he appreciates that.
You're the one getting the hospital
such great recognition.
I'm the one who should be thankful.
It's all because of your father
that I can work in Germany like this.
Do your best, Kenzo.
Everything will be okay if you just
follow father's lead and do your best.
It's only a matter of time before
he becomes board chairman at the hospital.
And you will soon be Chief of Surgery.
Eventually, you'll be the Director.
Then, I'll be the Director's wife.
I'm not built for a hard life,
so you'd better make me happy.
Do you want to go out, or…?
Blood pressure is 128/64.
Brain spatula.
Now to trim the medullary pyramid.
Dr. Tenma, your surgery
was excellent as usual.
Thank you.
DR. BECKER
And surgery isn't
the only thing you're good at.
Being Head of Neurosurgery at your age.
The Director and Chief of Surgery
both favor you.
You even have the heart
of the Director's daughter.
What are you trying to say, Dr. Becker?
Ah, I don't mean anything bad.
Just that it's all politics
in the hospital.
Of course, you know that the Director
is just using you. Right?
He talked about the opera singer's surgery
as if he was the one who operated
during the televised press conference.
Well, being used is proof
that you have the skills.
When you're promoted,
don't forget about me, okay?
I'll buy you a drink some time.
May I help you?
Are you Dr. Tenma?
Yes.
Bring my husband back.
I want him back!
Why didn't you do his surgery?
You…
My husband was brought into the hospital
before that opera singer!
But you put off his operation!
Aren't you the best doctor
in this hospital?
Why…?
Why!? Why!?
At that time...
I was about to perform the surgery
on the Turkish construction worker.
Dr. Tenma.
Yes.
You shouldn't be here.
Go to Operation Room One immediately.
It's the Director's order. Hurry!
You... If you had operated on him,
he would have been saved!
You...
-Mommy!
Give him back to me. Give him back!
Mommy!
…and I was fighting over
that dress with my friend.
It was the only dress of that size.
But don't worry, I won.
-Hey, are you listening?
-Oh.
Yes.
What's going on with you?
I read the records.
Dr. Becker did the surgery
on that Turkish man.
Are you still on that?
He obviously took too long
to perform the surgery.
If I did the surgery,
that Turkish man could have survived.
Stop that. We're having dinner.
I mean, what did she want from me?
I only followed the Director's order
to do the opera singer's surgery.
It's not my fault.
Don't you think?
Of course.
After all,
people's lives aren't created equal.
Give him back!
Give him back to me!
...to me! ...to me!
Is that the house?
Yes, the neighbor called the police.
How many gunshots?
About five to six.
Who lives in that house?
That's… where the East German defector
Mr. Liebert has been staying.
What? This could be problematic.
On my count of three.
One, two, three!
This is horrible.
What the hell happened?
Someone's there!
We have a survivor! It's a girl.
A man and a woman are dead,
and a boy is in critical condition.
I repeat, a boy is in critical condition.
An emergency…?
Bullet in the head?
Is the boy the only patient?
Yes. Both of his parents are dead.
They said it was a robbery.
Okay. I'll be at the hospital
in five minutes.
Oh, Father.
Dr. Heinemann, I'm sorry
to have kept your daughter out
so late at night.
What are you talking about?
You're Eva's fiancé,
so don't worry about it.
Why don't you come in for a cup of tea?
Have you told your parents in Japan
about the wedding date?
Uh, yes.
But my father is a doctor
at a small private practice,
so I don't know if he would have
time to come to Germany.
Isn't this a good chance
for him to come
and enjoy a bit of traveling?
Yes! It'd be our pleasure to have him.
Thank you.
I am very grateful to you
for taking me under your wing.
When you came to Germany,
I thought you were like a high school boy.
Now you're the up-and-coming
top surgeon at Eisler Memorial Hospital.
By the way, Kenzo, about your research
on cerebral vasospasm following
subarachnoid hemorrhage…
Yes, I'm making a model of a dog
with subarachnoid hemorrhage.
Sorry, but we're canceling
the research project.
What?
I will be a presenter
at the next symposium
of the European Society
for Emergency Medicine.
I'd like you to prepare my speech draft.
Well, but…
I'm almost done with my research--
I had a tough afternoon today.
What happened, father?
Some shady group came to the hospital
and protested about the surgery
for the opera singer.
They said that we put off
the Turkish man's surgery for the singer.
It's a total misunderstanding.
The Turkish man's surgery
was performed earlier.
Nothing wrong with our procedure.
Right?
Uh… Yes.
Do they think doctors
are volunteers or something?
We have to advance as academic scholars
before we can save lives. Right?
I'm counting on you for my manuscript.
I have high hopes for you, Tenma.
Yes… Thank you.
Damn it!
-How is the patient?
-He's inside.
How are his vitals?
Blood pressure is 72/50.
Pulse rate is 137.
The bullet entered from his forehead…
Show me the X-rays.
Right away.
Ah, Dr. Tenma!
What about this girl?
She is the boy's twin sister.
Any injuries?
No, but she has suffered
severe mental trauma.
What is it?
Kill…
What?
Dr. Tenma.
The X-rays and CT scans
of his head are ready.
Alright, I'll be right there.
It entered deep into the brain
from his forehead.
Yes.
It'll be difficult.
The bullet grazed
his left middle cerebral artery.
I see! Dr. Tenma is right.
This is going to be tough.
If we moved the bullet even a little,
the artery might break
and lead to hemorrhaging.
Sorry I'm late.
Dr. Becker.
How can you be late
when you're the one on duty?
We'll do a bifrontal craniotomy,
clean up any bones and infection.
Then, we'll carefully
take the bullet out.
Finally, we'll do angioplasty.
Yes.
It will take some time,
but let's do our best.
Blood pressure is 120/80
and pulse rate is 92. Looking good.
Anesthetic applied.
-Dr. Tenma.
-Yes?
You shouldn't be here.
Go to Operating Room One right now.
Mayor Roedecker has collapsed
with cerebral thrombus!
He will arrive in ten minutes
by helicopter.
Then, please call Dr. Boyer.
He might have an arterial occlusion.
If that's the case,
you will do the surgery.
But I'm about to start
on the surgery for that boy.
It's the Director.
This is Tenma.
Ah, Tenma, I'm leaving you to take care of the mayor.
I've got Dr. Eisen and Dr. Boyer coming
so it should be fine.
But I'm just getting ready
for another surgery.
You can let Dr. Becker handle that.
What?
To be honest with you,
my current patient's
left middle cerebral artery
was grazed by a bullet.
It will be a very complicated surgery.
But I think I can do it.
Dr. Boyer can operate on the mayor.
I have to be the one
to operate on the boy.
Tenma, you must do your best
to save the mayor.
The mayor has promised that
he will increase
our hospital's subsidy
during the next medical audit.
We can't let him die just yet.
I'm counting on you, Tenma.
I have high hopes for you.
Yes.
The mayor has arrived at the heliport!
We will do an angiogram after the CT scan.
Check where the thrombotic occlusion is.
Get ready, Dr. Tenma.
We're relying on your genius.
Do they think doctors
are volunteers or something?
We have to advance as academic scholars
before we can save lives. Right?
I only followed the Director's order
to do the opera singer's surgery.
It's not my fault.
Of course.
After all,
people's lives aren't created equal.
Bring him back!
If you did his surgery,
he might have lived!
Bring him back to me!
Bring him back!
What's wrong, Dr. Tenma?
I…
I have another surgery to do.
Hey! Dr. Tenma!
It's the Director's order!
The mayor is having a CT scan.
Please go to the CT scan room now.
Got it.
Wait, Dr. Tenma!
Dr. Tenma!
Don't worry. Hang in there. I will save you.
Kill…
And slowly, you come to realise
It's all as it should be
You can only do so much
If you're game enough
You could place your trust in me
For the love of life
There's a trade off
We could lose it all
But we'll go down fighting
Downfall