You haven't taken a shower recently,
have you, Mr. Mauler?
I thought we agreed when you moved
to the desk next to me...
...that you would at least take a shower every two days!
God, you are so annoying!
There is a guest in the reception room.
I'm going home now, so please make
some tea for him yourself.
A guest?
At this hour?
He has not taken a bath in while, either.
He smells as bad as you!
What is that supposed to mean?
Whose fault is it that I haven't taken a bath in a while?
The only reason you can still work for this newspaper
with no hope for advancement...
...is all thanks to the great Mauler.
And yet she doesn't even realize it.
Damn it!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
My name is Tenma.
Please, I hope you can help me.
I see.
He is indeed dirty.
I see.  So you are a doctor?
You sure don't look like one, though.
So Doctor, is this what you are trying to say?
The next target in the slew of middle aged couple
murders happening throughout Germany...
...is here in Heidelberg.
That a middle aged couple has a foster daughter.
When she turns twenty, the killer
will come to take her away.
And when that happens, the foster
parents will definitely be killed.
But you don't know who or where the
foster parents and the girl are.
You have got some sort of complex!
This is no laughing matter!
Please believe me!
That is just nonsense.
Not even a third rate tabloid would buy a story like that.
I didn't come to here so you could write an article about it!
There is more than a six month gap...
...between the time the twins disappeared
from the hospital...
...and when the brother reappeared.
So what?
According to my theory, they came here to Heidelberg
after they disappeared from the hospital.
Yeah, according to your theory.
And the two were raised by the current
foster parents of the sister.
However, the brother ran away shortly after coming here...
...leaving the sister behind with the parents.
You should write a book about this.
Although I doubt it would sell very well.
There is a chance that a search request
was filed for the brother.
And it might have appeared in a newspaper!
Please allow me to look through the
newspapers from nine years ago!
I'm begging you!
Please!
There must not be any more victims!
Please...!
The boss is allergic to hiring help.
Here are the compact editions and files
of the manuscripts from that time.
And these are the rough drafts
and files of the material used.
Thank you very much!
This is what they call a Japanese bow?
You are very welcome.
For the record, I just didn't want to listen
to your stupid stories anymore.
Just hurry up and go home when you are done.
Man, we get those kinds of weirdos sometimes.
Please...
Please let it be here!
The Missing
Good morning, Nina!
Oh, good morning.
Oh, I'm so glad!
You seem fine, Nina.
You scared us to death when you fainted so suddenly.
I guess you really didn't like the
man we introduced to you.
N-No, that's not it.
I just suddenly felt sick, that's all.
I should apologize to him.
Oh that's okay.
You don't have to worry about that guy anymore.
After talking to some people, it turned out that
Otto guy wasn't your prince on a white horse.
He said he didn't email anything like that to you.
I... I see...
You are saying that the reason you fainted
was because you saw that man?
Yes.
What was he like?
I only saw him for a split second,
so I don't really remember...
How did you feel?
What kind of impression did you get from him?
Somewhat nostalgic...
But that is not exactly it.
I can't quite explain it, but...
But?
It is okay, Nina.
You do not have to push yourself.
Absolute evil.
I can't quite explain it.
Yes, I felt the same thing as when I had those nightmares.
If we are talking about absolute evil,
then we are talking about religion.
I don't attend church either, but...
I think if I see him again, I'll understand.
You feel that your lost memories will come back?
Yes.
That is one method.
But I don't think you need to set that as a goal.
It's also important to think of the future
without pushing yourself to the limits.
Okay.
Everything is okay!
Go play some sports, sweat it out, and your anxiety will be gone.
You pulled an all nighter again, Mr. Mauler?
Yeah.
Oh, yes.
Are you the one who let that man use the reference room?
That man?
Yeah.
He was there just now, so I asked him,
and he said he had your permission.
He is still here?!
Damn it!
Hey!  You should...!
Hey!
Are you alright?
Go ahead.  Eat up.
Thank you.
It is good, right?
I always come to this restaurant for breakfast.
You don't go home?
Do you have a family?
I don't have one.
My wife left me.
I was too busy with work.
When I finally realized it, my wife had taken my
daughter and went back to her home.
Don't you want to go and get your wife?
Why?
She is the one who left.
Why should I go and pick her up?
Well, you seem to regret being so
occupied with your work.
Stop all that nonsense!
A man's first priority is his job.
Besides, if she leaves because she can't understand
this line of work, then so be it.
I'm sorry for saying such things.
Yeah, it's none of your business.
Oh, and one more thing.
You are smoking too much.
I'm warning you as a doctor.
I said it is none of your business!
Stop talking like my wife!
That means your wife was worried about your health.
That's none of your business.
Is that a birthday present for Nina?
Yes, I finally finshed knitting it.
She used to wear sweaters this small when she was little.
Dear, are you really going to tell her?
That she isn't our biological daughter?
I don't mind things the way they are right now.
Yeah, you are right.
We don't have to tell her.
Nina is our daughter, right?
I'm home!
Welcome back!
Oh, I'm so hungry!
Think about my future, huh?
Maybe Dr. Geitel's right.
"Tomorrow at 7 pm, on the night of your birthday,
we will meet at Heidelberg Castle."
Tomorrow...
At Heidelberg Castle...
I can't believe I'm starting at a pile of scraps with
you when I have so much of my own work to do.
Shouldn't you give up already?
Hey, Doctor....
If, and I'm just saying if...
If I, uh went to see my wife...
Do you think she would come back with me?
Sure, if you stop smoking.
What is wrong?
I found it!
"An eleven year old boy missing..."
"There is a possibility of abduction..."
"...but there have been no ransom requests or
messages from the kidnappers at this point."
"Number 16, Neckar Street."
Someone named Fortner requested a search!
There should be more information
about that article in here...
Oh, here it is.
What is wrong?
You said the killer was going to pick up his
sister when she turned twenty, right?
If the boy in this article is her brother...
Look, his birth date is written here.
Today is the twins' twentieth birthday.
Oh, Papa.  It's me.
I just got off work.
I'm going to meet up with a friend now, so...
Yeah, at Heidelberg Castle.
Okay.  Your mom is preparing a birthday
party for you right now.
Was that Nina?
Yeah, she said she'll be back after seeing a friend.
I wonder what kind of friend he is?
Nina's about that age now.
Maybe now I can finally understand...
...my memories...
I want to know who I really am...
So Doctor, what are you going to do if the
twin sister really was at the Fortner's?
First, the family is definitely in danger.
I'll call the police and ask them to guard the family.
You think the police will take action
just because of your theory.
Nothing has even happened yet.
It's too late to call for help after something has happened!
Nothing will happen!
It is all in your imagination.
Listen to me, Doctor.
Of the four murder cases...
...I went to the Köln crime scene to ask some questions.
That crime was special.
I couldn't see any purpose.
I didn't sense any purpose or hatred.
It felt like the point was just to end their lives.
If you see a crime scene like that,
you'll immediately understand.
You said a boy not even twenty was the killer, but...
...do you really think a child like that
can kill without any emotion?
That was not a child's doing.
It was something bigger.
What do you mean by "something bigger"?
That is the problem.
I can't find the right words for this case.
If I had to say something, it would sound like a cop out, but....
...that was the work of the devil.
If the killer appeared in front of me...
...I'd kill him without any hesitation.
Number 16, Neckar Street.
This is it.
Good evening!
Sorry to intrude on you so late!
Yes?
Excuse me.  I'm Mauler from the Heidelberg Post.
What does a newspaper reporter want with us?
I'd like to ask you about something.
About what?
Oh...
...it's about the search request that
you filed for a boy in 1986.
W-We don't want to talk about that anymore!
Please, can I ask you some questions?
Do you have a daughter?
The twin sister of the brother that went missing?
Please, answer me!
This is bad...
The cake.
She was preparing the cake for the birthday party.
You took in the twins nine years ago, didn't you?
The sister lives here, doesn't she?
Please go away!
We raised Nina as our real daughter until now.
Please, don't cause any problems for us!
Leave us alone!
You took the twins in nine years ago.
The brother had a scar on his head from surgery.
And the sister had amnesia.
Isn't that right?
Mr. Fortner!  We have to call the police immediately!
You and your daughter's lives are in danger!
Mr. Mauler...?
W-What do you mean?
Please let us speak with your daughter.
She is out right now.
W-Where?
She is at Heidelberg Castle.
She said something about meeting a friend.
Let me use your car!
Wait, we have to call the police first!
We don't have time to give the
police a thorough explanation!
Hurry and give me the keys!
Alright.  I'll call the police from here.
Please!
Hey, Doctor!
Be careful.
Like I just said, the boy is messed up.
Don't you dare die!
Mr. Mauler...
Come back alive.
When you do...
...I'll stop smoking, just like you suggested, you quack.
You wife will be happy.
Now then, how am I supposed
to explain this to the police?
Is our daughter safe?
What happened?
It is fine.
Let me borrow your phone.
Did something happen to our daughter?
Please tell us!  Please!
Calm down!
How could this happen?
The phone line has been cut!
Anna...
Please be safe, Anna!
It is way past the time we were supposed to meet...
I guess it was a prank after all.
Guess I'll go home.
You can't.
You have to wait here.
Who are you?
He asked me...
...to make sure you would wait for him here.
I said wait.  Don't you understand what I'm saying?
Wait!
You have to wait here!
He told me so!
Anna!
Anna...
No, you are Nina Fortner, right?
Do you remember me?
I am Doctor Tenma.
Thank God you are safe!
Anna...
Dr. Tenma
Now, let's go home.
You are the prince on the white horse?
Who are you?
Don't interefere...
Don't interfere!
She has to wait here.
Otherwise, I...
I...
I won't get my money!
He said no one would come!
Damn it!
Are you alright?
That surprised me!
Give me something to tie his hands with!
Who hired you?
I... I don't know!
When did he say he was coming?
I don't know!
He only said that he'll come here after he has
taken care of something important!
Oh, no...
Your house!
We have to hurry back to your house!
W-What do you mean?
I'll explain later!
Hurry, Anna!
Anna?
Hurry!
Damn it!  I can't get loose!
Please tell me!
Who are you?
And my name is not Anna.
It is Nina!
No.
When you were brought into my
hospital, your name was Anna.
And...
...your brother's name...
...was Johan.
Brother?