You look well.
Yeah...
How's work?
Everything going okay?
Yeah...
That's good.
And Rosemary?
How's she doing?
She's fine.
She's made lots of friends.
I see.
That's great.
Yeah, really wonderful.
She must be getting used to school by now...
I'm sorry.
I have to get going now, or...
I brought you a picture of Rosemary.
Will you let me see her?
How about here, two days from now?
I've stopped drinking.
My life has gone back to normal...
No... this might be the first time I've
actually lived a normal life...
Because I understand the significance of what I've lost...
I'll let her decide if she wants to see you or not.
Y-Yeah, you are right.
Alright, I have to get going.
O-Okay...
Yes?
Another coffee, please.
Article of Evidence
Doctor, what kind of man do you think he is?
Hey, Richard!
Yes?
Why do you think you are here?
You are here to receive my counseling, that's why!
I already told you, I'm not a fortune teller!
It's just years of experience dealing with clients, right?
So, who is the kid?
He's the one who found him.
This man was the one who found Fahren's corpse.
But supposedly he was just a friend.
Hey, Richard...
Yes?
Hard work is good, but you also need
some time to relax, you know?
I'm taking my time with it.
That's fine, then.
The truth is, Doctor...
What is it?
I... might get to see my daughter.
You must be excited, then.
I am!
However...
Even if you do see her, you won't be
able to get back what you've lost.
Always keep that in mind.
I will...
No matter what happens, never touch alcohol again!
Got that?
You don't have to worry about that.
You are going back to work now?
Yes.
How about it?
Don't you think it's about time you faced the
case that got you kicked off the police force?
Yes, of course.
He was seventeen years old...
A serial killer...
I shot... and killed him.
Because I got drunk while on duty.
Very good.
It's impossible to run away from that, even if you try.
You can't erase the truth.
But what is important...
...is to get past that incident.  Right?
Excellent.
You are a very good student.
Do I get a 100%
Nonsense!
I don't give out full points that easily!
Besides, people who score a 100% are boring.
Karl Neumann...
A student majoring in economics
at that University of Munich.
Just like Fahren...
...he told the prostitute that he's Schuwald's son.
Whether or not this is true has yet to be proven.
However, this boy knows something about the...
Yes?
Mr. Richard!
I've finished cleaning, so I'll be leaving now.
Oh, thank you, as always.
Oh, it's no trouble.
It's not easy for a guy to keep his place this clean.
Oh, no.  It's been much worse than this.
You've got a new picture of your daughter.
Yes...
I'll get to see her soon.
Oh, my!  I'm so happy for you!
I'm sure your daughter will be delighted!
I wonder about that...
Of course she will!
Any daughter would be happy to see her parent.
University of Munich
- Friedrich Emmanuel School -
Oh?  That's good.
So, were you able to hand in your report?
Karl Neumann...
Why won't you tell Schuwald that you are his son?
Are you a fraud too, or are you the real thing?
If you really are Schuwald's son...
A father always wants to see his child.
I'm sorry...
She said... she doesn't want to see you...
Oh, no.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
I'm kind of in a hurry...
I... I see.
It's okay.  Don't worry about it.
Goodbye.
Bye.
Yes!
Would you like to order something?
A... A whiskey...
Yes, sir.
Here you go.
Excuse me...!
Then I'll go to Dad's place!
Not now!
When you are older...
If you still want to meet him after you've grown up...
However, you mustn't want anything from him!
You mustn't hate him, even if he acts cold towards you!
Because I don't hate him...
Take this with you.
Your father meant to give you this when you were born.
"With none to love it..."
"...Lares' daffodil bloomed with pride."
"With none of heart..."
"...Pieria's trees rustled."
"O!  You furrows of blood that trail the
footsteps of nameless humans."
Splendid...
Huh?
Mr. Neumann, you really have
become a wonderful reader.
T-Thank you very much.
It's noteworthy that your Latin has improved
so much in this short period of time.
To tell you the truth, someone's been tutoring me.
He must be an excellent teacher.
Who is it?
Johan...
Johan Liebert.
Johan, huh?
He's perfect.
Yes.
Not just his Latin...
Not just in law and economics...
No, he has a perfect philosophy about everything.
He's so perfect, he's beautiful.
E-Excuse me, Mr. Schuwald...
If a guy like him...
What would you do if he were you real son...?
He smiled...
Schuwald smiled.
Looks like he thinks you are fit to be his son.
To tell you the truth, I was jealous.
Even though it's clear that you are better than me.
I hate myself for being jealous...
Why don't you tell him?
Tell Schuwald that you are his real son.
Cut it out!
I told you, I never intended to do that!
Even if I did tell him, he wouldn't believe me!
Even worse, he'd just see me as one
of those hyenas after his money.
I don't want that happen!
He doesn't know what kind of life my
mother led before passing away!
He doesn't know the feelings
that have driven me this far!
I want him to know the truth before
he thinks of me that way!
That's why you are going to tell him.
You are going to make him understand the whole truth.
He won't believe a thing!
There must be a way to make him believe.
Something that will make him
believe you are his real son...
I... I don't have anything like that...
Try to remember.
You should.
I said I don't have anything!
I have no intentions of telling him!
Then why are you making me teach you Latin?
Because you want him to be happy?
Because you want him to like you?
I'm thinking of quitting...
I'm going to quit.
...my part time reading job...
Thank you for worrying about me...
It's... okay now...
Johan...
I'll only tell you this.
The truth is...
...I do have some proof.
What?
But I have no intention of claiming to be his real
son by shoving something like that in his face!
My foster parents are coming to see me next week.
I've decided.
I'm going to...
I see...
Maybe... so you don't change your mind...
...maybe I should hold onto that
article of evidence for you.
I'm glad you are doing okay.  Right, mom?
Yeah.
I was worried if you were still eating properly.
Actually, I've been watching what I eat because
I'd get fat if I ate out all the time.
You mom's cooking would make you fat, also.
Because it tastes so good!
How's college going?
Have you made any friends?
Yeah, someone I can talk to about anything.
I see.  Those are the best kind!
I can tell everything is going great
just by looking at your face.
I'm really grateful that I can study like this.
Hey, why are you getting so formal all of a sudden?
I've been passed around by so many
foster parents all this time, but...
...you two have been really nice to me.
Because you are a wonderful child.
He's right, Karl.
Thank you very much, Mr. and Mrs. Lindner.
Won't you ever stop calling us that?
Have you decided...
...to become our adopted son yet?
You asked us to give you some time
after starting college, but...
...I think it's about time.
We believe in you .
You believe in us as well, don't you?
Of course.
Your real mother and father may
still be alive somewhere.
No matter what we do, we may never
become your real parents, but...
That's not true!
Because the two of you...
...are my real mother and father.
Oh, honey...
Let's have a toast!
We are going to order the special wine today!
Okay!
Hey, excuse me!
Can you bring us the wine menu!
Today's a special day!
Yes, hello?
Is this Mr. Neumann?
It's me.
Mr. Schuwald...
I heard about you quitting your part time job.
Y-Yes...
What a shame...
I'm sorry for being so selfish...
You did very well...
You did well to improve your Latin so much...
Thank you very much.
It's really a shame...
I'm really going to miss you...
Would you mind...
...reading something to me one last time?
Sure, I'd be happy to.
Will chapter three of "From Aoelis to Limnos" be okay?
Yes, that's fine...
"That deep sea of mystery..."
"...was it not wishing death even upon God Phoebus?"
"What pleasure did it have..."
"...other than to bring death to sons
and daughters like Cerberus?"
"Now, move on, Zeus murmured."
"Move on.  Move on."
"Dance in the shadowy temples of the gods."
"Oh, gods of Juno, dweller of the land, the sea..."
"...and the heavens."
"From the summit of the Parthenon..."
"Take... the forbidden apple... of Campania..."
"...and bring all here..."
"...to save my heart..."
"My heart..."
Mr. Schuwald...
That call was...
Well done...
It was the most heartfelt recitation I have ever heard.
Why did you keep this from me all this time?
T-That's...
This is indeed the rabbit's foot I
gave to your mother, Margot.
A good luck charm to bring you fortune from birth.
This is yours...
Karl...
I've made you suffer...
Father...
My son...
It's all thanks to him...
He's the one who told me everything...
He's going to be working as my secretary from now on.
He's a boy I can trust.