Petra, open up!
Petra!
You are going in to get looked at today no matter what!
I said you are wasting your time, no
matter how often you come here!
Why do you think I'm coming all the way out here?
Nobody called for you!
You stubborn, pigheaded woman!
Look who is talking, you quack!
I have not seen a doctor once since I was born...
...but as you can see, I am doing just fine!
Go on, get lost!
Why, you little...!
Doctor, we have an emergency!
Dr. Schumann!
What happened?
It is that drunkard, Fink!
He was hit on the highway.
So, is he conscious?
The guy who carried him in is treating him right now.
Someone who was just passing by is examining Fink.
What do you mean?
What is the meaning of this?
When I told him you were out on a house call, he just...
You allowed that person to treat him?
I'm sorry.
I tried to stop him, but...
...he said the patient might choke, so I
had to let him give first aid, at least.
Who was that man?
I'm not sure.
He left without giving his name.
Oh, he did write something on the chart.
"The patient said not to take him to a
doctor because he had no money..."
"...so please use this to pay for his medical fees."
God damn it!
Where are you going, Doctor?
What did he look like?
He was Asian, and he had a boy with him.
Umm... what about Mr. Fink's treatment?
Just leave him on the bed.
B-But that man only too emergency measures.
Those were not emergency measures.
They were perfect.
Petra and Schumann
Hey, Dieter...
You really can't follow me...
I can't just stay in one place.
You can't go to school like this.
You won't be able to make any friends.
I have a friend.
Who?
Tenma.
Listen to me, Dieter.
Was it you?
Were you the one who wasted your time at my clinic?
Don't insult me!
I'm well aware that Fink is just a penniless drunkard!
I've never even considered taking money from him!
No, I...
You are probably some elite doctor
from a famous hospital...
...showing mercy during your vacation...
...and having a good time!
Yo!
Welcome.
So, how is work?  Are you busy?
Let's go, Dieter.
Yeah, sure am.
Hey!
Listen to me when I am talking!
I'm terribly sorry...
...but we are in a hurry.
Fink was involved in a hit and run.
That lush?
Yeah.
So I'm looking for witnesses.
Oh, that must be tough.
Hey, Dr. Schumann.
What is Fink's condition?
It is not fatal.
Although I am worried about his drinking problem.
Who is this?
He is Dr. Chang.
He was my junior at my old college.
He is visiting this village because he is on vacation.
Dr. Chang?
Have we met before?
He treated Fink for me today...
...while I was off making a house call.
By the way, do you know where I went today?
I went to see your mother, Heinz.
My mom?
You should tell her to come to the clinic.
We may need to treat her immediately.
That is impossible.
That stubborn woman won't listen to anyone.
How can you say that like it doesn't concern you?
Don't worry about it.
My mom won't die that easily.
What...!
Besides...
She's been watching over me this long...
I don't think she has anything left to regret.
What did you say?
Hey, wait!
She's only just begun to live her own life!
Why did you lie to him?
For saving Fink.
Without your swift treatment, he would have died.
Thank you very much.
You turned white as a sheet when
you saw the policeman...
Are you...
Oh, well.  Doesn't matter.
At least now I'm sure you are not an elite
doctor from a famous hospital.
I can't thank you enough.
I don't know how I can repay you.
A debt, huh...?
Well, I guess I'll ask you to pay some of it off.
Ow!  Ow!
Your cast is a little off.
This might hurt a bit, but bear with it.
Ow!  Ow!
Alright, you will be fine.
You should be able to take it off in two weeks.
Hey Doctor, I got some nice apple brandy.
Wanna have a drink?
An injured man should not be thinking of such things!
You are making good progress.
You will be back on the farm in five more days.
Isn't that great, Mr Schöne?
Doctor, please take some potatoes with you.
They are very tasty this year!
I guess I'll come by in my truck next
time and fill it to the brim!
You have been a great help.
My area of expertise is internal medicine.
Though I'm doing my best in areas outside my expertise...
...I can't take care of everything by myself.
Amazing.
Yeah.  Even though there is nothing
here, it is a peaceful village.
No, that is not what I meant.
You are loved by the people here...
...and you really love them back.
Love?
I lost such admirable feelings long ago.
I'm merely doing my job.
Now then, help me with one more place.
This one is a pain!
You are so persistent!
Yeah, and I'll keep coming back!
I don't care how many times you come!
Just hurry and get lost, you quack!
As you can see.
She is the mother of that policeman you met.
She said she suddenly felt sick during her farm work.
I tried to take her to a clinic, but...
...she said she felt on the way there...
...and went back home by herself...
That is troubling.
Yeah...
Would you like me to try to convince her?
It might turn out the same, but...
Are you still dawdling about out there?
Where I dawdle is none of your business!
Now, now.
If you keep yelling like that, nobody
would want to come out.
I'm taking you to a clinic no matter what!
I can't lose my reason for living!
I... I just meant that I don't want to lose
the person I love to argue with.
A-Also, I would not be able to eat the goulash she makes.
You face is really red, mister.
W-What did you say, you brat?
Please open the door, Ms. Petra.
What?  Another doctor?
That stubborn woman is hopeless!
Why do you hate doctors?
Why, you ask?
They mess around with people's bodies
thinking they are gods or something!
Gods, huh?
There are times I wish I were a god.
Even though we try our best...
...mistakes will always happen.
I wish I could heal people perfectly, like god.
My heart hesitates every time I examine a patient.
Please, at least show us your face.
This smell is...
You are making goulash?
What?  You like goulash?
Yes.
Though it looks like Dr. Shumann only likes your goulash.
This is the first I have heard about it.
Every time I made it for him, he just sat and ate.
He is very shy.
This looks really good!
Geez, my shoulders ache so much...
...but I have to prepare dinner.
Your shoulders ache?
Ms. Petra, can you touch your chest with your chin?
Of course I can!
See?
Excuse me.
I can fit four fingers in...!
What kind of charm was that?
No, it is nothing.
How is she?
It is probably...
...a subarachnoidal hemorrhage.
What?
Petra!
We received this fax regarding the
search for a murder suspect.
Make me some copies.
Is your mom okay?
I heard she collapsed three days ago.
Don't worry.
She won't die, even if you kill her.
72 hours since her first spasm...
She is borderline.
We have to operate immediately!
I don't know if they will make it in time, even
if we call for a helicopter right now...
Can you do it?
Please!
If you can operate on her, do so!
Or else...
...I'll lose another loved one, and it will be my fault again!
You sure he was Kenzou Tenma?
Yes!
Okay, he could not have gotten very far yet.
Put up roadblocks on the highway!
It will be a great achievement if we catch him, Heinz!
Y-Yes, sir!
All officers, emergency deployment!
All right!
If everything goes well, I'll get a promotion!
Hey, Heinz.  You have a phone call.
Yes, Heinz here.
Oh, hi, Nurse.
My mom collapsed again?
If only I had forced her to check into
a hospital after the first spasm...!
You are my only hope, Dr. Tenma!
Just as I thought...
It is an aneurysm in the fork of the middle cerebral artery.
Damn it!
I don't even have a surgical microscope
or craniotome here.
If you have cerebral artery clips, I'll try operating
on her without a microscope.
But that will be difficult, even for you.
We can only try.
If her cerebral aneurysm ruptures again...
...I'm afraid she might not make it.
It is happening again, and it is all my fault...
What is wrong, Dr. Schumann?
You are not acting like someone who has taken
care of an entire village single handedly.
I don't know what happened in the past, but...
...we must work our hardest for the patient before us.
That is all doctors can do.
Yeah...
Hey, kid!
Is Dr. Schumann inside?
Yeah, he is operating right now.
Operating?  On my mom?
He did not bother taking her to a city
clinic... he is operating on her here?
It is okay.
Tenma is with him.
Tenma?
Blood pressure and pulse?
Blood pressure, 126/84.
Please, 88.
Amazing...
He doesn't even have a craniotome...
...but he opened her skull this quickly!
What are you doing?
As you can see, we are operating on your mother!
What do you think you are doing with that gun?
Put you hands up, Tenma!
Tenma!
We are in the middle of surgery here!
Are you trying to kill your own mother?
He is the one who is trying to kill her!
That guy is running around the
country suspected of murder!
What?
He has already killed a man in Heidelberg.
He is also a suspect for the serial murder
of several middle aged couples.
I never thought I would find you here!
I'm very grateful to my mom.
She is giving me a great opportunity!
Now, hurry and put your hands up!
Or else I'll shoot!
Get lost!
This is a sterile operating room!
You are bringing in germs!
If infection enters this room, your mother could contract
meningitis, and her life would be at risk!
Then hurry up and stop the operation!
Are you really trying to kill your mother?
Your mother is suffering from a
subarachnoidal hemorrhage.
She first collapsed three days ago.
If we don't treat her now, it will be too late!
Now get out!
You think you have a hostage or something?
You are thinking of taking my mother hostage...
...and getting out of this situation, aren't you?
Cerebral artery clips and forceps.
Cerebral artery clips and forceps!
Right!
That is my mom!
I won't forgive anyone who hurts my mom!
That is right, Petra is your mother.
But...
What have you done for your mom these past five years?
Have you even gone to see her since
you moved out to the city?
What have you done for your mother
in return for her raising you?
Listen!
People you cherish will disappear someday.
Do you still remember the taste of your mother's goulash?
Even now, Petra makes your share out of habit.
I end up eating your share as well.
It is delicious!
There is nothing else like it!
Dr. Tenma is fighting vigorously right
now, trying to save your mother.
If you want to taste that goulash again...
...then just get out!
See?  Everything is okay, thanks to Tenma.
Blood pressure, 140/86.
Pulse, 82.
Her vital signs are normal.
You should get some rest, Ms. Pionere.
But what about you, Doctor?
I'm okay, Go get some rest.
Okay, I will take your word for it.
Nice work.
You should get some sleep as well, Dr. Tenma.
I'm okay, too.
You were in that difficult operation
for several hours straight!
Better safe than sorry...
...so that once Ms. Petra's all better,
you can propose to her.
What do you mean by "propose"?
I-I thought you were asleep!
I won't go to sleep.
Not until I take that guy in!
Moreover, what did he mean by that?
Don't tell me you are...
Nonsense!
Nonsense...
I'm...
...not someone who can propose to others.
When I was working in a university hospital...
...I felt that talking to my patients was secondary.
I was more concerned with how to
solidify my position in the hospital.
I sided with the director's political faction...
I wrote the director's thesis for him...
And finally...
...I got permission to marry the director's daughter.
After that, I just kept marching
down the promotion highway.
I did not even look at my wife.
Yes...
If only I had looked at my wife, I would have noticed...
If I had been a real doctor...
For a long time, my wife had been plagued by
symptoms similar to that of the common cold.
If only I had paid more attention to her, I would have noticed.
It was liver failure.
With her last breath...
You finally... looked at me...
I don't have the right to love anyone.
That is not true.
You looked at them all.
You looked at everyone in this village.
Ms. Petra was saved because you looked at her.
You still want to take this man in?
You still think he is a murderer, after he
gave his all trying to save your mother?
Heinz!
This is Heinz.
Get me the chief.
Sir, I'm sorry.
It was someone else.
Please call off the roadblocks.
The person I saw wasn't Tenma...
I mistook him because he is Asian.
I'm terribly sorry, sir.  Please forgive me.
That doctor from the national hospital was very surprised.
He probably never thought to see such splendid medical
treatment from a clinic out here in the country.
Doctor!
You are gonna let that young doctor go?
I thought I would treat him to something
tasty, but he already left.
Tenma!
Don't go!
This village is safe!
You don't have to run anymore!
Dr. Schumann...
Dieter, you like it here too, right?
I see...
This village might be good for Dieter.
Not just Dieter.
We can protect you from the police
if you stay in the village.
Please take care of the people here with me.
This village needs you.
But...
I have to go.
Why?
Please take care of Dieter for me.
Tenma!  I'm coming with you!
If you stay here, we can save numerous lives!
Please, let us work together!
Save numerous lives...?
I...
...have to kill a certain man.
What?
Tenma!
What do you mean, Tenma?
You are not capable of such a thing!
You work so hard to save the lives of others!
He is going...
Tenma will go no matter what...
Go, Dieter.
If you are with him, he won't stray from his path.
Watch Tenma carefully.