Now, eat up!
This white sausage is the best!
Isn't it good...
Uh...
...Dieter, wasn't it?
Hey, if you don't start eating, Dieter's
going to have everything.
Don't worry, Dr. Tenma.
We're safe here.
Only regulars come here.
If anyone new comes in...
...Otto here will chase them away.
And because of that, business isn't getting any better.
Who ordered the spaetzle?
Oh, I did.
I set up a cot in the attic.
You'll sleep fine if you can stand the rats.
Sorry about this, Otto.
He may be brusque, but he's a good person.
Now then, you can't fight on an empty stomach.
Thank you.
You've even arranged a room for me...
I should be thanking you.
If you hadn't saved me back there,
I'd be in a morgue by now.
And I can only eat such good food when I'm alive!
Now, eat up!
I've contacted Dr. Gillen as well.
He was relieved to hear that we found you.
He also put an ad in the paper with a message for you.
"Let's reminisce about our cheating."
So you knew about it?
Yes.
Then, why didn't you contact him?
I...
...didn't want to drag him into this.
Don't be silly!
What you need most are friends.
So, you said you've been watching me all this time?
Because of Richard Braun's case...
Richard?
The case where he shot a young serial murderer...
...while he was still with the police.
When I was reading the article about him...
...Dieter saw the picture of the one
who got shot and told me...
...that he had been at Kinderheim 511.
Kinderheim 511?
It was an orphanage in East Berlin.
A rather special one, at that.
Dieter's foster father was a former official there.
He kept a large number of pictures
of the children who were there.
And what of that orphanage?
Johan had been there, too.
Are you saying that the boy Richard shot
and Johan are somehow connected?
I'm not sure.
I came here hoping to learn more about that, but...
...Richard passed away.
I saw you at his grave in the cometary, so...
Richard...
It feels like he brought you to me...
You did well to have made it this far on your own.
But you're not alone anymore.
We will prove your innocence!
Johan is right in front of us!
We have the photo...
Oh, no!
I must have left it in my office!
Showing you Johan's photo would have
cleared everything up...
The man who came after you probably...
Yeah, he probably destroyed it.
He said his name was Hesse.
He and his wife both came in for counseling.
I looked up his information and checked
out the address he gave me...
...but nobody named Hesse lives there.
Johan is right in front of us...
If he's in front of us, we can see him, right?
Yes.
We can clearly see...
...Johan.
Into the Daylight
Thalbach & Schuwald AG...
AG = Aktiengesellschaft = Corporation
This company is at the center of
Schuwald's financial group.
Recently, Schuwald has started appearing
more than he used to.
Around this time of day...
...he visits the companies he's affiliated with.
It's something Richard discovered while he was still alive.
Not only this company.
...but every company in the financial group...
...has started to grow after he began visiting.
Ever since a certain young man became
Schuwald's right hand man, that is.
Here he comes!
The man in the wheelchair is Schuwald...
...and the one pushing him is Karl.
And...
Well?  Were we mistaken?
You weren't mistaken...
Good!
This is the first time...
...I've seen Johan in broad daylight.
That's right!
Let's drag everything out into the daylight!
Now is the only time...
Yeah.
Now is the only time we can prove your innocence!
But for now, hide yourself in the attic of Otto's restaurant.
Soon, your innocence will be proven!
Richard's file was around here somewhere...
There it is.
This is it.
Good thing I brought it back home with me...
Soon.
Soon, Richard.
Your battle for revenge will soon be over!
We've cornered Johan!
We've found Dr. Tenma, a definitive witness.
All that's left is...
All that's left is find a witness from
the night Richard was killed.
There must be someone!
Then we can prove that Johan was with Richard that night!
Even if we can't...
Fahren, the student who claimed to be Schuwald's
son and committed suicide...
To determine whether Johan took
him to see that prostitute...
...we only need to find her, and
the proof will be established!
No, not only that!
If we dig into the past of the people
who claim to be Johan's parents...
...we'll know who Johan really is!
Since we've already found Johan Liebert's grave!
We've completely entangled "Johan" in our net!
Hey, Dr. Tenma...
You remind me of Richard when I look at you.
It's like you're carrying all the justice in the world on your shoulders.
But you're not alone!
You have Dieter!
And you have Dr. Gillen and me, too!
Everything is okay now.
You should get a good night's sleep tonight.
I...
...didn't want to get him involved.
This is the first time...
...I've seen Johan in broad daylight.
Now is the only time...
Y-You...!
Quickly, run!
Hurry!
Hello, Reichwein speaking.
Doctor, it's Gillen.
Oh, I was just about to call you.
I'm on my way over right now.
What's Tenma doing?
He's currently at the hiding place.
Tell him not to leave that place!
Something has been bothering me.
Me, too.
That his...
Dr. Tenma's reason...
...for going after Johan isn't to
prove his innocence, but to...
I don't like to think about it...
But I was worried about that myself.
Dieter...
Why are you here?
Tenma... told me to come here...
Wh...
Where is Tenma?
He left...
Where?!
He's going to do it...
Tenma's going to do it.
Stop him...
Mr. Reichwein, please stop him!
Tenma's going to become a murderer!
We'll stop here for today...
Come on, Doctor.  Please listen to what I have to say.
I'm just getting to the good part!
No, you can take your time and tell me about it next time.
The story about how I killed the third woman is the best!
Hey, Doctor!
Hey, listen to me!
What kind of sound do you think
she made when I strangled her?!
Hey, Doctor!
Listen to me, Doctor!
That woman!  She was...!
Where did you go, Tenma...?
We finally meet, Dr. Gillen.
Who are you?
My name is Lunge, from the BKA.
I've heard some rumors...
You've arrested several of the serial murderers...
...who are serving as my research subjects.
I've read your book as well.
Thank you.
It was a wonderful book.  "An Introduction
to the Transcendental Criminal Psychology."
No other publication delves so deeply into the heart of a criminal.
Especially the third chapter.
The inquiries on Heinz Kaul from pages 262 to 294.
I especially liked how you concluded
that the killer's childhood trauma...
...led to his crimes.
You're very familiar with it.
I'm honored that you read it so carefully.
My method of investigation also involves peering into the mind of the killer...
...and by becoming the killer...
You seem to have a lot of experience...
If you ever have some free time,
I'd like to talk more about it...
Because we both don't have much time...
...I'll ask you here.
You've been going to Munich quite
often lately, haven't you?
What about it?
Well, please have a seat.
I promise I won't take up much of your time.
You're meeting with the psychological
counselor, Dr. Reichwein.
Yesterday as well...
Yes.
Because he was a teacher I admired when I was in college.
When you were at Düsseldorf University...
Yes.
When you went to Düsseldorf University...
...there was a rather excellent neurosurgeon
in your class, wasn't there?
What are you trying to say?
Did you get to meet with Dr. Tenma?
What are you talking about...?
"Let's reminisce about our cheating. Rudi."
From May 1st to May 22nd...
...you put this three-line message in all the
major newspapers throughout the country.
I'm quite surprised.
Who would have thought that esteemed
people like you and Dr. Tenma...
...would have cheated when they were students.
It must be nice to have friends.
I wasn't friends with Dr. Tenma when we were students.
Last May in Oder Park...
...with your help...
...the Velbert police had Dr. Tenma surrounded
and almost captured him...
...but he got away.
That was because my wiretap malfunctioned, and...
One can infer that you assisted in his escape.
He's...
Dr. Tenma is innocent!
Oh?
I want you to listen carefully.
The three murders at Eisler Memorial
Hospital in Düsseldorf...
The patient murdered at the construction site...
The murders in Heidelberg...
The middle aged couple murders
occurring all over Germany...
...were all done by someone other than Tenma!
This is the conclusion that I, a criminal psychologist,
have come to after interviewing Tenma in person!
I see.
So, where is he now?
He's on the move again.
Why does he run?
If he's innocent, why does he run away?
He's not running away!
Then why didn't he tell you where he is
going, even though you're friends?
I have evidence that he's not the killer.
Take a look at this.
This paper analyzes all the information about the case.
This took a lot of work.
Now do you understand?
Yes...
The unnatural death of a young man named Fahren,
who claimed to be Schuwald's son...
The unnatural death of former police officer Richard
Braun, who was investigating the case...
The trouble caused by those scrambling to become
wealthy Schuwald's illegitimate son...
In the center of everything lies a young man.
His name is the same as the one Tenma
claimed was the true killer...
Johan Liebert...
Additionally, a person of the same gender and name...
...was found in a grave in Brunthal.
Oh top of that, Dr. Reichwein, who took
over Mr. Braun's investigation...
...was also targeted by someone the other day.
I understand everything now.
It's impossible.
It's impossible to prove that these cases are all connected.
Because he understands that best,
Tenma went into hiding.
Am I wrong?
The way you move your hand...
Please don't mind it.
It's a little tool for memorization.
From a psychological point of view...
...it seems as though the uncertainty in your
heart is revealing itself in your hand.
It's the same with me.
Instead of my hand, I use my cassette recorder.
But everything recorded onto these
cassettes is entirely objective.
However, the information memorized by your hand...
...is affected by your subjectivity.
That's probably how you've always worked, isn't it?
The memories created by that hand are absolute...
...and you never have any errors in judgment, right?
Do you have a family?
What is your hobby?
You live only for work, don't you?
Have you ever made a mistake?
Maybe you're terrified of making a mistake?
To you, Tenma has to be the bad guy.
Or else your identity will fall apart.
Look at the truth!
This is a picture of Johan Liebert himself!
Can you prove they are all lies told by Tenma?
He...
Where is this boy right now?
He's a student at the University of Munich.
Right now, he's one of Schuwald's secretaries.
May I keep this photograph?
Starting now, this is police business.
Perhaps I've made a very big mistake.
Where is Dr. Tenma right now...?
H-He should be in Munich.
Yes, this is Lunge.
Contact the Munich police.
Request an all-points bulletin.
Tenma is in Munich.
A sniper rifle?
I have no idea what you are talking about.
You should have gotten a call from Mr. Heitmeyer
in a mountain retreat in Fussen.
10,000 marks up front.
I've prepared it.
This order is somewhat difficult to fill, so it'll take a week.
Until then, do something about that body of yours.
Even if you lay down the money
and get the right equipment...
...it'll just be a pearl thrown before swine.
Next in the news...
The reception party to be held next week
for the Munich Electronics Expo...
...will be located at the provincial Chamber
of Commerce and Industry building.
Important economic leaders are already gathering there.
With the EU integration, the Bayern Industry will carry the New Media Network on it's shoulders.
It will be the largest trade fair ever seen.
At a reception...
...Hans Georg Schuwald appeared for
the first time in twenty years...
...and was showered with applause.
Even though Mr. Schuwald attended
in his wheelchair, he looked well...
...and showed off his good health.