You can't sleep in a place like this!
I'm fine, I'm fine.
Leave me here.
You left her there.
Am I right?
You left your mother there, didn't you?
The next morning, you were told...
that your mother froze to death.
But at the time, you thought to yourself...
that it wasn't your fault.
You only left her there because she asked you to.
That's exactly right.
It wasn't your fault.
You only let those who wanted to die, die.
You aren't wrong. You're right!
You set them free from the misery of living.
Eva wants to die, too.
Just then, the devil arrived.
I passed by making sure not to look at the devil.
I can't look...
I must not look at him.
I recited that to myself, like a child.
Eva wants to die, too.
Please kill me!
Leave me here.
Kenzou...
I...
won't be a part of the devil's plans.
Because nobody...
wants to die.
The Man Who Knew Too Much
Where's the woman?
Eva isn't here anymore.
Where did you send her?
I finished her off.
Don't lie, Martin.
You can still...
I'm not lying.
Pathetic.
What is?
Losing your life for a woman.
You're awake.
5 Minutes Ago
They're here.
Their car just stopped outside.
It's only a matter of time.
I stole a maid's uniform.
Put that on and escape through the back door.
What about you?
If we leave together...
it's like asking to be caught.
You'll be killed if you don't run!
If I'm by myself, I'll manage.
Go to the place written in the note on the desk.
It's Tenma's hotel.
Hurry up and change.
I'll be waiting for you at Frankfurt Central Station.
Let's run away together.
Knock it off.
This isn't the time for jokes!
Listen!
Going to Tenma's place is the only way you'll be safe...
and it's what you wanted!
That's an order!
Hurry up and go!
You have no right to give me orders.
It was a joke.
I'm going.
Don't do anything reckless that'll get you killed.
I have no obligation to go that far for you.
Goodbye...
That's right.
I have no obligation...
I have no obligation to go that far for that woman.
One...
Two...
Three...
Four...
I'm surprised I lived through that.
Frankfurt Central Station, huh?
Out of bullets...
Guess I'm out of luck.
Idiot!
Aim for the head!
In a suburb of Frankfurt...
four people died in a gunfight at
the Regen Motel in Sossenheim.
It is thought that the fight was an internal gang dispute.
The police are now questioning the people staying
at the motel, to get a better picture...
Robby...
Did you hear that, Robby?
It's the story of my fight...
Robby...
We're here, Martin.
Are we at Frankfurt Station?
Hey, Doctor...
I've done all the emergency treatment I can...
but I can't do the rest here.
Let's go to a hospital.
Don't...
I already know...
it'd be useless...
Eva...
Where is Eva...?
What happened to Eva?
She... didn't come here...?
What are you laughing about, you idiot?
Just keep quiet!
I can't do that.
Listen to me, Dr. Tenma.
I don't know where to start.
I've learned... too many things...
The Red Rose Mansion experiment is still going...
Do you understand... what I'm saying...?
And...
the devil got himself a disciple...
That man...
is trying to create a dictator...
That man?
The man with glasses...
The survivor from the Red Rose Mansion...
Peter... Čapek...
That man...
is trying to control the devil, but...
The devil is...
The devil is more terrifying...
More terrifying...
Hotel Jahreszeit...
Room 606...
That's where the devil's disciple is...
You must not... look at the devil...
You must not play a part in the devil's plans.
Nobody... wants to... die...
Martin!
I am... so fortunate...
I don't have to look at the devil anymore...
Eva...
Eva is...
at Frankfurt Central Station...
I'm sure she bought two tickets for us...
so we could go as far as we can...
As far as we can...
Is Eva waiting for you?
Please protect Eva for me...
Protect Eva...
Don't die.
You have to go to the station, right?
You don't have to wait there, you know.
You've still got plenty of time before the first train comes.
Are you waiting for someone?
It's a guy, isn't it?
I can tell these things.
I've been working at the station for a long time.
Then, can you tell if someone will come or not?
I can't tell something like that.
I'm not a fortune teller.
However, the fact that you have someone
to wait for is a happy thing.
Whether the person comes or not.
Happy?
That's right.
You don't get the chance for something
like that when you're my age.
Happiness, huh?
Oh, I guess the person you're waiting for is coming.
Kenzou...
Martin is...
dead.
Looks like he wasn't the one she was waiting for.
He came to my place to give me
some important information.
With the last of his strength...
Hurry up and run.
Eva.
There's still time before the first train comes.
Will you keep me company for a bit?
Sure.
You sure you don't want alcohol?
Martin...
He hated alcohol.
I see...
To Martin.
It's been a while.
Yeah.
Are you eating properly?
You look pretty worn out...
Yeah.
Strange, isn't it?
Here we are, holding a funeral for Martin.
He was a good person...
I did terrible things... to such a good person...
I made him wear the same suit and tie...
that I once gave you.
I'm the worst...
I'm the absolute worst...
Why am I still alive?
I even gave false testimony against you...
that made you out to be guilty of a crime.
So why am I still alive and well?
Because Martin protected you.
Why would he protect me?
Why would he protect a woman like me?
"Nobody wants to die."
That's what Martin said.
He said he was happy.
He said you were waiting for him at the station.
That alone made him happy.
Munich...
Go to Munich.
A friend of mine who's a psychological counselor is there.
Dr. Reichwein.
You know him?
Yes.
For now, ask Dr. Reichwein to hide you.
He'll treat you well.
Then go to the police.
Tell them that you're being targeted by
The Baby's organization in Frankfurt.
And how you're being targeted by Roberto.
Tell them everything.
I'll tell them about you, too.
You didn't kill anyone.
Everything was Johan's fault!
I'll tell them everything!
So you should come to Munich, too!
He's right in front of me.
He's very close.
You saw him at the party, didn't you?
Johan is right in front of me.
I have to end this.
I can't...
lose any more people like Martin.
You understand, don't you?
I have to bring this to an end.
I'll write a letter to Dr. Reichwein.
I'll include all the information I know.
Kenzou...
Now, get going.
But Kenzou...
The only way you can help me...
is by going to Munich and telling them everything.
You did well to bring us and Johan together.
I thank you.
I heard rumors that someone like him was in Frankfurt...
so we asked you to help us identify him.
Pardon me for interrupting you during your meal.
You have a phone call.
Hello, it's me.
Johan?
I see.
Where?
An apartment on Haldecker Street?
An apartment on Haldecker Street...
Johan...
I can bring this to an end, too.
Hotel Jahreszeit...
Room 606...
That's where the devil's disciple is...
You're the one who wants a gun?
Yes.
There are many different types of guns.
I want the biggest one you can give me.
A beginner can't handle a big gun.
What are you trying to shoot?
A devil.
Yes
Cherish what you know is true in this world.
Ima kono sekai de wakaru koto mitsumete
Yes
Please believe in the kindness of your eyes
Anata no hitomi no yasashisa wo shinjite
Make it home to your land of harmony
Make it home to your land of purity
Make it home