Your mom threw you away!
She threw you away like trash, along
with that drunk dad of yours!
Don't ever leave this trash dump again!
The Town of Slaughter
Sorry, but would you mind getting out of here?
If you want to drink, pay off your tab first.
I've got cash.
See?
I've got enough for today.
I don't have anything to serve to someone
who takes the money his son worked for.
What did you say?
I said leave.
He's suspicious.
You're talking about the incident with Mr. Konrad?
Maybe he was the one who shot Mrs. Hillman's dog, too.
He doesn't have the guts to fire a gun.
That's true!
He's just a drunken coward!
Man!
How am I supposed to search in this rain?
Hey, Merkel!
We should call it off, too!
I found him!
Merkel!
Mer...
Merkel?
T-This is Laufer!
Please respond
Someone!
Someone, please answer me!
I'll take your gun, too.
He doesn't have the guts to fire a gun.
That's true!
He's just a drunken coward!
There are dead bodies strewn all over town...
It's like a battlefield...
Wim?
What's wrong, Wim?
It's okay.
Calm down.
It's me.
I...
Calm down.
Now, let go of the gun.
I don't really remember...
I shot them, didn't I?
They kept teasing me...
So I...
Wim, you...
It's okay.
Calm down.
Everything is okay now.
Don't be scared.
Try to calm down and remember everything.
Who gave you this gun?
Hang in there!
I'm amazed that you got here with that leg, Laufer!
C-Call the station...
The phone lines are down.
H-He took my gun...
Someone from this town?
No.
He was an outsider I've never seen before...
Let's apply first aid, and then...
Was he a friend of yours?
What are you talking about?
How many of your friends have come to this town?
What are you implying?
You did manage to spread quite
a few guns around, though.
You even gave one to a child like this.
Wim!
A gun?
Don't tell me you...!
"You aren't trash."
"Don't take them seriously."
"There was a reason you were born."
It seems that you've been encouraging him by saying that.
He didn't fire the gun.
All the bullets are still in it.
Wim kept to what you taught him.
I'm proud of you, Wim.
It's okay.
It's okay now, Wim.
However, the town is full of dead bodies.
How many did you distribute?
How many guns did you distribute in this town?
How many people took guns from you?
Don't make me any angrier!
Something terrible will happen if you make me angry!
He looked just like our grandson!
What?
He looked just like our grandson who passed away.
"He"?
He knew a lot about us.
He was just like our grandson.
Who is this person?
You were writing a letter to your dead grandson.
So you were passing on information to "him."
Who is he?
He's probably after me.
His target is probably me.
Yes.
That's right, Mr. Poppe.
No.
Franz Bonaparta.
The heavy rain that has been falling in southern Germany...
...has caused significant amount of damage to Bayern.
The state has raised its warning level to grade four...
Hey, you're smoking too much!
as the damage continues to mount.
Who cares? At least I quit drinking.
You should quit smoking, too.
Hey, Dieter.
What have you been drawing?
What do you think? Does it look like him?
Who?
Tenma, of course!
I'd turn that over to the police next time.
Those guys don't believe the important details.
That's why I'm going to tell them.
That this is the man I was talking about.
That he has gone by himself to kill a monster.
Tenma will come back, won't he?
Now, here is the reported damage for each area.
Due to the flooding of the Elgar River, several places are blocked.
Therefore, the railroad is out of service in both directions.
Now because several locations have no power,
it's difficult to make phone calls...
I received this letter three days ago.
After consulting with Dr. Gillen...
we've decided that we shouldn't hide it from you.
Please.
"To Nina."
"I'll be waiting for you in Ruhenheim."
Johan...
You think so, too?
You told us before what Johan is trying to do.
A "perfect suicide," right?
As well as how numerous innocent people will die.
Ruhenheim.
There's a country town in southern
Germany with that name.
There's a chance that Tenma went there.
I have to go.
Please let me go there.
This is a very strange feeling that I'm getting.
At first, I thought you were just a character
from a certain person's imagination.
Yes, just like the characters that
appear in your picture books.
For years, I've been carrying out my investigations
by collecting objective data.
However, this time, I completely ignored the data
and purely followed that man's imagination.
As I followed the clues, partially for my own amusement...
I met a young man who had entered the Red
Rose Mansion many times in Czechoslovakia.
He was your son.
This postcard you sent him with a hand-drawn picture.
Under your real name, Klaus Poppe, signed K. P.
Even after arriving at this location...
and seeing you with my own eyes...
I still feel strange.
I feel as if a character from a storybook
has escaped from its pages.
However, this is reality.
In the list of names I had researched of
people who escaped Czechoslovakia...
the name "Klaus Poppe" was indeed on it.
Right before the Berlin Wall fell...
you fled to this land.
What were you running from?
People like myself?
Kinderheim 511 was created in East
Germany based upon your concept.
I was created there.
Were you trying to run away from people like me?
I can tell.
What he...
What the young man named Johan is trying to accomplish.
And right now...
that's exactly what's happening to this town.
Another gunshot!
A ton of people were dead on the way to this hotel, too.
Something is happening to this town!
Hey!
Please hurry and take me away from this town!
I can't do that right now.
The roads have been closed.
Oh, geez!
What are you doing?
Coming and going from the hotel.
And every time you come back, you take a shower.
I feel sick from the gunpowder and the smell
of blood that's covering the town.
Now, calm down.
I ordered a hot cup of tea from the front desk.
It's okay.
There's nothing to be scared of.
Everything will have disappeared
by the time the rain stops.
Disappear?
What will disappear?
All the memories.
We have some conditions if you're going to go there.
Dr. Gillen must go with you.
Also...
I can't let you have a gun.
I don't need a gun.
I'm going to get ready to leave.
Also, please hurry and do what we just discussed.
Dieter and Eva...
and you, Dr. Reichwein.
As well as Mr. Schuwald, Karl, and Lotte.
Everyone who knows Johan should go into hiding.
Johan is trying to erase all the memories.
Now, hurry! Before Dieter notices!
My memories of Dieter...
My memories of you, Dr. Reichwein...
My memories of Karl and Lotte...
My memories of the Fortners...
My memories of Tenma...
I have many memories that I don't want to forget.
Even though I have memories that I do want to forget...
Johan...
What about your memories with Johan?
I must not erase them.
A police officer...
His gun has been taken...
Don't move!
Please...
save the town...
Who shot you?
They're shooting... all over town...
At first, several armed men came in...
Eventually, even the townspeople picked up guns...
and started shooting each other...
I have to go...
Have to call for help...
I have to save... the children...
I have to...
Johan...
The first time I heard that name...
was in 1995.
It was during the testimony of a certain neurosurgeon.
Dr. Tenma...
Then you're admitting that your deduction was wrong?
No.
He is still an important reference for me.
Johan is just a fictional character to me.
Fictional character...
Those are the words that captivated
me during my vacation.
How can a real man become a fictional character?
The answer is simple.
All the people who know him...
All the people who know his past...
Everyone must be erased.
And ultimately, it'll become like the ending
to one of your books, Mr. Bonaparta.
"Even though he now had a name, there was
no one left to call him by his name."
"Johan."
"It is a wonderful name."
If that's what's happening in this town...
If I was Johan, that's what I would do.
I'm also a fictional character.
I'm not a man named Neumaier
who signed the hotel registry...
nor am I Wolfgang Grimmer.
I am nobody.
Then let's disappear together.
Along with the man who
stole my memories and my name.
I was waiting...
I was here, simply waiting for my sentence...
I'm not afraid to die.
However, I don't know how I can atone.
That's why I've decided to accept
whatever happens here, and...
You were waiting?
You're not afraid to die?
Do you understand what kind of sin you've committed?
Do you understand what it means to destroy
the boundary between good and evil?
Do you understand what happens to people
if you awaken the monster inside them?
People...
People have to think of food as delicious...
They have to enjoy a picnic on a holiday...
They have to think a beer after work tastes great...
People...
People feel sad from the bottoms of their
hearts when their children pass away...
I won't let you die.
I'm taking you away from this town,
and I'll publicize everything
I'm going to show the world the identity
of the monster that you've awoken!
Until then, I'll protect you.
Where is Johan?
I... I don't know.
Then there's a man who's controlling this massacre.
Where is he?
I... I don't know.
Another gunshot.
Is anybody here?
Can you see it?
See? I'm not carrying anything.
It's okay.
Don't be scared.
I came to help.
Please, rest assured.
It's dangerous here. Do you understand?
You have to leave the town.
Stop crying!
I'll take you to the entrance of the forest!
Can you all run?
T-There is a man giving orders in Hotel Bergbach!
I see.
However, this is the only gun...
These two were outside.
We're terribly sorry.
This all happened because I won the lottery.
If we had only told someone sooner
about Konrad's dead body...
Before the entire town went crazy...
You bought these?
I... I haven't fired a single shot yet!
It's the truth!
Let me borrow this one and this one.
You protect this hotel.
What about you?
Even ordinary townspeople are carrying guns.
I'm a detective.
I can tell the difference.
Oh, that's right. Mr. Grimmer.
When this job is done, let me buy you a beer.
Yes, please.
A delicious beer.
Now!
Run!
Live!
Yes
Cherish what you know is true in this world.
Ima kono sekai de wakaru koto mitsumete
Yes
Please believe in the kindness of your eyes
Anata no hitomi no yasashisa wo shinjite
Make it home to your land of harmony
Make it home to your land of purity
Make it home