Please tell me!
Who are you?
And my name isn't Anna.
It's nina!
No.
When you were brought into my
hospital, your name was Anna.
And...
...your brother's name...
...was Johan.
My brother?
Johan...
Anna...
House of Tragedy
Mr. Fortner!
Mr. Mauler!
Mr. Mauler!  Mr. Mauler!
Mr. Fornter!  It's me, Tenma!
I brought Anna... I mean Nina back safely!
Mr. Mauler!
I'll call the police from here.
There are no signs that the police were here...
Oh, no!
Come back...
Please!
Come back to life!
Please come back to life!
Please...
I beg you!
Please!
Mr. Mauler...
Here's the cigarette that you loved so much...
Mr. Mauler!
Back then...
I killed him...
...killed him...
Kill... him...
I... killed him...
I killed him...
Nina.
I killed my brother back then!
I brought him back to life.
The phone line has been cut.
We have to hurry and get out of here!
He will come here to take you away.
Are you okay?
We're the police.
We received a report and came over.
Please excuse us.
Let us look around a little.
Oh my god.
This is terrible.
Are you two alright?
Either of you hurt?
That is good to hear.
Reinforcements should be arriving soon.
Let's leave the crime scene to them...
...and have you two come down to
the station to give a statement.
Is she the daughter of the victims?
I feel sorry for her.
I see...
So you didn't get a look at the killer?
I never thought something like that would
happen in a peaceful town like this.
What country are you from?  China?
No, I'm Japanese.
My name is Tenma.
Oh, you are from Japan?
What a horrible situation to be in.  In a
foreign country so far from home.
Calm down.
It is okay now.
Excuse me, but where are we going?
The police station.
But the Heidelberg Station should be
towards the middle of town.
We came from the neighboring Mannheim Station.
Why are they taking us to a station in another town?
We will be arriving in about fifteen minutes.
O-Okay.
They received a report?
They said they came because they
received a report, didn't they?
But whose report?
The phone line was cut.
This car came without the siren on.
Do the police remove the primary witnesses...
...without first preserving the crime scene?
But... their police badges looked real...
That is blood!
Oh, no!
Could they...
Could these men have...
E-Excuse me!
O-Officers...
We are saved!
We are looking for a hit and run driver,
so I would like to ask for your cooperation.
E-Excuse me...
Hey!
If it isn't Detectives Messner and Müller!
Keep up the good work.
Are you heading back to the station?
Hey, this is a brand new car!
What is going on here?!
It is nice!
It will be worn out soon enough...
...since we treat it badly.
E-Excuse me.
Umm, she said she's not feeling well...
So can she go outside to get some fresh air?
Oh, s-sure.  Go ahead.
Did those two do something?
No, it is nothing like that.
What is going on here?!
Are they real detectives?
But what about that blood stain?
Whose report did they receive?
Why did they come without their siren on?
What should I do?
What should I...
Are you alright, Dr. Tenma?
How...
How did you know?
I told you my name, but I never said I was a doctor!
How did you know that?!
There is a general store nearby.
I managed to get some clothes to change into.
I got some bread, sausage and cheese.
I also had them fill the thermos with some warm coffee.
I know you might not be hungry, but you have to eat.
First things first.  You should get changed.
Your body is freezing.
A lot of people... were dead...
My brother and I...
...were walking among them together...
The world was...
...it was like we were the only
two people left in the world...
Where were you?
Can you remember?
We crossed the border...
My uncle and aunt cheered us up...
They were very kind to us.
And then my brother said...
...that he had the perfect plan.
Soon afterwards...
...my uncle and aunt died.
For some reason, those who are kind to us...
...every one of them...
...just dies.
But on that night...
...I found out why.
On that rainy night...
The Lieberts' case?
My brother shot them.
He... shot all those people...
My brother killed them all!
That is why... I picked up the gun.
That is why I aimed it at my brother.
Then, he said it...
He was laughing when he said it...
He said to throw the gun out the window after I shot him.
And to aim straight for his head.
I shot him...
I aimed for his head...
Why did you save him?
If only you had not saved my brother...
...Papa and Mama would not have been killed!
Why did you save him?
You stay here.
I'm going to the police.
If those two detectives from last night were real...
...it would mean that Johan has
connections with the police.
But we can't just stay here like this.
Listen to me, Nina.
Johan is trying to take you away with him.
If someone comes after you, hide.
Eat well, drink the warm coffee, and take a nap.
That is how people live.
You are still alive.
Think about what you should do.
Think about your future.
Do you have any leads on the killer?
Heidelberg Police Station
Any connections to the middle aged couple murders
that have been occurring throughout the country?
Like I said, we are putting all our
resources into the investigation.
But I cannot give you any specific information at this time.
According to what we have learned...
...the Fortners had a daughter.
Where is she right now?
That is also currently under investigation.
Why was the reporter named Mauler also
in their house when they were killed?
Who was the Japanese man seen together with him?
A Japanese man?
That guy smells suspicious.
Is the murder at Heidelberg Castle that occurred roughly
at the same time the work of the same man?
Heidelberg Castle?
He was killed, too?!
Anyway, detailed information will
be given out when we are ready!
Excuse me!
Please let me through!
Excuse me...!
Thank you for coming all the way from the
Mannheim Station to help us out.
This will really help, Detectives Messner and Müller!
Just let us know what you want us to do.
We are happy to help.
What is the current status of the investigation?
Let us discuss this thoroughly inside.
They were real!
Those men... were real detectives!
What should I do now?
Yes, the Heidelberg Post.
What?
I can't hear you!
The editorial department is packed right now!
Who are you?
Hey, can you guys keep it down?!
I'm on the phone!
Hello?
I'll bring an important witness with
me and be there at 5 o'clock.
Please do not report this to the police.
Are you serious?  This is not some kind of false lead, is it?
Hello?
If I can't go to the police...
...only the newspaper is left.
It is the only place that can ensure Nina's safety.
Mr. Mauler...
Hey, don't come into the room without permission.
And besides, even though you are from the BKA,
You are here to investigate the murders
of the middle aged couples, right?
We only have material on the man who
was killed at Heidelberg Castle here...
...Inspector Lunge.
Oh, pardon me.
I was just curious.
Your case and this one both happened at the same time.
It was not done by the same person.
I see.
This man has the marks that suggest he was bound.
Did you find rope or something nearby?
No.
When the victim was found, his
hands were already untied.
Oh, is that so?
There are four routes from which
to escape the crime scene.
The answer is...
...somewhere he wouldn't be suspected of going.
He took the footpath as his escape route...
The well lit walkway...
Found it.
Nina, it's me!
It is me, Tenma!
Nina!
You don't have to hide anymore.
Nina.
Oh, no!
Nina!
Where is she?
Nina...
Were you taken away?
I should not have left her alone!
Dr. Tenma, it is not your fault.
You only performed your duty as a doctor.
It is not your fault.
Please eat the sandwiches.
And please, get some sleep.
Please stay alive.
And... please save as many lives as you can.
Nina Fortner.
Nina...
What are you planning to do now?
Are you going to kill him again?
It was me who brought him back to life.
It was me who brought that monster...
...back to life!