You should... hurry up and run...!
The police are coming...
B-But...
Dresden...
Wait at the train station...
Hurry and give me the message.
Here.
Cedok Bridge...
The Three Frogs...?
And my father also said this...
"If the monster you are after is a twin..."
"the mother of the twins..."
"is alive in Prague."
Here!
There!
Hey, give it back!
Here, pass!
Nice!
Over there!
Stop it! Give it back!
Grimmer
How's it going, Mr. Grimmer?
Were you able to find what you were looking for?
After the unification of the East and West...
the school system was completely changed...
so that's the only old material we have left.
No, thank you for your trouble, Director Albrecht.
It's actually rare to see this much left.
Since after the Berlin Wall came down...
most of the sensitive documents
of old East Germany disappeared.
However...
it's certain that juveniles were oppressed
in the orphanages of old East Germany.
But...
it's really hard to find documents to prove that.
I'd imagine so...
The orphanages of old East Germany were...
often under the jurisdiction of the
Ministry, of Health and Welfare.
The problem children were those whose parents...
were criminals, anti-government advocates, spies,
illegal immigrants, or unsuccessful refugees.
Among the orphanages that housed
those types of children...
there was a Kinderheim with a really bad reputation
under the jurisdiction of the
Ministry of Domestic Affairs.
In that special orphanage...
I'm interested in the poor treatment and unlawful
personality corrections that were conducted.
So I want to uncover as many details as I can about that.
To find out exactly what went on in there.
Exactly, huh?
I see. That's quite an investigation.
Everyone involved was either exiled or silenced, right?
That's right.
The school nurse, Mr. Schnur, was involved as well...
Mr. Schnur?
He was part of the teaching staff at Kinderheim
62 in old East Germany.
I asked for an interview, but I was rejected.
You should be careful.
There's a chance Mr. Schnur was abusing children
when he was in old East Germany.
Oh, may I make copies of these?
O-Oh, sure! Go ahead!
Mr. Grimmer, you're a journalist who
was born in old West Germany, right?
No, I was a reporter for a newspaper
in Leipzig on this side.
I didn't know people fighting for human
rights came from the East.
Oh, come now.
I was traveling the world as an overseas
correspondent back then.
It was a job given to me by the government.
You understand, don't you?
I was a spy.
Here we go!
That's a lot of luggage.
It's full of documents I found in various
places in old East Germany.
I'm looking forward to a good report.
So, where are you headed now?
Prague, in the Czech Republic.
Thanks for all your help, Director.
They got you pretty bad back there, didn't they?
In the end, they took your shoes, huh?
Stop crying already.
People can live without shoes.
Since we were all born with bare feet.
However...
those who pick on others by taking away their shoes...
are the worst.
You don't have to cry because of such losers.
See you later.
Is it hard to walk in them because they're too big?
Dresden-Station
Um, excuse me...
Huh?
Do you have a minute?
Sure.
What's wrong?
The truth is that...
I'm in some trouble...
The bag that had my passport in it was stolen.
Your passport?
Oh, that is a problem.
Yeah, it is...
I was on my way to see my little sister in Vienna...
Yesterday, I received a call saying
that my sister had collapsed, so...
She collapsed?
Then you have to hurry up and get to her!
We should go to the police right away!
N-No, I've already done that!
The thing is... my sister doesn't have the
money to cover her medical expenses...
Oh, no. That's awful!
And my wallet was also in the bag that was stolen...
I can't go now, but...
if I could just send her the money, she'll be saved!
But now, I can't even do that...
How much do you need?
Oh, no! I don't need that much!
All I need is enough to get her to a
hospital to have her looked at...
I can only give you this much...
Oh, thank you!
Danke schon!
I'll pay you back, I swear!
Oh, please write your address on this.
No, don't worry about it.
If it'll save your sister, then it's nothing.
T-Thank you!
God bless you!
Take care of your little sister!
How could you give money to someone like that?
That was an obvious lie!
A lie?
Those guys are always looking
for marks at the train station.
You shouldn't let them trick you like that.
I was tricked...?
Express line to Prague will depart
from Platform Seven at 3:15.
Oh thank you.
That really helped. Thanks!
It's nothing.
Thank you for before.
Can I sit here?
Go ahead.
Where are you headed?
Prague.
You're Japanese, right?
Konnichiwa.
Oh, hello.
I've been to Japan.
I see...
I wonder how many years it's been?
It was 1982...
Oh yes. I went to Akihabara.
I remember I got a lot of things like wiretaps
and high tech equipment and material.
Also, I think a song like this was popular.
Let's see now...
"At the road to the cemetery in the north was..."
That's not it...
"In the north..."
At the bar street.
Oh, yes! That's it!
"At the bar street in the north was..."
And there were robots.
My boy was so happy when I bought him a plastic model.
Where's your child now?
Oh, he's dead.
Border security check.
Allow me to inspect your passports.
O-Okay...
Danke schon.
The Elbe River!
How's the trout fishing this year?
Not too good.
Oh, I see!
I caught one about this big last year!
It's impossible this year.
Danke schon.
They know your passport is fake.
You should run away from here, Dr. Tenma.
How do you know about me...?
More importantly...
the border police found out about your counterfeit
passport, and are on their way.
You should run away, Dr. Tenma.
Hey, you.
We'd like to pass through here.
O-Oh, I'm sorry.
My bag is so big, it got stuck.
It's not budging at all.
Man, what in the world are you doing?
Hey, please don't be so rough!
What's in that thing, anyway?
Valuables.
Oh, I'm free!
Do you know what happened to
the man who was just here?
There was an Oriental man in this room with you!
I don't know.
Maybe he went to the dining car?
Hey, check that car over there!
Yes, sir!
This is passenger car two!
We have an emergency!
An Oriental passenger is using a counterfeit passport!
What's wrong?!
Hey!
Emergency stop!
Well done! Well done!
They aren't coming this way.
I got off the train because it stopped.
Oh, I haven't introduced myself yet.
I'm Grimmer.
If you want...
would you like me to show you
to the border, Dr. Tenma?
I know this place very well...
because I come here to fish quite often.
Although climbing the mountain may be hard...
the scenery you'll get to see is well worth it.
Why are you helping me?
When I used to live in old East Germany,
I worked for a newspaper company.
I'm a freelance journalist now, though...
I've read all the articles about you...
because I find you interesting.
In old East Germany, false charges
were an everyday occurrence.
This political prisoner was falsely accused...
That murderer was also innocent...
With this and that, I can distinguish between a
real criminal and someone wrongfully accused.
You're innocent.
Isn't that right, Dr. Tenma?
Would you stop calling me doctor?
But you're an excellent neurosurgeon,
aren't you, Dr. Tenma?
I'm no longer a doctor!
Well?
It's a great view isn't it?
From here, we'll be able to see them coming.
Now then...
Let's take a break here.
Would you like a sandwich?
I have wine as well!
Also, I've got this delicious cheese...
Well... uh... I don't have that much time...
The sun's still high in the sky.
It's better to cross the border when it's dark.
Picnics are so much fun!
It's nice to do something like this once
in a while, don't you think, Dr. Tenma?
Such beautiful scenery!
And such delicious food!
Times like these are when you feel happy to be alive.
I look up to doctors like you.
Even for a journalist like myself...
I might be able to give people the joy of
being alive if I can write a good article.
But you can give people life itself.
I...
shot someone.
Last month, in Munich...
I shot someone for the first time.
He probably died.
Until I shot, my hands kept shaking...
I couldn't aim very well...
But once I pulled the trigger...
my hands stopped shaking.
And then...
there's still another man out there I have to shoot.
I'm no longer... a doctor...
Every time I come to the Elbe River, I think to myself...
that I wanted my kid to fish here, too.
The child who passed away...?
You can catch trout this big!
He passed away without knowing how fun fishing is.
If there had been a doctor like you nearby, then perhaps...
his life would've been saved, and...
No, I'm serious!
You really can catch trout this big!
If you cross that mountain, you'll
be at the Czech Republic border.
Once you cross the border, you'll
come to a path in the forest...
and you can probably hitch a ride.
I'm going to head back to the station now.
Thank you.
You've really helped me, Mr. Grimmer.
I wish you luck, Dr. Tenma.
Now then...
If we meet again, let's have another picnic.
Dr. Tenma.
Everyone is burdened with different sins.
Those sins will never disappear.
But you still have to go on.
Prague (Czech Republic)
Wonderful...
My, it's simply beautiful!
This is my first time here, but Prague at night...
looks just like a town out of a fairy tale.
Um, may I sit here?
Sure...
I've really become fond of this town!
You're Mr. Petrov, aren't you?
You've bought yourself a Russian nationality...
and are now living in the Czech Republic.
There's something I want to ask you about.
Would you please help me out, Mr. Petrov?
No...
Your real name is Mr. Reinhard Biermann...
There was a special orphanage
in East Germany, wasn't there?
A testing site to scientifically correct
the children's personalities...
Kinderheim 511.
You were the director there.
You should know everything...
since you were the director, after all.
What were you trying to do?
At that place in old East Berlin?
At Kinderheim 511?
Yes
Cherish what you know is true in this world.
Ima kono sekai de wakaru koto mitsumete
Yes
Please believe in the kindness of your eyes
Anata no hitomi no yasashisa wo shinjite
Make it home to your land of harmony
Make it home to your land of purity
Make it home