So you're Roberto.
I don't have a name.
That's a shame.
As an officer...
I should at least know the name
of the man who killed me.
A Man Without a Name
Oh, how could this have happened?
He was such a wonderful man...
He put his life on the line for us.
Mr. Grimmer...
Where are you going, Dr. Tenma?
I don't have time for this.
You're going to find Inspector Lunge, right?
I'll go with you.
I have a gun.
This letter...
This letter the Inspector asked Mr. Grimmer to keep...
I heard Inspector Lunge found it at the Red Rose Mansion.
"I've been watching you all this time."
"To eat up every bit of you."
"But instead, everything about you has devoured me."
"When I was on the verge of falling
apart, how did I look to you?"
"That which you gave me as I was falling apart..."
"You left me with such beautiful jewels."
"The twins, who are like eternal life itself."
"The greatest sin is to take away a person's name."
"Reclaim your name."
"I return your name to you."
"Your name is... Anna."
"I'm filled with sorrow now."
"Filled with sorrow..."
You wrote this, didn't you?
I was in love with the mother of the twins.
My way of thinking changed completely in an instant.
And then...
I killed everyone who knew about her...
everyone who knew about the twins...
and everyone who knew about the experiment.
That's all.
Answer me.
Who are you?
You'll die from that wound if you don't treat it.
Answer my questions if you want to live.
Where is Johan?
Why have you gone this far to obey Johan?
How are you related to Johan?
How far you have fallen, Inspector Lunge.
The brilliant agent of the BKA...
is here in this country town, all by himself.
On a sightseeing vacation without even his police badge.
Because you looked too deeply into
a senate member's scandal...
you were hung out to dry.
Now you exist only to chase after Tenma.
That's exactly right.
You did your research.
Your wife is living with another man.
She looked really happy.
Your grandson thinks that man is his grandfather.
He just started to talk.
He kept calling that man, "Grandpa! Grandpa!"
Shut up.
You want to see him, don't you?
Your grandson is growing up to be a cute little boy.
Shut up.
You want to see him, don't you?
Shut up!
You sure have sunk pretty low.
The old Inspector Lunge wasn't like this.
You asked who I am?
How I'm related to Johan?
I don't have a name.
I don't have a homeland.
I don't have any memories.
I realized my first memory while
working after escaping the orphanage.
One day, Johan appeared before me.
He helped me recall one of my memories.
My only memory.
What was his real name?
He said he didn't know.
His own name?
Yeah.
He told me he was in an orphanage.
But he told me once...
that even though he had forgotten everything
else, he remembered his friend's name.
He forgot his own name, but remembered his friend's?
Yeah.
He said that person liked to draw, and he loved bugs.
But he didn't like to kill bugs...
so he would set them free from their cages.
I think his name was Adolf Reinhart.
He said he loved the cocoa they were given once a week.
Johan came to me and offered me a mug.
And then I remembered.
The only thing I looked forward to each
week while I was at the orphanage.
I loved that warm cocoa.
It would be nice if the rain washed everything clean.
Fear.
Anger.
Sadness.
However, in actuality, the complete opposite happened.
Everything was blown out of proportion.
It was raining like this on that day, as well.
The other day, Mr. Liebert, the East German foreign trade adviser...
who emigrated to the West from the East...
appeared before the media with his wife and children.
The Lieberts showed no sign of fatigue...
and appeared happy, standing with their two children.
Are you also an emigrant?
Yes, from Czechoslovakia.
You said you knew these children?
Please let me see them.
Even a glance will do.
Even if it's just their sleeping faces.
A tragedy happened that night.
Survivor confirmed, one young girl!
A man and a woman are dead!
The boy is severely wounded, but he has a pulse!
What's his condition?
Blood,pressure, 72/50!
Pulse, 137!
So the bullet entered in the front?
Kill... him...
I didn't have any idea what happened.
No, I did know.
I knew everything, but I ran away from it all.
I stopped thinking about everything, and ran away.
I tried to draw them.
A picture of the ideal twins.
Those children enveloped in love.
However, no matter how many times I tried,
I just couldn't draw something like that.
Because I knew...
there was no such thing.
Inspector Lunge is at Hotel Bergbach, just ahead, right?
Yeah.
Let's go.
Please be careful.
Who knows where they're aiming from?
I...
I created a monster...
I revived that monster.
This won't kill you, will it?
I have no strength in my right arm.
I was shot by Dr. Tenma in the library in Munich, you see.
It would have been easy to kill him there.
But I couldn't kill him.
Because Dr. Tenma is someone who will remain standing.
He will be the last man standing, all alone.
He will die in solitude...
and without a name.
This is Johan's calculation.
Dr. Tenma was allowed to see
the landscape that Johan saw.
I want to see that landscape, as well.
I want to see it.
Inspector Lunge, you won't see it.
You'll die!
This, too...
is part of Johan's calculation!
Calculation?
Such calculations can't be processed
by the computer in my head!
Answer me!
Where is Johan?
This is terrible.
This is just like a battlefield.
Johan isn't here.
How can you tell?
He's watching from somewhere.
Like watching a line of ants.
Well, let's search inside.
This was where Tenma was headed.
Anybody?
Is anybody here?
I'll check the second floor.
A child?
Don't come over here!
It's okay.
We're on your side.
We came to help.
See, I don't have anything.
See, it's okay.
The girl from the drawings...
What do you mean, the girl from the drawings?
There were lots of drawings.
You look just like the girl in them.
Lots of drawings?
She was with a boy with the same face.
They were drawings of twins.
Where did you see those drawings?
Where did you see them?
l-lt was in the vampire's mansion...
right on top of the hill to the south.
Hey, has anyone seen...
Has anyone seen my son?
Hey...
Where did Wim go?
Everyone is dead...
A devil...
A devil came to this town!
It seems that no one is here anymore.
Johan was here not too long ago...
is what you're saying, right?
They're all attempts at drawing you two...
but they're all unfinished.
They're all smiling happily in the drawings.
The one who drew these was Franz Bonaparta?
I wonder what Johan felt when he saw these drawings?
Welcome back.
I'm home.
Nina.
I...
saw a scary thing.
A very, very scary thing...
A lot of people were dead.
The Red Rose Mansion...
Everyone drank the wine...
And then...
Everyone started to suffer!
They all collapsed on top of each other before my eyes!
Where's my mommy?
I'm sorry...
Why are you apologizing?
Back then...
You two had to live on your own...
Please live on your own...
Why do you cry?
Why are you crying?
Don't cry!
Nina!
He was crying.
Nina?
In this room.
Until just now, in this room...
All by himself...
He was crying, just like that time.
On that rainy night...
I had to shoot him.
If I had forgiven him...
this wouldn't have continued.
This many people wouldn't have died.
It may be too late...
But this time...
Where is Johan now?
He went into town.
To end everything.
Yes
Cherish what you know is true in this world.
Ima kono sekai de wakaru koto mitsumete
Yes
Please believe in the kindness of your eyes
Anata no hitomi no yasashisa wo shinjite
Make it home to your land of harmony
Make it home to your land of purity
Make it home