Over here!
Wait for me!
Double Ranger Kick!
Hey, that's cheating!
You're supposed to fall down when you get kicked!
The evil empire plotting world domination
won't be defeated so easily!
It's a rule on TV that you're supposed
to lose at the end of the show!
Is your world domination progressing smoothly?
Oh, Johan!
He won't go down!
But the hard part comes after
you've conquered the world.
What kind of world are you planning to create?
I dunno.
I'll just wreck everything, and that'll be that.
If you're gonna wreck everything,
that sounds a lot more fun.
Foget the Rainbow Rangers, I'm
gonna join the evil empire, too!
Wait for me!
Now then, shall we head back?
Okay.
Let's all go back.
Don't forget your stuff.
Okay.
Execution
It's getting warmer out...
Yeah...
How's Rosemary?
Did she catch a cold this winter?
No...
She was running around outside with her friends.
She used to get sick every year.
Yeah, when she was about this old.
We had to rush her to the doctor
in the middle of the night!
You carry that album around with you all the time?
Yeah.
She must have gotten big by now.
She's in her growing years.
Since I haven't seen her lately, I wonder
if her face has changed, also?
But you know what?
I'm confident...
...that no matter how big Rosemary gets...
...I'll be able to recognize her immediately.
Oh, that's right!
When the time is right, please show these to her.
They're newspaper clippings from the
time I shot that young serial killer...
...and copies of written reports.
I'm not asking you to explain things to her.
I'm not trying to make excuses, either...
It's just that...
...I want her to know the truth.
I understand.
When... do you think I can see her...?
I'll ask her again if she ever plans
on seeing her father or not.
R-Really?
Then I'll be waiting for her answer!
I'm home at 9 o'clock every night!
You've really gone back to the
way you used to be, Richard...
Like when you were young, and had
just become a police officer.
Your eyes are the same as when we first met.
I see...
Hessen
Offenbach
How does that sound?
We have special deals right now if you sign up with us.
No, we've already got insurance with another company.
Please reconsider our offer, Mr. Liebert.
We're happy with what we have now.
We don't have enough to pay for more anyway...
We just signed up four years ago when we moved in.
Four years ago?
Where were you before?
A place called Brunthal, near Mannheim.
Brunthal?  That's a nice place.
Were you born there, sir?
Yes, I had lived there all my life before moving here.
By the way, do you have any children, ma'am?
Oh, our son is currently attending college in Munich.
A college student!
I've got the perfect insurance
for young people right now!
Please, at least hear me out.
S-Sure...
This is your son?
He was very cute.
What's his name?
Johan.
Would you like some tea?
No, I couldn't!
Please don't mind me.
He's barely called since he started
going to school in Munich.
That's how boys are.
That's no fun.
I went there today, Dr. Reichwein.
Yes, to Johan's home.
Yes, it was a pretty normal family with
nothing at all out of the ordinary.
So...what do you think, Richard?
Well, in my police days, I would've thought...
...there's nothing more suspicious than
something that seems perfect.
I see.
Anyway, I'm going to scope out Johan's
background a little more.
Something...
There has to be something...
At the high school Johan went to...
...he was at the top of his class,
with irreproachable conduct.
But you know what?
I'm confident...
...that no matter how big Rosemary gets...
...I'll be able to recognize her immediately.
That baby's face!
There is no way he'd look like
Johan when he's grown up!
Brunthal Town Hall
Here, this is his birth certificate.
Oh, thank you.
Johan Wilhelm Liebert...
Born on February 9th, 1976...
So he was born in this town...
Nothing out of the ordinary...
Mr. Herz!
How many times do I have to tell you?
There is no smoking in here!
Oh, come on.  Don't be so stingy,
just give me an ashtray.
Absolutely not!
This place caught on fire four years ago, remember?
Don't you remember how hard a time
we had when all the files burned up?
You restored all the records, though?
Y-Yes...
We restored them by having everyone
resubmit their information.
But since this is a small town...
...it really didn't take that much effort.
Ah, thanks for coming, Dr. Gillen.
It's been a while, Professor Reichwein.
You said Dr. Tenma came to your place
looking for a man named Johan?
Yes.
But he had no proof to back up his story.
However, if this person...
...was the "friend" who instigated the serial murders...
...committed by Peter Jürgens that I'm researching...
...then the entire chain of events can be pieced together.
I'm counting on you, Dr. Gillen.
Yes, sir.
I'll seek permission for another audience
with Jürgens immediately.
Once I show him the photograph...
...depending on his reaction...
...we may be able to prove Dr. Tenma's innocence.
Johan Wilhelm Liebert
02/09/1976 - 04/01/1978
Dead?
Yes...
The real Johan who was born in Brunthal
died at the age of two...
In other words...
...the Lieberts altered their dead son's documents...
...by taking advantage of the town hall's fire,
and made it look like he was still alive?
Most likely...
Then...
...the person who calls himself Johna Liebert...
Just... who is he...?
Anyway...
As I just told you, I gave you
Johan's photograph to Dr. Gillen.
Let's just hope we get an answer from him.
So, would you like to have dinner?
No, actually, I should get going...
What?
You're going back to work even
after running all day?
No, I might be getting a phone call
Maybe...
...I'll get to see my daughter.
Don't worry.
Moving forward is what is important, right?
Okay!
You have now fully recovered!
Yes, hello?
Daddy?  It's me!
Rosemary...
Yeah, I'm doing fine...
Yeah, we'll see each other again...
We can see each other... anytime...
Mr. Richard?
It's me, Johan.
This boy here, Jürgens.
Do you recognize him?
Have you met him before?
I don't know him...
You said your friend Johan...
...only sent you letters, and you never
met him face to face, right?
But Johan knew you very well.
Can I borrow... a ballpoint pen...?
I'm sorry, but I'm forbidden to give you any objects.
A pen, please...
The park...
It was in the park...
The day after I killed someone...
"Let's stop this..."
"Let this be the end of it..."
That's what went through my head
as I went to the park...
He had a lot of kids with him...
Hold on a second!
I forgot to start recording.
Can you start from the beginning again?
"You come, too."
"You come..."
Wha...
What do you want?
We met at Mr. Schuwald's place.
My name is Johan Liebert.
I called several times, but you weren't home.
So I came over in person.
Hello.
Oh, Dr. Gillen.
So, how did it go when you showed
Jürgens the photograph?
He's dead?
Yes.
Just moments ago at the hospital...
I can't do anything right now due to the questioning.
Because I was careless and gave him a ballpoint pen...
...we've lost an important reference.
However, Professor Reichwein...
His suicide was clearly...
...a reaction to Johan's photograph.
As soon as the questioning is finished, I'll rush right over.
Okay!
I'll contact Richard immediately.
Richard...
A college report...?
Yes.
I'm researching the convention established
by the United Nations in 1989...
...the "Convention on the Rights of the Child."
Would you like a drink, Mr. Richard?
No, I'm fine!
You've quit drinking, haven't you?
Yeah, that's a smart move.
Because you executed that boy while you were drunk.
Am I right?
Y-Yes...
Even though it was because of the alcohol...
...I did something unforgiveable.
I want to ask you something regarding that case.
That boy you shot and killed...
...was Stefan Joos, seventeen years old.
What kind of crime did he commit?
Boy, huh?
A seventeen year old boy committed crimes of the devil.
Nine cases of rape and murder,
two attempted murder cases...
And that's why you executed him?
It wasn't an execution!
Oh, pardon me.
By the way, did you know that under Article 40
of the Convention on the Rights of the Child...
...under the power conferred by the convention...
...one is presumed innocent until there
is firm proof he is guilty?
You're aware of that, aren't you?
Yes, I know that.
I've worked with the juvenile division before.
I see.
Then what about Article 37?
Those under the age of eighteen who commit a crime...
...cannot be executed or given life sentences
where there's no chance of release.
The majority of the convention...
...are the basic rights inherent
to a person in this country...
...whether that person is an adult or a child!
When I shot and killed him, it wasn't an execution!
It was a mistake due to alcohol!
I know I did something unforgiveable...
I even accept all the social reprisals I get, like this!!
Now, now. Please take it easy.
I wanted to meet you so I could write my college report.
If I put you in a bad mood, I apologize.
How about we go for a walk to get some fresh air?
I'll take this bottle of whiskey.
The night breeze is just going to get colder.
Oh, Dr. Gillen!
I still can't get a hold of Richard.
He said he might be able to see his daughter, but...
...I don't think they would be
meeting at such a late hour.
Well, please tell him to be careful when
you do get in touch with him.
I'm on my way over there right now.
Are you familiar with Stefan Joos' personal history?
I think he was in some orphanage in
East Germany when he was young...
I think you ought to know more.
This is an extremely important
point when discussing him.
The orphanage he was in...
It was a terrible place.
He was a really good kid.
But he was mistreated horribly at the orphanage
And his mind was twisted while he stayed there...
Article 6 of the Convention on the Rights of the Child...
An inherent right to live.
Guaranteed survival and development.
Article 8...
The preservation of identity.
Article 19...
Protection from abuse.
No...
That nightmarish place didn't bother
giving him those rights.
That place was Kinderheim 511.
Are you going to see your daughter soon?
H-How do you know about that?
How did you know about that?
Was it your daughter who called
you at home before?
Will you be able to see her tomorrow?
What are you trying to accomplish?
I'm writing my college report.
Not that!
Your purpose for being with Schuwald!
You...
Who... are you?
You said you shot the boy because you were drunk.
Answer my question first!
It's true that you were seen drinking at
a bar after you shot him that day...
But something is strange.
According to my research...
...not one person saw you drinking
before you killed the boy.
You weren't drunk when you
shot the boy, were you?
What...!
You were sober.
And you were calm.
You wanted to execute him...
...so you calmly pulled the trigger.
Am I wrong?
Yes!
Why are you trying to forget?
Or are you just lying?
Are you lying to others?
Or are you lying to yourself?
Did you confirm the boy's crimes?
Did you have the right to execute him?
Do you think that by lying...
...your sin will go away?
What a heavy sin...
Can a man who has committed such a sin...
...really meet with his daughter and
say he's turned  his life around?
Well?
Would you like a drink?
Gillen?
Is that you, Dr. Gillen?
We're the police.
Your patient, Richard Braun...
...has died.