"Oh, Corinna."
"Why was your letter so short?"
"Like Eupolis and his astrology..."
"You tear my heart asunder."
"And the pallid color of Idas' gold..."
"...like the artisans of Galonius..."
That's enough...
I said there is no need to read any further.
Um, is something...
You're done.
Hurry up and go home!
I-I'm sorry.
Did I do something to offend you...?
Those who can't even pronounce Latin correctly
don't have the right to read books to me!
I-I'm terribly sorry.
I'll be more careful from now on.
I said leave!
The Thursday Boy
University of Munich
Friedrich Emmanuel School
You really got chewed out at the mansion.
Cheer up!
Mr. Karl Neumann, Economics major!
How do you know about me?  Who are you?
I'm Lotte Frank, a Cultural Anthropology major.
Do you read books to him part time, also?
No, I only take care of his personal needs.
He only has male students read books to him.
You're in charge of Tuesdays.
On other days, he has other students read
to him, since he's practically blind.
Hey, so what do you think about the mysterious
wealthy juggernaut, Hans Georg Schuwald?
I... I don't know...
I only jumped at the chance because the pay was good...
Have you heard rumors about him?
They say that with a single phone call from his mansion...
...he can control all the stocks in Germany.
People call him the Howard Hughes of Bayern.
He has no family.
He's not close with anyone.
And yet, his fortune only grows.
What do you think he's going to do with all that money?
Who knows...
And there is an even bigger mystery.
His other nickname is the Vampire of Bayern.
Vampire?
When the bell tolls at 2 AM...
...he and his butler leave in his hearse like car,
and they wander the nighttime streets.
It's just like a setting from one
of those gothic horror stories.
He's probably just taking a walk.
Soon I'll be able to confirm if it's just a walk or not.
What do you mean by "confirm"?
It's just for my research paper.
"The Psychology of Medieval and Present
Day Financial Figures in Bayern."
I'm sure he'll be the perfect subject.
So that's why you did some research on me, huh?
I only looked up your name and major.
Anyway, just because Schuwald yelled
at you, don't let it get to you.
He has said horrible things to all the other students, also...
Yeah...
I'm used to being yelled at and getting hit...
You're used to it?
Y-Yeah...
I've had to change foster parents pretty
often because so much has happened.
Speaking of which, you didn't go to
one of the local schools, did you?
So you did check up on me.
I see...
You don't have any parents...
To tell you the truth...
I enrolled in the University of Munich
hoping I could see my mother.
Oh, your mother is in Munich?
So, were you able to see her?
No, but it's okay...
Huh?  Why?
But she's so close!
You know her name, right?
Yeah...
What is her name?
I said I don't care anymore.
Oh, just tell me!
If I become curious, I'll find out anyway.
Margot...
Margot Langer.
She will be easy to find if you know that much!
Go see her!
I'm sure your mother will be happy!
Like I said, it's okay...
Margot Langer... Margot Langer...
No way!
"The chestnut horse's sprint..."
"...gathered like thunder in the pond of blood..."
"...and caused the tide to rise..."
I can't bear to listen to this!
I only love that which is beautiful.
I can't bear to listen to this.
Why did you tell me something so important?
I did some research on your mother.
I don't know what to say...
That's why I said I don't care anymore, get it?
Karl, is there anything I can help you with?
Thank you...
I'll be fine.
Karl...
Hey, Lotte...
You said you were going to find out what
Hans Schuwald does at night, didn't you?
Can I come with you?
Yes, of course!
I'd feel much better if you came along!
I'm telling you the truth!
This is the first major scoop since the founding
of our Occult Phenomenon Research Society!
I wonder...
Either way...
...this poem was written by one of the founders
of this university, Bishop Gropius.
This is the poem he wrote in 1502, no doubt about it!
What is important is this verse right here!
"In the penultimate intercalary year..."
"...the Thursday boy will visit this land."
"All books will be engulfed in flame."
"And the entire world will be engulfed in sadness."
So what?
Don't you get it?
This is the "penultimate intercalary year."
It's talking abut 1996.
In other words, it's talking about this year!
Why?
An "intercalary year" is a leap year.
The only leap year left in this century
are this one and the year 2000.
He "will visit this land" and "all books
will be engulfed in flame."
When it talks about "all books" and "this land"...
...it means that this university will be burned down!
Then who is the "Thursday boy"?
Thursday...
The root of Donnerstag is Donner.
Which means thunder!
It's talking about a thunder god!
That's pretty far fetched!
This is no laughing matter!
This should be the topic of our next issue!
I don't really mind if we print it,
but who is going to believe it?
That a god of destruction is going
to come to this university?
Vampire of Bayern, my ass!
This is the truth behind his mysterious outings?
Talk about being deluded...
Quiet!  They are coming out!
Oh, this is ridiculous!
I'm going home.
Okay, be careful.
I'm going to go take a look.
Go?  Go where?
Hey, we shouldn't do this!
Yeah, this isn't a place for girls.
You should go home.
"I only love that which is beautiful."
I want to know...
...just how low that man is.
It's open.
If you're looking for a girl, you've
come to the wrong place.
Because I retired a long time ago.
Who are you?
When you come into someone's place,
you normally introduce yourself first.
I'm Margot Langer.
You seem to be a college student...
Y-Yes...
I work part time for Mr. Hans Schuwald.
So, what do you want with me?
He...
I want to know why Mr. Hans Schuwald comes here...
He comes here for entertainment...
...is what I'd like to tell you, but...
His thing seems to be useless now.
He comes to hand over money.
Of course.
Because when I told him my name...
...he started to cry and apologize to me.
Because he fathered my child, and
then threw me away like trash.
Karl, then you're...
You're Hans Schuwald's child!
Oh, but...
That is a lie...
You...
You... are not Margot Langer!
That's right!
She was in the newspaper a year ago!
"Former prostitute..."
"Former Prostitute Margot Langer Killed!"
"Killer Currently Unknown."
His mother is already dead!
You are just using that name to become my mother...
...to become Margot Langer and swindle
money from Hans Schuwald!
He knows it too.
He's paying me, knowing full well that I'm not really her.
Because he knows that the real Margot he should
be paying is no longer of this world.
That is his way of atonement.
Money!  Money!  Money!
For someone who has lived only for money...
...this is the only way.
It may sound presumptuous of me for saying this, but...
People aren't all that different.
They would say that you are acting like that old timer's
son, since he doesn't have much time left...
...in order to inherit his enormous estate.
What are you trying to say?
You guys call me a liar, but...
...who knows what YOUR intentions are.
There is one more person...
...who claims to be his son.
He came here just like you and
asked the same questions.
That is... impossible...!
That is a lie!
He is the one who is lying!
Who knows who is lying?
To me, you both look like impostors.
Who is this person?
He is the same as you.
You guys take turns reading books to
Schuwald on different days, right?
He's one of them.
Yes that is right...
He's the Thursday boy.
Why didn't you tell her that you are the real thing?
I...
I went through numerous foster parents...
...and a lot has happened...
But my current foster parents are really kind to me.
So kind that I would never be able to thank them enough.
That is why I thought of meeting my real parents...
By knowing how much of a lowlife my real father was...
...I thought I could love my foster parents even more.
That was all I wanted...
Have you ever met this Thursday boy?
I'm off on Thursdays, so...
Oh, but once when I went back to
get something I had forgotten...
You've seen him?
What kind of man is he?
What kind?
He has blond hair and a really pretty face...
Monday
Who is it?
Who is the Thursday boy?
Someone at this university is trying to be me.
Listen closely to what Mom has to say, okay Karl?
Take this money and take the train on track five.
If you get off at the eighth stop, there will
be a lady named Martha waiting for you.
What about you?
I told you, I can't go with you.
Are the police after you?
I want to stay with you!
No!
If you stay with me, you'll be put in a foster home!
If you stay here, people say
you are the son of a prostitute!
Now, hurry!
What about my dad?
My father's name is Hans Georg Schuwald, right?
Who told you?
Mrs. Bella from across the street...
He's rich, isn't he?
She said I was abandoned by my father...
You weren't abandoned...
Then I'll go to Dad's place!
Not now!
Then when?
When you are older...
If you still want to meet him after you've grown up...
However, you mustn't want anything from him!
You mustn't hate him, even if he acts cold towards you!
Why?
Because I don't hate him.
Take this with you.
Your father meant to give you this when you were born.
I found something, Karl!
I found out who the Thursday boy is!
His name is Edmund Fahren.
He is a student in the Literature Department.
Without a doubt, he works part time
at Schuwald's place reading books.
And he is in charge of Thursdays.
Edmund Fahren...
Here.
Looks like class just ended.
Hey!
We would like to speak with Edmund Fahren.
Edmund, are you here?
Edmund?
He didn't come to class today.
There you go.
I see...
That is a shame...
Oh, but it's only a matter of time.
We are going to get our hands on that swindler!
Because you are the one who is going to
inherit Schuwald's enormous estate.
That's not it...
I don't care about the inheritance.
But...
I don't care how much of Schuwald's
money has been swindled!
But...
But?
But... that bastard, Edmund Fahren...
I can't forgive him for calling himself my mom's son!
Tuesday
"The petals of your silk flowers..."
"...fluttered in the wind."
"So cried the mockingbird within my heart."
You aren't going to say anything today, Mr. Schuwald?
Why didn't you quit after I yelled at you?
Because the pay is good?
It's not...!
It's not... that...
Can you only talk about money?
It's just as you say...
Who are your parents?
I... was taken in by foster parents...
I see...
Forgive me for asking.
Don't you want to see your real parents?
The truth is...
I...
I think the boy who appeared this
time may be the real thing...
He wasn't after my money...
"He"?
It's nothing, I'm just talking to myself.  You may go now.
Oh, also...
Your Latin...
It's gotten much better.
Thank you very much...
Wednesday
Looks like Edmund Fahren isn't here today, either.
He is probably in bed after catching a cold or something.
Tomorrow is Thursday, so you don't have to rush around...
He will be at Schuwald's place for work.
Oh, I get it!
You are going to reveal his true nature
right in front of Schuwald!
Let's do it!
Let's go all out!
Thursday
He's not showing up...
It's been an hour already...
If he has a cold, we can always
attack him while he is in bed...
Hey!
Hey, given our situation, how about
we barge into his dorm?
You even found his address?
204...
204!
Here!
Come on.
Friday
What a horrible thing...
The entire school is talking about Edmund Fahren now.
Who would have thought he would commit suicide...?
Even the school newspaper mentioned
his suicide note, right?
"I can't deceive him anymore."
Then, this must be...
Yeah...
Because he got too close to Schuwald
by pretending to be his son...
...he was tortured by his conscience.
If he was so confused that he would kill himself, he
shouldn't have done it in the first place...
Lotte, it must have been difficult yesterday.
Yeah...
The police were questioning me the whole day...
The part time reading job was canceled today, too...
Mr. Schuwald is really upset.
Oh, Karl.  Let me introduce you two.
He's the person in charge of Fridays...
Nice to meet you.
Oh, hi!
I'm Karl Neumann, an Economics major.
I'm Johan Liebert, majoring in law.