How are you feeling, Mr. Junkers?
Mr. Junkers, do you know who I am?
Can you see this finger?
How about it?
Can you answer me?
Yes?
What is it, Mr. Junkers?
...nster... coming...
Coming?  What's coming?
The monster... is coming....
The monster... is coming...
Monster?
Night of the Execution
I know you can speak now, Junkers.
The four middle aged couples murdered
in the past two years...
You were seen near three of those crime scenes.
Well, Adolf Junkers?
Well, that's fine.
I know you're employed as a lock picker.
Your job is to merely open locks.
You couldn't possibly have slit their throats
in such a splendidly horizontal fashion.
Which means there were others besides you.
The way I see it, there had to have
been at least three people...
...in order to get past the strong locks and kill the middle aged couples without resistance.
We're pretty much done narrowing the list
of suspects who are skilled with knives.
It's only a matter of time before we determine
who your partners were...
...whether you tell us or not.
But that isn't what I really want to ask you.
I'd like to know why you bothered to go all
over Germany to commit those four crimes.
And why you only killed childless middle aged couples.
Valuables were taken, but...
...after splitting such a small amount
between the three of you...
...this crime doesn't add up.
Well?
How about we make a plea bargain?
If you confess now, we'll dismiss all charges against you.
Who hired you guys for these jobs?
Mr. Junkers!
It's okay!  It's okay!
This interrogation has gone far enough!
No, we just need to push a little further.
Please leave!
That's an order from the attending physician!
Well, that's fine.  I'll return some other time.
However...
I'll be leaving some observers behind...
...to make sure he isn't poisoned
or doesn't disappear on us...
It appears that trouble seems to follow
you for some reason, Dr. Tenma.
What are you trying to say?!
It was only a joke.
Now then, please excuse me.
Hey, where are you going?
Just out for a walk.
You can't just do these kinds of things by yourself!
The patient needs a change of scenery once in a while.
We're only going out to the yard.
If you're so worried, why don't you just come with us?
It's so nice and warm today.
You can talk now, can't you?
It's days like today that make me really glad to be alive.
At times, I feel like I wouldn't be able
to go on without these kinds of days.
Especially when faced with life
and death each and every day.
That's why it's easier for doctors if they
only focus on promotions or research.
I used to be like that, too.
I wanted to get promoted so I could do my own research.
I thought that being successful in surgery
was the only way to secure my position.
But I changed as a result of operating
on a certain little boy.
He was a twin... the older brother.
By saving his life after he was shot in the head...
...I was able to get back to being a real doctor.
He made me realize that all human lives are equal.
And that it's a doctor's job to save them.
Thanks!
People can change for the better.
It's never too late to start over.
Doctor...
You and I aren't that far apart in age, but...
...you're like my father.
You saved my life.
You feel like a parent to me.
Well, looks like I just gained quite a large son!
When I was a child, I always wanted a mechanical clock.
You know...
...the kind where the wooden Nutcracker soldier
comes out every time it strikes an hour.
I dreamed of that clock every day, and always
had my face up against the shop window.
That shop was the first one I ever broke into.
I was caught immediately that time,
and couldn't get the clock.
But after that, picking locks became my job.
At first, I just wanted that clock...
I just wanted that clock, and yet...
I...
Confess everything.
Tell the police everything, and start over.
They were killed...
All my partners...
...were killed...
By who?!
By that monster you were talking about?
You better make it tonight!
I went through a lot of trouble to set this up just right.
She's the daughter of a state legislator.
I guess she's what people call a
woman with wit and beauty.
She's fine, I tell you!
I won't know until I meet her.
But I guess you're right.
Maybe I should start settling down...
Right?
It's unthinkable for a man in your
position to not have a wife...
Hey.
The kind where a wooden Nutcracker soldier
comes out every time it strikes an hour.
This is it!
Excuse me!
About the clock in the window...
Hey, what are you doing?
It's time for your date!
People can change for the better.
It's never too late to start over.
Officer...
Hey, Officer!
You're there, aren't you?
I'll tell you everything.
But can you call Dr. Tenma over?
Officer?
Officer...
I know it's late, but can I enter the ward?
Oh, sure.  Go right ahead, Dr. Tenma.
What's that?
I found something nice.
Hey, what's wrong?!
Hang on!
He's dead...
Candy...?
Mr. Junkers!
It's the same as back then!
Poisoned by candy!
My patient disappearing!
This is just like what happened nine years ago!
Mr. Junkers!
Mr. Junkers?
It's me, Tenma!
Doctor!
Don't come, Doctor!
Let's go back to the hospital, Mr. Junkers.
Everything will be okay.
No, Doctor!
You can't come here!
You must not look at him!
Him?
He's the one who killed off my partners!
He'll kill you too, Doctor!
W-Who are you?!
No, Doctor!
Don't come any closer!
It's been a long time, Doctor.
It's me.
You saved my life nine years ago, remember?
Nine years ago...?
You probably already forgot about those two little twins...
Johan?
Johan...
Yes, those twins.
So you do remember me.
Run!
He'll kill you too, Doctor!
W-What are you going to do to him?!
Mr. Junkers is my patient!
What...?
Execute him, of course.
Stop!
Doctor, run!
He's the one who killed off my partners!
We were hired by him!
We always received phone calls from him!
Every time we finished a job...
...he transferred a large sum of money to a bank account...
...and we'd split it between the three of us!
Then...
...the client who ordered the murders
of the four middle aged couples.
...was you?!
Because the police were onto us,
we became obstacles to him!
Fritz, the knife user, the Big Boris...
He's killed them already!
Before he died, Fritz told me...
...that we'd been hired by a monster!
He doesn't even blink at killing someone!
Run!  He's going to kill you too, Doctor!
Run, Doctor!
You like to talk, don't you, Mr. Junkers?
Stop!
Don't do it, Johan!
Mr. Junkers doesn't seem to know your identity, but I do!
I was your attending physician!
You're Johan Liebert, the elder of the twins.
The East German trade adviser who fled in 1986...
...you're the son of Michael Liebert!
It's impossible for you to run if I know about your past!
Don't commit any more sins, Johan!
Johan, huh?
I guess there were times when I was called by that name.
But that isn't my real name.
What do you mean?
Nobody must know my past.
Those four couples, and the Liebert family...
But it's different with you, Doctor.
You saved my life.
You're like a parent to me.
Parent?  Me?
Because if you didn't exist, I wouldn't be here.
Stop it!
You can't kill people!
Why not?
What do you mean, why not?
What do you take human lives for?!
I was only able to get back to being
a real doctor by saving your life!
I realized that human lives have equal value by saving you!
Nobody has the right to take another's life!
I've been living as a doctor with that
engraved upon my heart for years!
What's so funny?!
I heard you became the chief of the surgical department
after that incident, right Doctor?
I'm really glad you were promoted
to the position of head surgeon.
What are you trying to say?
You're in that position today because the director,
head surgeon, and chief are dead, right?
I'm really pleased.
Then... it was you...
You said it yourself, Doctor.
You wanted it.
You said it when I regained consciousness.
You hated them so much that you wanted to kill them.
I'm not wrong!
People like him...
...are better off dead!
I only did what you wished for.
Doctor...
I'm scared, Doctor...
Help me, Doctor!
I don't want to die!
Doctor!
I should have died back then.
But you brought me back to life, Doctor.
What a down pour...
Personally, I hate rain.
It washes away all the evidence of a crime.
What about you, Dr. Tenma?
Now then, here is where we stand.
Let's piece together what you told us.
In 1986, Mr. Liebert fled from East Germany with the twins.
After their exile, the members of the Liebert family were shot, and both parents died.
The older brother suffered a severe head injury.
You operated on that boy and saved his life.
However, to your surprise...
...the boy killed the director, head surgeon, and department chief with poisoned candy, and ran away.
And last night, he reappeared after nine years.
He killed a county police officer
with poisoned candy yet again...
...and shot Adolf Junkers to death right in front of you.
He's the one who hired Junkers and two other
men to kill the four middle aged couples.
His name is Johan Liebert.
Is that how it goes?
Hey...
Y-Yes?
Let him go for now.
It's unthinkable that someone in his position
would commit such awful crimes.
He has an alibi for the time when the officer was killed.
Plus, no traces of gunpowder were found on his hands.
Now we've lost the only lead we had on solving
four murder cases of the middle aged couples.
Should we check out this Johan Liebert
person, Inspector Lunge?