And I stood upon the sand of the sea, and saw a Monster rise up out of the sea,
having seven heads and ten horns, and upon his horns ten crowns,
And upon his head the name of blasphemy (...)
And they worshiped the dragon which gave power unto the Monster:
and they worshiped the Monster, saying,
"Who is like unto the Monster?
Who is able to make war with him?"
< The Black Book of Johann, Revelation 13, #1-4 >
This is an actual passage from the Bible with the word
"beast" replaced with "monster," and "Ioanes" with "Johann."
That was amazing!
Yes, his skills are unmatched
I couldn't believe his speed, even when clipping
that difficult cranial arterial mass!
Yes.
That was a splendid operation, Herr Dr. Tenma.
I finally got to see what a genius Kenzou
Tenma is with my own eyes.
No, it was all due to everyone's hard work.
Thank you very much.
I can't believe the sun is so high already...
Well, we did operate for six hours straight.
There aren't any other patients today, so rest up.
Hey, where is daddy?
What happened to daddy?
Herr Dr. Tenma
Düsseldorf
(Germany)
Come on, wake up already.
Good morning.  This is the news at eight.
Wake up, Dr. Tenma.
We're here to bring you the following news.
Kenzou Tenma
Don't you think the roles have been reversed?
Eva Heinemann
It should be a princess like myself being woken with a kiss.
First, the widespread news about the East German
Foreign Trade Adviser, Mr. Liebert.
Oh, you are here, Eva?
Hello, Mr. Reimann from Düsseldorf.
You forgot about our date, didn't you, Kenzou?
We're here in Düsseldorf.
No, it's not that I forgot about it...
Now that the Foreign Trade Adviser who fled to West Germany...
Adviser Liebert made an appearance before the media with his family yesterday.
Mr. Liebert, without any sign of fatigue on his face...
...along with his twin son and daughter...
...appeared, smiling brightly.
His family is planning to stay here in Düsseldorf for some time...
...and carry on with their daily lives in an apartment provided by our TV station.
I don't feel like I've slept at all...
Now, onto the next story.
Hey, wake up!
The famous opera singer, Mr. Rosenbach...
This one is about you!
...collapsed yesterday due to an internal hemorrhage.
He is reported to be in stable condition after surgery.
Director Heinemann, from the Düsseldorf Eisler Memorial
Hospital, participated in the operation...
...and held a press conference a short time ago.
Mr. Rosenbach's diagnosis revealed that he suffered
from a ruptured artery in the brain.
The operation itself went accordingly.
The clipping went extremely well, too.
Mr. Rosenbach has numerous fans.
Do you think he'll make a full recovery?
Yes, we'll put forth every effort
to recover his singing voice.
Dr. Heinemann's team has had success in
numerous difficult operations to date.
But with this operation, we can now say that they have
secured their position in the medical world in our country.
That is amazing, Kenzou!
The news wasn't about me...
It was about your father.
That is true, but...
It's because you performed a perfect surgery
with my father's team last night.
In other news...
I'm sure father appreciates your efforts.
You're responsible for improving the hospital's reputation.
I'm the one who should be thankful...
...since it's thanks to your father that
I can work like this in Germany.
Good luck, Kenzou.
I'm positive everything will work out fine
if you follow in my father's footsteps.
It's only matter of time before my father becomes the chief director.
Then you'll soon be the head of the surgical department.
And eventually, a director.
That'll make me the wife of a director.
You better make me happy...
...because hardship doesn't suit me.
Should we leave?
Or should we...
...the southern region will be rainy over the weekend.
Blood pressure, 128/64.
Retractor.
I'm going to make an incision in the pyramis now.
That was a perfect operation as usual, Dr. Tenma!
Thank you very much.
Although it doesn't seem like you're
only good at operating on people...
Dr. Becker
You hold the position of chief at such a young age...
...and both the director and the surgical head hold you in the high esteem.
And on top of that...
...you won the heart of the director's daughter.
What are you trying to say, Dr. Becker?
Sorry.  I don't mean anything bad.
Because a hospital is just a world of politics.
You know full well that you're being
used by the director, right?
The operation that you performed
successfully on the opera singer...
He held a press conference on TV
as if he did everything himself.
Although it means you have talent, if you're being used.
When you get promoted, put in a good word for me.
I'll treat you sometime, okay?
Umm, may I help you?
You're Dr. Tenma?
Yes.
Give me back my husband.
Give him back!
Why didn't you operate on my husband?!
Y-You are...?
My husband was brought into the hospital first!
He was brought in long before that stupid opera singer!
But you guys pushed him back!
Aren't you the most skilled doctor in this hospital?!
So why?
Why?!
It was then I recalled that....
I was going to operate on a Turkish man who
got injured in a construction accident.
Dr. Tenma!
Yes?
This isn't your operation.
Hurry up and go to operating room #1.
It's an order from the director.
Please hurry!
If only you had operated on him,
he would have survived!
If only you had...!
Mom!
Give him back!
Give him back...
Mom!
So my friend and I fought over that dress.
They only had one dress of that size left.
But you don't have to worry about anything.
I made it mine in the end.
Hey, are you listening to me?
Yeah...
What is wrong with you?
You seem out of it.
I checked the medical records...
The one who operated on the
Turkish man was Dr. Becker.
Oh, come on.  You're still talking about that?
It's obvious that he took too much
time to begin the treatment.
If I were the one who had operated on him...
...maybe I could have saved that Turkish man's life.
Stop it!  We're eating here!
But what does she want from me?
I only operated on the opera singer because
the director ordered me to.
It's not my fault.
Don't you think so?
Of course.
Because people's lives aren't equal.
Give him back!
Give my husband back!
Is that the house?
Yes, the report was made by one of the neighbors.
How many shots were fired?
Five or six, sir.
Who lives in this house?
W-Well...
It's the house of Mr. Liebert, the trade adviser
who fled from East Germany a few days ago.
Oh, this is going to be a problem.
We're going in on the count or three.
One...
Two...
Three!
This is terrible...
Who could have...
S-Someone is there!
Survivor confirmed.  One young girl.
A man and a woman are dead.
A boy in critical condition.
I repeat...
A boy in critical condition!
An emergency case?
A bullet in his head?
The boy is the only patient?
Yes, his parents died instantly.
It appears to be a robbery of some kind.
Okay, I'll be at the hospital in about five minutes.
Oh, father.
Please forgive me, Dr. Heinemann, for
keeping your daughter out so late.
What are you saying, Tenma?
Eva is your fiancé, isn't she?
What do you say?
Would you like to have a cup of tea?
Have you given the wedding
date to your parents in Japan?
Y-Yes.
But my father is only a practitioner in a small hospital...
...so I'm not sure if he can make
time to come to Germany.
It's perfect opportunity, so they
should enjoy an overseas trip.
Yes, since we're the ones who invited them.
Thank you very much.
I'm indebted to you for everything.
When you first arrived in Germany...
...I thought you were just some high school kid.
But now, you're the number one young surgeon of Eisler Memorial.
By the way, Kenzou...
Your current research into cerebral ischemia
and subarachnoid hemorrhages...
Yes, we're currently making a canine model
of the subarachnoid hemorrhages.
Sorry, but that research has to be canceled.
Excuse me?
In the upcoming European Medical Science Symposium,
I am making a presentation as a speaker.
I want you to prepare the manuscripts for me.
But... we're near the completion of our research.
Man, you should have been there this afternoon.
What happened father?
Some suspicious civilian group
came rushing into the hospital.
They made a commotion about the operation we
performed on the opera singer the other day.
They accused us of pushing back the case
of the Turkish man that came before him.
They completely misunderstood the situation.
The Turkish man's operation was performed first.
There was nothing wrong with our procedures.
Isn't that right?
S-Sure...
I swear, they think doctors are some kind of volunteers or something.
Even before saving lives, we doctors value academics first.
Isn't that right?
In any case, I'll leave the manuscripts
for my presentation to you.
I expect a great deal from you, Tenma.
Thank you...
Shit!
Where is the patient?
They have taken him inside.
What is his condition?
Blood pressure, 72/50
Pulse, 137.
So the bullet entered his skull from the front...
We need X-Rays immediately!
Yes, sir!
Oh, Dr. Tenma!
Who is this girl?
She is the twin sister of that boy just now.
Any injuries?
None.
It appears she suffered a massive mental shock.
What is it?
Kill. Him.
Dr. Tenma!
Head shots and CT scans are ready.
Okay, I'll be right there.
It entered the head from the front, and embedded itself near the center of the brain.
Yes...
This will be difficult.
The bullet grazed the left side
of the middle cerebral artery.
I see.  Dr. Tenma is right!
This won't be easy.
If we move the bullet even a little...
...it might rupture and cause a massive hemorrhage.
Sorry, I was late.
Dr. Becker!
Why are you late when you're
supposed to be on duty?!
We'll do a full frontal craniotomy on both sides...
...remove the bone fragments...
...and damaged brain matter as well.
We'll then carefully remove the bullet...
...and finally, repair the artery.
This operation will take time, but...
Everyone, let's give it our best!
Blood pressure, 120/80.
Pulse, 92.
Everything looks to be in good condition.
Anesthetics administered.
Dr. Tenma!
Yes?
This isn't your operation.
You must go to Operating Room #1 immediately.
The Mayor, Mr. Roedecker, has collapsed
from a cerebral thrombosis.
They're bringing him in by helicopter right now.
They should be arriving in ten minutes.
Then please contact Dr. Boyer.
They're afraid that his artery may be blocked.
If that is the case, you must operate on him!
But I was about to start the operation on that child!
It's an order from the director.
Yes, this is Tenma.
Oh, Tenma.  Please take care of the Mayor's case.
I've already contacted Dr. Eisen and Dr. Boyer.
This situation should be acceptable, right?
But Director, I was about to start
on another operation!
Just leave that to Dr. Becker.
W-With all due respect, sir!
The patient in the operation I'm about to conduct...
...had a bullet graze the left side of his middle cerebral artery...
...and it'll be a very difficult operation!
However, I'm confident that I can save him.
I'm going to leave the Mayor's case to Dr. Boyer.
I must operate on the boy for him to survive.
Anyway, Tenma, please give everything
you have to save the Mayor's life.
The Mayor has already promised...
...to greatly increase our subsidy
at the next medical assessment.
We can't have him die yet.
I'm counting on you, Tenma.
I expect a great deal from you.
Yes, sir...
The Mayor has arrived at the heliport!
Get to angio immediately after the CT.
Please confirm which areas are blocked.
Hey, you better make preparations, Dr. Tenma.
We're relying on those brilliant skills of yours.
They think doctors are some kind of
volunteers or something...
Even before saving lives, we doctors
value academics first.
Isn't that right?
I merely operated on that opera singer
like the director told me to.
It is not my fault.
Of course.
Because people's lives aren't equal.
Give him back!
If only you had operated on him, he would have survived!
Give him back!  Give him back!
What is wrong, Dr. Tenma?
I...
I have an operation waiting for me in there.
H-Hey, Dr. Tenma!
This is an order from the director!
The Mayor is currently having a CT scan done on him.
All doctors, please report to the trace-reading
room immediately.
Okay!
Wait, Dr. Tenma!
Dr. Tenma!
You'll be okay.
Hang in there!
I'll save you!
Kill... him....