Mr. Petrov.
No...
Your real name is Mr. Reinhard Biermann...
There was a special orphanage
in East Germany, wasn't there?
A testing site to scientifically correct
the children's personalities...
Kinderheim 511.
You were the director there.
You should know everything.
What were you trying to do?
At that place in old East Berlin?
At Kinderheim 511?
Ghosts of 511
Please wait!
Please wait, Mr. Petrov!
I heard that you're both a psychologist and a psychiatrist.
On top of that, your specialty in the Ministry of Domestic
Affairs was personality programming...
In other words, a form of brainwashing.
I don't get it.
Why was a brainwashing expert appointed
to a mere orphanage?
If it was just to raise the children...
there must've been others who were better suited.
Right?
Go home.
I have no idea what you're talking about!
You should go home.
Where did you hide them?
The records of the experimental
results from Kinderheim 511.
Don't you hear all the rumors?
About the location of the numerous top secret documents
from East Germany after the Berlin Wall came down...
According to one theory...
they were being transported to the Soviet
Union by train via Romania, but...
unfortunately, a revolution took place there...
and the political power of Ceausescu crumbled.
And the documents were lost, never to be found.
But I don't think that's what happened
to the documents regarding 511.
Do you know why?
Because you're a scholar.
For scholars...
research thesis and data are more
important than their lives.
They wouldn't let them go that easily, would they?
I would really like you to show me those documents...
I don't know.
What were you trying to accomplish at Kinderheim 511?
I don't know!
Was the experiment a success?
Is it fun to manipulate people like guinea pigs?
The experiment...
was a failure, wasn't it?
Kinderheim 511 was destroyed by a fire in 1985.
According to the rumors, the children
of the facility killed each other...?
At that time...
I had already been relieved of my duty as the director.
It had nothing to do with me!
That's right.
You were lucky.
Because your successor was the first
one killed during that rebellion.
That kind of thing wouldn't have
happened if I had been there.
The experiment was a success.
Oh?
So that's what you're trying to say?
That during your term of office,
the experiment was going well?
I see.
Which means that...
although it is said that all documents regarding
Kinderheim 511 were burned back then...
it looks like the experimental
data from your term in office...
still remains intact right?
You're treading on dangerous ground.
I won't be held responsible if anything happens to you.
Now you're threatening me?
I'm not really afraid or anything.
Get lost!
No.
I'll accompany you until I discover the truth.
Get lost!
Don't ever show your face around me again!
Grandpa!
We came looking for you because you were late.
Who's this guy?
Oh, it's nothing.
All right, let's go home.
Keep your hands out of this!
He's living the rest of his life surrounded by
his grandsons, and he leads a calm life...
The man who did such horrible things to children...
Yes?
Who is it?
We have something from Mr. Petrov.
Petrov?
Wait right there for a minute.
Although that corner room has a terrible view...
it's pretty convenient at times like these.
There!
Hey, wait up!
All right, shoot!
I've already had a dangerous run-in this morning.
Some weird men came to my hotel.
Are they your grandsons?
That's nice.
It's a quiet and relaxing retirement,
free from worldly cares.
I'm the same way.
When I was a news reporter in old East Germany,
I couldn't even fathom a lifestyle like this...
Since I'm a freelance journalist right now.
Free!
In a socialist society, you couldn't
even think about being free.
Being free is good...
I can follow you around as long as I like.
I've followed you ever since you left your house.
That was a magnificent house.
The rooms looked pretty big.
The rent is fairly high, isn't it?
You spend the entire day sitting at a cafe
and taking walks with your grandsons...
Even though you aren't working
now, this is your lifestyle...
Where is your money coming from?
What did you sell?
Data from your failed experiment?
Did it fetch a good price?
It was a success.
Then it would sell for even more!
Leave me alone!
Just... leave me alone...
Man...
Takes his grandsons to watch a movie...
then they have a chocolate parfait at the cafe...
They're different children again...
One, two...
three, four...
five, six...
Oh, no...
Hi.
This is Mr. Petrov's residence, isn't it?
Can I come in?
Hi!
Oh my Cod...
He's doing... the same thing...
He's conducting the same experiment...
all over again...
Oh my God...
How could that man...
I can't believe he was still conducting the experiment...
You know the red-light district at the
border between here and Germany?
These children were born there.
And right after the Berlin Wall came down...
there are those who were abandoned
because of poverty.
You've gathered children like that...
and are continuing your experiment
from Kinderheim 511 here...
Oh, Mr. Petrov.
Is he your guest?
Yeah...
Don't worry about him.
He's leaving soon.
[Editor's note: Icnedliky = dumplings]
Would you like knedliky for dinner tonight?
Yeah.
Everyone loves your knedliky, Ana.
Continuing my experiment from Kinderheim 511, huh?
I've said it many times already, but...
the experiment there was a success.
There's no need to continue it.
Success, my ass.
It means that the educational program I created...
would definitely nurture a wonderful personality.
Educational...?
What part of that was educational?
That was just human experimentation!
Think carefully.
What is education?
Isn't education meant to create a
person that conforms to society?
What kind of education must be administered...
to create a human being that meets society's demands?
Education is an experiment.
Kinderheim 511...
It's true that an advanced educational
system was established there.
How dare you say that...
after you've done such horrible things...
Horrible things?
Yeah!
Think about what you've done to the children!
You're just an idealist...
Don't act as though you know everything
just because you did some research!
What's with that look?
Are you saying that the incident where
the children killed each other...
was also a result of your experiment?!
Like I said!
That was something that occurred after
I was relieved as the director.
It occurred because an unexpected factor
was introduced into the program.
Unexpected... factor...?
Darkness.
Hatred...
Nihilism...
Destructive impulses...
They're all things that can control human beings.
At that time, Kinderheim 511 was possessed by them...
All thanks to the appearance of a young boy...
You're saying that you're not responsible for that, either?
Like I've said many times...
the experiment was a success.
That's a lie!
There is a common trait among everyone
who came out of Kinderheim 511.
They...
cannot love anyone.
You make an interesting point.
Now then, that's all I have to say.
I'll ask you to leave.
Please don't intrude on me anymore.
No.
The Czech Republic is a democratic country now.
I'll report you to the police.
You don't have the right to manage
an orphanage in this country.
This place is unapproved.
If I file a report, you'll be arrested.
A deal?
In exchange for not reporting me...
you want me to hand over my experimental data to you.
That's the deal you want, right?
Everyone, let's go!
What are you doing?
I know! Let's play soccer!
Soccer?
I want to play soccer!
Okay, let's go!
Let's go! Let's go!
What are you thinking?
It's just like you heard.
We're going out to play soccer.
Hey, everyone!
Mr. Petrov wanted to make a deal with me...
But for your sakes, his deal means nothing to me.
If I report this to the police...
you guys will be free.
You guys want to leave that house, don't you?
No.
There's more freedom outside!
Hey, listen to me!
Hey, mister! The ball's coming your way!
That was so bad!
They're laughing...
How can that be...
It's as though they're truly having fun...
Don't tell me...!
Hey, mister!
Wait for us, mister!
What a pretty lady...
Yeah.
Mr. Petrov!
Could it be that you were trying to...?
What...?
Mr. Petrov!
Mrs. Ana!
What happened, Mrs. Ana?
Mr. Petrov!
Get ahold of yourself!
Grandpa...?
Grandpa!
Who did this to you, Mr. Petrov?!
A woman...
A woman?
Grandpa!
What happened, Grandpa?
You're bleeding, Grandpa!
Mr. Petrov!
Don't tell me you were trying to...
Key...
Key and...
card...
The PIN...
On the back...
of my third drawer...
Inside the safety deposit box...
is my experimental data and a tape...
A tape?
It's an interview... of a young boy...
By administering hypnosis... and prescribing drugs...
we made him speak about his past.
It's the monster that led Kinderheim 511...
down the path of destruction...
Grandpa!
I don't want you to die, Grandpa!
Well?
Were these kids... lacking anything...?
Mr. Petrov, you were...
You were administering education that was totally
different from that of Kinderheim 511...
Hatred...
Nihilism...
Destructive impulses...
I wanted to create a person who wouldn't
be engulfed by darkness...
How does one do that...?
Love...
It really was...
a brand new discovery...
Mr. Petrov...
It's just a perfectly normal, natural thing
that a parent gives to his children...
No...
It's an experiment!
Grandpa!
Yes
Cherish what you know is true in this world.
Ima kono sekai de wakaru koto mitsumete
Yes
Please believe in the kindness of your eyes
Anata no hitomi no yasashisa wo shinjite
Make it home to your land of harmony
Make it home to your land of purity
Make it home