He was discharged?
Yes.  Mr. Johan Liebert left this morning.
1 see...
I heard he had suddenly collapsed, but
I guess it wasn't all that serious...
You're that girl who always comes to the library...
You're the librarian at the college library...
I see, he was discharged?
I'm so glad.
I didn't know what had happened to him...
He collapsed right in front of you?
Yeah...
He was looking for a book.
I was helping him look for it, and...
And he suddenly collapsed?
Yeah, and he was screaming...
Screaming?
He was holding a picture book.
And then, when he flipped the page like this...
A picture book?
At the End of the Darkness
Shouldn't you be resting?
Although...
they didn't find anything wrong with your head.
You're perfectly healthy.
The doctor said that it might have
been caused by anemia or fatigue.
Or maybe you had an emotional shock.
That's what the doctor said, at least.
But I never knew about this.
You have a big scar on your head from an operation?
Either way, you should forget about
working, and just study for now...
Get some rest.
Oh, that's right.
A letter for you arrived while you were in the hospital.
A letter?
There's no return address on it.
Well, I don't think it is a letter bomb, at least.
What?
What's so funny?
Who's it from?
It's from the "Red Hindenburg."
Looks like a pretty one has wandered in.
Are you lost?
Or are you trying it for the first time?
I'll gently teach you everything, starting at the beginning.
Come with me.
Do you know where the Red Hindenburg is?
It's written here that the Red Hindenburg
is somewhere around here.
At your age?
You've sure got some weird tastes.
She's down that way.
Pills...
Give me some pills...
Is the Red Hindenburg up ahead?
Come in!
I'm glad you came.
Have a seat.
Yes, yes. That's the face.
You have a pretty face.
1 saw you on the news with Schuwald.
After calling yourself Margot Langer...
you now call yourself the Red Hindenburg?
Until recently, I was Blue Sophie.
Names don't mean anything.
Isn't that right, Johan Liebert?
Anyway, that's what my boyfriend calls me now.
My boyfriend who's on the other side of that door.
Right, honey?
So I wouldn't think about doing anything foolish.
He's got a really big gun cocked
on the other side of that door.
He's got a really big cock too!
You really got me.
What a meticulous plan to get back
at that rich bastard Schuwald.
No, I'm really impressed.
You brought in a kid named Fahren once, remember?
But I never thought Schuwald's real
son would appear after that!
I feel sorry for Fahren.
Once there was no more use for
him, he committed suicide. .
Anyway, it took two years to get here...
Luckily, the real Margot Langer passed away
at the perfect time two years ago too.
And her passing sure helped me a lot.
It's not like I was really close to her anyway...
She wasn't a street walker!
She had cleaned herself up already.
We just had a drink two or three times, that's all.
She probably didn't have anyone to talk to for a long time.
I got her a little drunk, showed some crocodile
tears, and she told me everything.
Her love affair with Schuwald...
The son she gave up for adoption...
And then that woman got herself killed.
Thanks to that, I played the role of Margot Langer
and got a big pile of cash from Schuwald!
Although the police filed Margot's case
as just another phantom killer...
I don't think the police would've ever suspected
that a plan like this was in motion.
Oh yes.
That detective Richard was a sad case, too.
If only he hadn't interfered.. .
he wouldn't have had to "commit suicide."
Now then, how many people have you killed?
Now then...
let's cut the small talk...
and get down to business.
You can't run anymore.
You should just give up.
Isn't that right, honey?
Say it!
How much are you willing to offer?
Are you listening to me?
What do you think the most frightening thing is?
I thought I had seen the darkest place...
Changing the subject isn't going to do you any good.
But beyond that...
I have found an even deeper darkness.
Hey, wait!
You think you can just leave?
I've quit.
I'm not interested in Schuwald anymore.
Cut the crap!
That's useless...
because I don't exist.
Don't you look down on me, damn it!
Honey!
Come out, honey!
H-Honey...!
W-What are you...?
R-Roberto?!
Can I have a balloon?
You can buy your pills with this.
Carstensen Street
(Munich)
Are you done yet, Doctor?!
It hurts!
His head is bleeding
What are you talking about?
It hurts! It hurts! It hurts!
My child comes first!
Shut him up! It's just a broken bone!
God, he is  so annoying!
Why don't you two stop arguing...
and just sit down and wait your turn
No matter how much commotion you guys make,
there's only one good doctor around here.
Right?
What's that long stick thing?
Well... it's something...
Is the doctor here really good?
Of course!
If this doctor wasn't here, all the Asians around here
would be dead by now, especially the Vietnamese.
Is that so?
You're not Vietnamese, are you?
No...
Hey, wait your turn!
You don't look too good, but the injured come first.
No, I'm not really a patient or anything...
Hey, just sit down and wait!
Hurry up and take a look at him, Doctor!
My son first!
Please excuse me.
What?
Get in line, damn it!
Excuse me, Doctor...
I have something I'd like to ask you...
How many times do I have to tell you?!
Go wait outside!
1 don't have time for you right now!
A girl?
And she's very...
Didn't you hear me?
Get out!
Just how old is this doctor...?
I'm in the middle of suturing, so don't bother me!
If something happens to this patient, it'll be your fault!
A stab wound to the femur...
Caused by a knife...
Her suture is pretty clean...
But...
You should insert a drainage tube.
Keep quiet!
If you can't, you should take him to a real hospital.
A real hospital?
This place is also...
This isn't a hospital.
I can tell just by looking at you.
You're not a real doctor.
If I could take him to a real hospital,
I would've done so long ago.
The majority of the people here are either
illegal residents or illegal immigrants.
If they went to a real hospital...
they'd be sent to an institution immediately.
And then deported back to their home country.
Do you know how many people around here died
because they couldn't go to a real hospital?
Don't talk big when you don't know anything!
Insert a drainage tube!
There's a good chance that he was
stabbed with a dirty knife.
If you don't treat him with a drain insertion...
the wound will fester...
and an abscess will form!
O-Okay!
Undo one or two stitches.
Okay!
Insert the drainage tube about 5cm deep.
Okay, everything went well.
Okay. Who's next?
You're awake.
I heard about it from a patient.
You've been taking care of them for 48
hours straight without sleep, right?
I also looked at the conditions of
the patients after their surgeries.
That was pretty good for an unlicensed doctor.
How old are you?
Seventeen...
I'm surprised at how skilled you are at your age...
You're like a real medical practitioner...
I was lucky...
The doctor that opened his practice here...
just happened to disappear without any explanation,
and left his equipment behind.
This isn't something you can do just
because you have the equipment.
Where did you learn skills like these?
Because my father... was a doctor...
Was?
My father was a Vietnamese doctor.
He took me with him to East Germany to study abroad.
And then he stayed, and opened up a small clinic.
But then the Wall came down.
Even with his limited ability, he tried to save the Asians...
And so they targeted him...
My father was killed by some punks
calling themselves the neo-Nazis.
He was killed because his skin color was different.
1 was suddenly alone, and was sent off to an orphanage.
Afterwards, 1 was taken in by a German family.
But they only took me in, out of
a sense of social obligation.
I was just a poor little yellow-skinned girl...
That's why I ran away.
I had been helping my father ever since I was little.
I also read many of,the medical
books my father left behind.
So I decided to follow in his footsteps.
Move aside.
I'll do the rest.
Okay, you're done!
If you want it to heal quickly, then take it easy.
Okay.
Then, will the next patient...
We're done.
You should go home and study properly.
This country gives chances to those who want to study.
It seems like you're a real doctor.
You're trying to say that amateurs
should just step aside, is that it?
That's not what I'm saying!
I just...
If I go away, what's going to happen to these people?
Who's going to take care of them?
No, that's why you...
Mommy!
W-What's wrong?!
M-My p-pimp went nuts... and pulled a gun... on me...
Mommy!
She walked all the way here after she was shot?
Mommy said you can treat her!
B-But...
Help!
Please help my mommy!
I... I understand!
It'll be okay!
Leave it to me!
Please, Doctor!
Mommy!
She's a prostitute.
They always end up like this...
I want to do something to help her...
but this is impossible...!
Let's get her onto the operating table!
Lift that side up!
It's impossible!
We have to go to a real hospital for something like this!
It'll be too late if we carry her to a hospital!
I know my limits!
I can t do anything about this!
Don't give up until the very end!
If the patient is still breathing...
don't give up hope until the very end!
Don't throw away your hope!
If her intraabdominal arteries were damaged...
her blood pressure would immediately drop...
and she'd go into a state of shock.
However, if she managed to walk all the way here...
her blood pressure is steadily dropping,
and she's in a state of pre-shock.
Judging by this gunshot wound...
there's a good chance that part
of the spleen was damaged.
Which means there's still hope if we perform an
emergency laparotomy while making a blood transfusion.
Now, let's begin
Pick up the scalpel!
Looks like he's sound asleep.
Luckily, her bones, intestines, and digestive
system weren't damaged.
We were fortunate that we only had
to remove the damaged spleen.
It was an excellent operation.
It was all because you were there...
Mommy...
Dr. Tenma...
Please stay here.
I came here because there was something
I wanted to ask you.
This news article...
Blue Sophie...
Also known as the Red Hindenburg...
I heard you were the first to arrive at
the murder scene of this prostitute...
Yes...
Will you tell me what the crime scene looked like?
That night, I came rushing in after receiving
a call from someone in town.
She had been shot in the head.
Death was instantaneous.
I've seen numerous crime scenes like that.
But this was the first time...
The feeling when 1 entered that room...
It wasn't a robbery...
It wasn't hatred...
She was... simply killed...
Johan!
If you stay in the darkness,
you'll sink into the darkness...
Shine light upon it..
Listen to me. Study hard.
I'm sure you can become a doctor.
I'm sure you'll be a good doctor.
Wait!
Where are you going Dr. Tenma?
You...
You seem like you're falling into
a deeper darkness than I am.
You'll come back again, won't you, Dr. Tenma?
Yes
Cherish what you know is true in this world.
Ima kono sekai de wakaru koto mitsumete
Yes
Please believe in the kindness of your eyes.
Anata no hitomi no yasashisa wo shinjite
Make it home to your land of harmony
Make it home to your land of purity
Make it home