The number of casualties from the fire at the Friedrich
Emmanuel Library at Munich University...
has now risen to five dead, thirty-four injured.
The search for the missing people still continues.
We were able to interview some of those
rescued, so please have a look.
I-It became a sea of fire before I
realized what was happening...
I thought I was done for when I was surrounded
by all the smoke and couldn't breathe...
Someone saved us!
Yes, he was Asian.
Is he alright?
He shot the hinges off the door and opened it for us.
Many more people would've
died if he hadn't been there
The authorities have concluded that this
fire was set using oil and gasoline...
and have announced that they will find the
person responsible as soon as possible.
The Hell In His Sight
Everything burned nicely.
Despite saying how books are the wisdom
and property of mankind...
if they burn, that's the end of them.
Any fingerprints from the sniper rifle?
Since it also burned, I'm not sure
if we'll find any fingerprints...
The model is most certainly the Mauser
SR-93 that the Asian man...
whom we believe to be Dr. Tenma ordered.
But since everything burned this badly...
it'll be hard to find any traces of the culprit.
No scene is completely devoid of evidence.
Here's a cuff link that was on the floor.
Take it to be analyzed.
Someone was here.
No one can leave a place without leaving
traces of his existence behind.
If he can, then he's not human.
Then, if by chance there's no evidence to be found...
Then he's...
A demon.
There is no such thing in this world.
That's why there's no criminal we can't catch.
Can I get an interview with Schuwald?
Ah, he's in the intensive care unit right now.
His burns aren't very serious...
but he is rather old.
So they're not allowing any visitors right now.
Let's go.
Huh?
No, you can't!
I can't give you permission to question him!
He's conscious, isn't he?
We'll only be a few minutes.
Mr. Schuwald is currently in a state of extreme shock!
He needs all the rest he can get!
Who is that person?
He's Mr. Schuwald's son.
You have my sympathies for this terrible tragedy.
I'm Lunge from the German BKA.
Um, I asked the police earlier, but...
there's someone I'd like you to find for me...
Who is this?
He's the person who tried to assassinate your father.
You really don't know him?
No, I don't.
But maybe he would...
He?
Yes, that's what I wanted to ask!
Please find Johan Liebert for me!
Johan... Liebert...
Johan should have attended the ceremony
at the library with my father!
But I can't find him anywhere,
no matter where I look...
Johan...
Johan Liebert.
I understand.
I'll request a search immediately.
This is the room Johan Liebert was renting.
He already moved out about two weeks ago, though...
His name wasn't in the registry at the law school.
He's not really a student.
Have you contacted his parents living in Offenbach?
Nobody was living there.
I heard they weren't too friendly
with their neighbors, either.
Should we try collecting fingerprints
in this room anyway?
You probably won't find anything.
No input data available...
This is the first time I've seen...
a room with so few traces of the
person who was living here.
I am Johan...
I am Johan Liebert...
Who am I...?
I was here.
But I do not exist.
A demon, huh?
I'm so glad you weren't hurt too badly, Nina.
I'm sorry I made you worry, Lotte.
Yeah, I was so worried!
Even though they were pulling people out one
after another, I didn't see you anywhere.
So I became really worried.
But I'm surprised you were able to get out of
that fire by yourself, with those injuries.
Even the firefighters were surprised.
Because someone helped me...
Someone helped you?
You were the last to come out of there.
A Japanese man...
Is there a Japanese doctor being treated
in a hospital around here?
There were several Japanese men, but...
I heard they were all businessmen.
That can't be...
Because he helped me when I was
crushed under the drop curtain...
Nina...
Nina!
Nina.
He was definitely there...
I heard that right before the fire broke out...
you told the people attending the
ceremony to evacuate, correct?
Why did you do that?
You sensed something beforehand...
Am I wrong, Mr. Schuwald?
Um, could you please...
Also, do you know this man?
Can you see it if I hold closer?
He's the man who tried to assassinate you.
There are witnesses who say they
definitely saw him at the library.
According to the witnesses, this man...
was trying to save the lives of others...
That's enough!
Please stop this!
Please contact us immediately
if you remember anything.
Oh, one more thing.
Do you know the whereabouts of
your secretary, Johan Liebert?
Please, leave now!
Looks like he's gone completely senile.
Well, I guess it's no surprise, after
having such a shock at his age...
I guess this is it for the Vampire of Bayern,
the Emperor of the Financial World.
No...
Those were the eyes of a man
who understands everything.
Let's try checking out the other witnesses.
Do you have a list of victims?
Oh, yes.
But I wonder what's going on?
The testimonies say that the person we
believe to be Tenma was saving lives.
I suppose this is another case
of his multiple personalities?
Nina...
Nina Fortner...
Something special about that name?
Miss Nina Fortner left the hospital this morning.
The address listed in the police registry was a fake.
How about the one listed here?
I'll go look it up.
Nina Fortner...
The daughter of the Fortners who
were killed in Heidelberg.
Current whereabouts unknown.
Thank you for speaking to me
of such difficult matters.
It fits perfectly with what Tenma says has
been going on for the past ten years.
Tenma?!
That's right.
He came here while investigating a string of cases.
And he left immediately.
In order to assassinate Johan.
On that day, at that library...
I thought Tenma was going to execute
his assassination plan...
so I rushed to the scene.
However, there was that big fire.
We don't know if Johan was there
or not, much less Tenma...
Listen to me, Nina.
Stop chasing after Johan.
He's not someone you can go up against.
It's true that the police aren't being compliant.
Let's just get ready and fight with caution.
The truth will be revealed one day.
It's okay!
We're here with you!
You're tired, aren't you?
You can stay at my place and rest for a while.
He was there when it happened.
When it happened, he was
definitely there at the library.
Tenma was definitely there.
You should eat something.
Thank you, Dieter.
The bread is Kaisersemmel.
I put roast ham and Gouda cheese on it.
It's Tenma's favorite.
Thanks.
It's delicious!
Really?
Yeah.
I feel much better when I eat something delicious.
Tenma always said that, too.
I want to see him.
I want to see Tenma.
Yeah.
It's getting nicer out.
Oh, I know.
How about we go on a vacation once you get better?
How about we go to Asia?
I think it'll be a good change of pace.
From now on, please take it easy.
You've fought long enough, Dad.
Bridge...
The Three...
What is it?
What are you trying to say?
The Three... Frogs...
His eyes...
Eyes?
There was hell...
in his eyes...
There was hell in the eyes of a living man...
Karl...
Yes?
There's something that I want you
to tell a certain man for me...
Y-Yes!
In Dresden...
a man is waiting...
Dresden?
What should I tell him?
Okay.
S-So all I have to do is go to Dresden
and tell that person the message?
R-Right away?
I understand.
I'll go right away
Karl...
Your mother...
Your mother must have hated me
so very much, didn't she?
No...
She didn't hate you at all.
Karl...
When you come back from Dresden...
will you stay with me forever?
Yes.
I'm scared...
Scared?
Scared of what?
I don't really know...
but I'm very scared.
Try to remember.
You don't have to rush.
Just take it slowly.
In a town straight out of a fairy tale...
A fairy tale?
Where is that?
The thing that you felt when you
looked at this picture book.
Anything's okay.
Just say whatever comes to mind.
Dr. Gillen...
No, just a little more...
Please stop it!
The Three...
The Three Frogs...
Frogs?
What is that?
A drawing...
A drawing?
Is it in this book that Johan read,
and the reason why he fainted?
There weren't any frogs in that book.
Where did you see it?
That's enough.
Let's stop here for today.
Okay...
It was a mistake to rely on that BKA agent Lunge.
Yes.
I think it would be wise if we c
hanged our plan, as well.
The next time we bring any
evidence to the police...
we must negotiate directly
with the people in charge.
Not only that, but we must present
the materials after we've...
taken our time to completely
back up our investigation.
Taken our time...?
How long would that take?
Right now, our information regarding
Johan is too vague and inadequate.
Schuwald, the one employing Johan as a secretary...
I think he has some information, but...
Schuwald still can't have any visitors.
How's his son, Karl?
Well, he left for somewhere two days ago...
and I can't reach him.
It's not definite, but amongst the
testimonies of the witnesses...
there are some who say that an Asian
man was helping people out.
But if Tenma's fingerprints were on the sniper rifle...
that was said to be found at the scene...
no testimony will do us any good.
How long must we wait?
There isn't much time left!
When the truth is revealed and the
police start to make their move...
When that happens, it's...
Tenma will...
already be...
Nina...
I-I'm sorry.
Nina, I understand how you feel.
I've also lost an important friend, Richard, in this case.
He had a bright future.
However, Johan cut his future short!
I won't back down?
No matter what!
Now, let's eat!
The Three Frogs...
A town from a fairy...
tale...
I've got it...
Dieter...
I'm going with you.
What are you talking about?
You can't!
You're going to stay here, okay?
Tell Dr. Reichwein thanks for
taking such good care of me.
Goodbye.
Dieter!
I want to see him...
I want to see Tenma!
Dresden
(Saxony)
No luck on the third day either, huh...
He told me to wait at the station square, but...
This place is too big...
Dad, I don't think I'll be able to meet
the man you were talking about.
Karl...
You're Karl, aren't you?
Y-You are...
The man who was plotting to kill your father...
Is that what the police told you?
Y-Yeah...
I've been watching you from the top
of the building for three days.
It doesn't seem like the police are following you.
Will you tell me the message?
Hang on!
We're almost out!
You should... hurry up and run...!
The police are coming...
B-But...
Dresden...
Wait at-the train station...
My son Karl will give you a message...
Hurry and give me the message.
Here.
Cedok Bridge...
The Three Frogs...?
And my father also said this...
"If the monster you are after is a twin..."
"the mother of the twins..."
"is alive in Prague."
Yes
Cherish what you know is true in this world.
Ima kono sekai de wakaru koto mitsumete
Yes
Please believe in the kindness of your eyes
Anata no hitomi no yasashisa wo shinjite
Make it home to your land of harmony
Make it home to your land of purity
Make it home