So she saw Johan, huh?
Guess I'll kill her after all.
I must have seen something I shouldn't have.
I saw him late one evening last year,
that beautiful, blond haired boy.
You kill those who see Johan, right?
I heard three shots, got scared...
...and started running.
I was sure Dr. Tenma was hit.
But the next day...
...the newspaper said that some guy named Junkers
was shot three times and died instantly.
That boy pulled the trigger, right?
Are you going to shoot me?
If you shoot me, you'll never get them...
Those pictures of Johan when he was
a child that you've been looking for.
What do you think will happen if you shoot me?
The pictures will automatically be delivered to the BKA.
If you want those pictures, tell me where Tenma is.
What is so funny?
Your legs are shaking.
You are acting pretty tough, but
you can barely stand, right?
You are an interesting woman.
I'll tell you.
What is Tenma doing now?
He is still a doctor, of course, but an unlicensed one.
Where is he?
There is a guy who rose to second in command
in this syndicate...
...and the boss became afraid of
him and tried to do him in...
...but only managed to wound him.
Tenma is treating him in a mountain lodge...
...near Füssen.
Men's Dining Table
Why have you been standing here for so long?
It's almost lunch time.
What are you up to?
What am I...?
Well, the weather is great today.
So, I'm thinking of having lunch outdoors.
Having lunch outdoors?
Dieter, bring those plates over here.
Okay!
Your rehab is coming along nicely.
Getting some sunshine will be good for you.
Dr. Tenma, you really saved my life.
You performed a perfect operation at
such an old clinic in a country town.
No, your head was only grazed, and the other
bullet passed directly through your leg.
Your anterior tibial artery wasn't hit.
You are lucky.
I'm lucky, huh?
Lunch is served!
That sure smells good.
Do you like it?  It's really good, huh?
Even though Heckel my not look like
a chef, his cooking is fantastic.
What do you mean by that?
This is Chicken Marengo.
The magic is in the sauce.
This is the secret recipe from the 3 star
restaurant "Le Petit Besson."
You are always bragging.
Kids wouldn't understand such things.
If you add a little soy sauce, I
think it might be even better.
You put soy sauce on everything you eat.
Are you complaining about my cooking?
A dining table...
This is what it's like to sit at a dining table.
I was willing to do almost anything for money.
Why did I bother making all that money?
I left home, made enemies of my brothers...
...and watched my wife and child get murdered.
And all I ever wanted was to sit at a table like this.
Money can corrupt a person.
Have you ever heard this story?
Five years ago, something similar to a bank...
...that monopolized all black market
money in Germany was established.
That was one hell of an operation.
We turned all the dirty money into clean, legit money.
That's money laundering, right?
Yes.
The organization borrowed and
traded like any normal bank.
It grew and amassed a huge fortune in only five years.
Then, the head of this organization suddenly
disappeared earlier this year.
What do you think happened after that?
Chaos...
Beyond your imagination.
There was a huge fight over who would control the money.
Most of the people died, and the organization collapsed...
...when all they needed to do was sit around
a table like this and talk things out.
I wonder what happened to that leader?
The one who suddenly disappeared?
I bet he was killed, right?
No.
He's alive... somewhere.
He might be a student at some school.
Student?
Yeah, don't be surprised when I tell you this.
Rumor has it that when that man, no, that child
started the organization five years ago...
...he was only fifteen years old.
Fifteen years old?  You have got to be kidding me.
There is no way a fifteen year old
could do something like that.
Nevertheless, he managed it.
As if he were experimenting on adults'
behavior towards money...
...like a kid crushing a line of ants.
Where was it?
Where was this black market bank?
The organization was headquartered in Düsseldorf.
The top guy was always moving about
and giving orders from various places.
Where was he last, before he disappeared?
I don't know the details, but the people who were
dazzled by the money all went to Munich.
Munich.
What's wrong, Doctor?  You look pale.
Hey, let's invite the man at the
bottom of the hill up for lunch.
Y-Yeah, let's do that.
I'm sorry, but as my bodyguard, he's got a job to do.
They think you are already dead.
Or do you think they are still after you?
Do you plan on keeping the protection you've always had?
He's been with me a long time.
Hey, boy... Helmut...
So his name is Helmut!
Yeah, tell him that he doesn't need
to be my bodyguard anymore.
He's the last friend I have.
Tell him to join me here at the table,
and we'll talk about our future plans.
Okay.
Mr. Helmut, lunch is ready!
Everyone is waiting for you!
Tenma is at the top of this hill.
You wanted to kill him, right?
What is it?
Something has happened to Helmut
at the bottom of the hill.
Helmut is probably...
Your enemies?
I don't know.
But...
I do know that someone is on his way up here.
Mr. Helmut...!
Go tell him...
...to hurry up and get away from here.
Tell him to hurry up and get away from here.
Now go!
Lady!
Hurry up and go.
But...
...your leg is...
I'm fine, just go!
Where is he shooting from?
Did you get him?
I don't know.
Forget that, just go!
I can't!  If I leave you here, you will be killed!
Don't worry about me, you have to hurry!
I said I can't...
I gotta hide you in the woods...
What the...
After all that, she...
...really didn't want to kill Tenma.
Are you okay, lady?
I'm fine.
But that guy may already be at the lodge.
No.
This is the only road up to the lodge.
What do you mean?
I've been up and down this hill lots of times.
You can't get up any other way because of the cliffs.
So that means...
...as long as we are here, that guy won't be able
to get up there without going through us.
"That guy"?  Who is he?
Roberto.
He's after Tenma.
After Tenma?  Who are you lady?
Are you Tenma's friend?
What is so funny?
First of all, call me "miss," not "lady."
Now, quickly, go and tell Tenma to run away.
But lady... I mean miss...
Like I said before, I'll be fine!
But you are bleeding pretty badly.
I'll go get Tenma, he will be able to help you.
Didn't I tell you that Roberto is out to kill Tenma?
If Tenma comes here, Roberto will
get exactly what he wants.
But if we run away, you will bleed to death, lady.
Didn't I tell you not to call me "lady"?
How do you know Tenma?
He's my friend.  How about you, la-- miss?
You are his friend, right?
You are protecting him even though you have been shot.
You like Tenma, don't you?
Are you Tenma's girlfriend?
Keep your eyes on your own side!
Do you like Tenma?
Yeah, a whole lot.
What do you like about him?
What do YOU like about him, miss?
Roberto!  If you think you can keep hiding
and toying with us, think again!
Like I said...
If I die, the pictures of Johan that you want...
...will automatically be delivered to the BKA.
If you want those pictures, get your ass out of here!
You know his weak spot, huh?
I'm lying.
Huh?
He may not fall for it...
Are you okay, miss?
I couldn't possibly be okay.
Hey, get out of here...
I can't leave you here.
Tenma will soon...
He's not going to come.
Yes he will!  Tenma will...
He won't be coming to rescue me.
He's not coming...
Dieter!
Dieter!  Where are you?
Tenma, I'm over here!
I'm coming!
Stay right where you are!
Don't come!
If you come over here now, you'll be shot!
You are his target!
T-That voice...
This lady is your friend!
She got shot, and she is bleeding pretty badly!
Eva!
I can't let you die here.
My goal it to take you in alive.
I want you to spend the rest of your life
in prison, regretting what you did.
Regretting that you ever dumped me!
Don't talk so loudly!
Dieter!  Can you hear me, Dieter?
Can you tell where the shooter is from where you are?
I can't tell!
I have no idea where he is hiding!
Don't come...
I can't let you die...
Hang on lady!
He wouldn't come...
...to save me.
He wouldn't...
Lady!
He wouldn't come...
Ten...ma...
What are you doing?
We are going to have lunch.
You are recovering very nicely.
You are well enough to have lunch
outside in this fine weather.
You are lucky.
I'm lucky?
Yeah.
The guy who shot you is a top notch professional.
He estimated how difficult it would be
to attack this lodge pretty well.
There is only one route up here.
It was pretty obvious that he couldn't come barging in...
...without knowing how much security I have.
That's why he used you.
He used me?
That's right.
He must have figured that the best way
to get in was for a woman to drop by.
But you betrayed him.
So, when that happened, his plan failed...
...and he quickly left.
He left?
Yes.
He was not hiding in the woods.
This is Chicken Marengo.
I don't know if it's any good, since
I copied the recipe from someone.
You are also lucky that you were...
...treated by Dr. Tenma, an outstanding physician.
Where is Tenma?
He's gone.
Where to?
He seemed very interested in Munich.
Munich?
Should we get started?
It seems that you also forgot...
...what it's like to eat at a dining table.