Oh, man...
Hopefully, we can hush everything up...
I sure could use a drink right now!
I've got some whiskey bonbons!
Hey, don't be like that.
I got these from a very hot chick!
What's wrong?
You look depressed...
I can't trust anyone now...
You can tell me, if you want...
I believed in him.
I never thought that Inspector Zeman, of all
people, would do something like that...
What happened?
I believed in him, and yet...
Right now...
the only peace in my heart...
is you.
An unbelievable, shocking development has
occurred at the Prague police department.
Chief Hamrik, Head Detective Patera, and Detective
Janacek were all found dead by poisoning.
What could have forced the killer to carry
out such a bold and horrific act?
With the shady connection rumored to exist
between the police and the secret police...
will this event trigger the discovery
of an even greater scandal?
Someone's coming out!
Do you know who the killer is?!
We've heard that the substance used in the murders...
was a muscle relaxant. Any comments?
Is it true that even the late Chief Hamrik
had ties to the secret police?
Well... that's, uh...
Any connections to last week's
murder of Inspector Zeman?!
W-We're still... investigating that matter...
You're saying that the investigators believe
that all these cases are somehow related?!
No!
What I'm trying to say is that we're going
to explore every aspect of these cases...
I'm terribly sorry.
He's in charge of another case, so...
Don't say anything unnecessary! Hurry up and go!
Y-Yes, sir.
When will you be holding an official press conference?
We will hold a press conference once
we have some information.
So please wait patiently until then.
That'll take too long!
The Two Darknesses
Please stop it already!
More questioning?!
I'm terribly sorry.
I was ordered by my superiors to re-examine
this case from the very beginning, so...
I've already talked to the children who were
taken in by other orphanages, so...
Try to put yourself in these children's shoes!
These children...
They saw Mr. Petrov, a man who raised
them in place of their parents...
and his assistant die right before their eyes.
Even now, there are children who have nightmares.
I'd like them to forget all about it
as soon as possible, and yet...
And yet...
I suppose it's not something they'll ever forget.
After all, someone they loved was killed...
Fifteen minutes per child!
Don't ask them anything too graphic.
Understand?
Yeah, living there was fun.
Both Mr. Petrov and Ms. Ana were really nice.
I see.
Well then, I want to ask you some things
about the day of the incident...
Did the guy who visited that dayr Mr.
Grimmer, ever come by before?
No, that was his first time.
Why do you think he was there?
I don't know.
Were Mr. Petrov and Mr. Grimmer
friendly with each other?
They didn't seem to be all that friendly, but...
But?
They were talking about something really complicated.
You guys know a little German, don't you?
What kinds of things were they talking about?
Something about, "This place is unauthorized..."
And, "I'll tell the police. "
Mr. Grimmer said that?
Yeah.
Also, something about "education" and "experiments."
Experiments?
Anything else?
And...
It's okay if it's something you don't
want to remember, Honza.
Oh, and something about "Kinderheim 511."
Kinderheim... 511...?
Do you know what that place is?
I don't know.
What about you, ma'am?
There is no such orphanage in the Czech Republic.
About Mr. Grimmer...
What kind of person was he?
He was a really nice man!
You too, Izzy?
We played soccer together!
He wasn't really good at it...
but Mr. Grimmer looked like he was having fun, too!
He was really bad at heading the ball!
He even landed on his butt!
He's probably the second worst, next to Honza!
Oh, and also...!
I heard that you were the leader
at that orphanage, Antonin.
It wasn't like I was the leader or anything.
It was just because I was a little older than everyone else.
About that day...
About Mr. Grimmer?
Honza and Izzy said they were questioned
about Mr. Grimmer, so...
Y-Yeah...
And?
He's a nice person.
Could it be that you suspect Mr. Grimmer?
No, that's not the case...
Mr. Grimmer isn't the killer.
He was playing soccer with us.
And when we came back, Mr. Petrov
and Ms. Ana had already been killed.
I already told this to the police!
But we saw it!
We saw a pretty blonde lady leave
our house and walk away.
Are you going to arrest him?
Arrest who?
Mr. Grimmer!
No...
We haven't decided anything like that yet, but...
I'm going to meet up with him soon.
We made a promise!
We've already decided where we'll meet, too!
Are you going to tell me?
Yeah.
You sure?
I may end up arresting him.
Because he would never kill anyone!
Yo!
It's been a while.
Is everyone doing okay?
We're totally fine!
You sure you guys weren't crying like babies?
This guy wet his bed twice!
I used to wet my bed until I was
much older than you guys!
Antonin.
Do you still have that thing I left with you?
Thank you.
Thank you for taking good care of it.
This is something important that your grandpa gave me.
Now then...
I don't have much time.
Everyone, take care of yourselves.
Let's play soccer, Mr. Grimmer!
Oh, I'm sorry.
I really don't have the time...
Let me introduce you to them.
They're our new friends.
Okay!
I guess I'll play for a bit!
Yay!
Go! Now's your chance!
Pass me the ball!
They got the ball!
That's a weak dribble!
Hey, defender! Get a grip, will you?!
Oh, man...
Here I go!
There!
Are you Mr. Grimmer?
Have you come to arrest me?
We're in front of the children.
Don't you dare wave a gun around!
Same goes for you!
Toss me your gun!
I don't have a gun.
You threw it away?
I've never carried one with me before.
Was it you who killed Inspector Zeman?
I don't know...
After all...
I was half dead after being tortured...
Your nails...
I'm not the one who fired the gun.
Although... I may have killed the other two...
but I don't remember.
Mr. Grimmer!
What are you taking a break for?
My team's short one player now!
Give me a break!
I'm already exhausted.
I'm the one who told the children to
invite you to play soccer with them.
I was watching you all this time...
So, what do you think?
Am I the killer?
I don't know.
During these past few days...
I've been betrayed by so many people...
I don't understand anything anymore!
I don't know what to believe in...
The only one you can believe in is yourself.
In the end, you're the only one you can believe in.
You're not going to arrest me?
Will you promise that you won't run away?
Where are you staying right now?
The Pavla Hotel, Room 302.
Come by whenever you're sure that I'm the killer.
I'll entrust that to you.
I think it's the cause of this chain of events.
It's a key to a safety deposit box.
This storefront signboard?
Oh, it's very old.
I hear it was for a tavern that was
here two hundred years ago...
Even though the tavern's no longer
here, the sign still hangs there.
Though the color has faded...
it has become a landmark of this street.
There must have been wars and chaos...
but it has managed to remain standing.
Even during the fire around ten years ago...
Fire?
Yeah...
A woman moved into the second floor with her child.
She was a beautiful woman...
but she seemed kind of gloomy.
She almost never went outside.
And I heard she was using a false name.
And then one day, a black car suddenly came...
and took both the mother and her child away.
We used to gossip about whether she was linked
to the anti-government movement or not.
Back then, talk like that was common.
It was the reign of terror during
the final years of communism...
Those were terrible times...
It wasn't uncommon for someone to suddenly disappear.
Didn't that woman have twins?
No, she only had one child.
That child had a really pretty face.
Was it a boy or a girl?
Oh?
Now that you mention it, I wonder which it was?
When children are young, there are times
when you can't really tell, so...
Well, aside from the mother...
everyone was saying how awful it was that
they even took away an innocent little child.
Then the fire started.
Everyone thought the fire started in a vacant room...
but surprisingly, that child was still in the room!
The child was probably released, and...
I guess it got lonely and hungry and
set a fire to make something to eat.
What happened to the child?
If I remember correctly, it went missing
right after being rescued from the fire.
I wonder what happened to the child after that...
What if that child was one of the twins?
What if one of the twins was taken away...
while the other stayed behind in the room?
I see. That's a possibility.
But why are you so obsessed with this twin thing, anyway?
That tall man named Grimmer you
said I should investigate...
I don't think he's the killer...
I see.
I'm sorry, Mr. Suk, for an amateur like
me telling you such useless things.
He's not a bad person.
I learned a lot of things while chasing him.
At first, I was all worked up, thinking
I would avenge Inspector Zeman...
But as I investigated...
I found out that even Inspector Zeman,
someone I once admired...
was actually really corrupt.
And in the end...
the chief of police and my two senior
detectives were poisoned to death!
After hearing about the poisonings...
I was left completely speechless...
I thought to myself...
just how far the realm of darkness
has spread in this world...
Darkness...?
The Czechoslovakian secret police that
they say are behind this case...
They're an organization controlled by the
former Ministry of Domestic Affairs...
and they worked for the Soviet Union.
But during the democratic revolution
that occurred about ten years ago...
the organization was dissolved.
Although the officials were tried in court...
several of them escaped to the underground...
and are still scheming to regain
the power they once had.
That much I do know!
But why must there be so many victims?
Are the former secret police really
the only ones behind all this?
How far has the darkness spread
into the world we now live in?
I can't believe in anything anymore.
But Mr. Grimmer told me...
that in the end, I'm the only one I can trust.
With that said, he entrusted something to me...
Sorry...
for going on about this...
No, it's okay...
I still don't know your name.
Oh, no! It's fine! You don't have to tell me.
Until now...
I thought trust could only be achieved if people
knew each other's names and backgrounds...
But I can tell you anything like this!
My parents were both teachers.
But my father got marked by the authorities for being
involved in the pro-democracy movement...
and my mother left my father,
thinking only of my future.
When I said I wanted to become a detective...
my mother protested vehemently.
Why did you want to become a detective?
My friends mentioned it before at the bar, didn't they?
Don't tell me you were actually influenced
by those detective dramas...
Yeah!
It's been my dream since I was a child
I was always acting out scenes from those things
Don't laugh so much.
But...
Sor what was the thing you were entrusted with?
You said a while back that you got something
from that Grimmer person.
A key to a bank's safety deposit box.
A safety deposit box?
There's supposed to be something
really important locked inside.
You remember the case...
where a German named Petrov who was operating
an unlicensed orphanage was murdered?
Yeah...
Inside the safety deposit box...
there's supposed to be data from Petrov's
human experiments or something.
It seems that this chain of events is all due to that, and...
You can't say anything!
You mustn't tell the police or anyone else about that!
But this isn't something I can solve by myself...
Do you know why your mother...
why your mother opposed your becoming a detective?
She thought about what could happen to your and...
I sense something very dangerous!
So you must not tell anybody
I feel the same way your mother did, so...
I'm sorry...
My name...
I'll tell you my name.
Anna.
Anna Liebert.
Anna...
That's a nice name...
You're German?
Well, see you later.
Anna...
Good evening, Mr. Tulunka.
Oh, what a nice evening it is, Anna.
Oh, good evening, Anna.
Good evening, Ms. Jalka.
A key to a safety deposit box, huh...?
Yes
Cherish what you know is true in this world
Ima kono sekai de wakaru koto mitsumete
Yes
Please believe in the kindness of your eyes
Anata no hitomi no yasashisa wo shinjite
Make it home to your land of harmony
Make it home to your land of purity
Make it home