"It's okay"?
What do you mean, Mr. Schuwald?
I mean that I want you to stop
the investigation I requested.
Hold on a second.
It's true that the investigation into Karl Neumann is over.
He's your son.
I'm very grateful.
N-No, just hold on a second!
We haven't learned everything.
There is still the possibility that Edmund
Fahren, who claimed to be your son...
...didn't actually commit suicide.
We still haven't found the person
who was controlling Fahren!
Everything has been resolved.
Tea is ready, Father.
Okay.
Oh, hello.
Would you like to join us?
Oh, no thanks.
Thank you for your work.
Send me the bill.
The weather is nice today.
Yeah...
Johan is here, too.
I see.
So Johan is here, too?
That ice cold, solitary man who didn't believe in anyone...
...turned into a  good natured
old man after finding his son?
That smile...
I can't believe he was once called the Vampire of Bayern...
"I see.  So Johan is here, too?"
So...
Just One Case
Now you're running around trying to find a dog?
Yeah...
It seems that my client's ex-husband kidnapped it.
Looks like parental custody of dogs can also be a problem!
Tell me about it...
Excuse me, I'm going to have some wine.
Go ahead.
Water is enough for me.
Even though you are taking a small
break from your line of work...
...it doesn't appear that you are
letting alcohol concern you.
Yes, I'm perfectly okay on that point.
On that point?
Is there something else on your mind?
Well, now that I have some spare
time, I'm doing some silly things.
Oh?
I've been looking through my case scrapbooks
that I made when I was still a detective.
The ones that were unsolved...
I see.
So, how do you feel when you look through them?
I'm mortified!
This murder case...
That murder case...
Just the thought of killers living casually out there...
I feel really helpless.
At my lack of ability, that is...
You did have the ability.
But Richard...
Because you were trying too hard, you
identified with the cases far too much.
Your irritation at your inability to read
the killers' minds became frustration...
...and I turned to alcohol..
Yes, that's right.
Thank you for waiting.
Oh, food time!
However, I don't think it was a bad thing.
Looking through your old case scrapbooks...
It just irritates me even more.
No, you're fine now.
I want you to tell me what you think...
...now that you're looking through
them with your new point of view.
You got drunk and shot that youth, who was a serial killer.
You are now prepared to face that truth.
But you're still running away...
...from remembering what was going through
your mind when you pulled that trigger.
You can still see him, can't you?
That kid's ghost...
Yes...
When everything becomes clear...
...when everything is revealed by daylight...
...that ghost will disappear as well.
Bring everything into the daylight, huh?
"The Murder Case of Holmer the Accountant."
The victim, Joachim Holmer, had a solid career...
...and wasn't the type to be the target of anyone's hatred.
Yet he was stabbed...
No sign of robbery...
"The Murder Case of the Voice of God."
The victims were a former house maid and a driver...
In both cases, there was a message that read "I
heard the voice of God" written on the wall...
"The Murder Case of the President
of the Dolnach Company."
Mr. Rudy Gauck, a prominent, wealthy man in Bayern...
...was found dead in the Hartholz forest.
"The Murder Case of the Spillers."
The drowned bodies of a middle aged couple
were found upstream in the Isar River...
Currently under investigation in connection with the
ongoing serial murders of middled aged couples...
The main suspect, the Japanese doctor, is still on the run...
Man...
The more unsolved cases I had, the more I drank...
But I'm different now.
I see...
It's just like the doctor said.
So this is what it's like to think without
being under the influence...
H-Hold on a second...!
Think carefully...
So...
What passed through your mind then?
Well, that's the thing...
I was thinking of something, but...
You saw the boy's ghost and you forgot
what you were thinking about?
Yeah...
There is no need to rush things.
Eventually, the thought will come back to you.
What was I thinking about...?
An important key to solving one of the unsolved cases...
Just my imagination...
Who's there?
Who's there?!
Who's following me?!
This is exactly like that time!
At the time...
...I was running down an alley like this...
...chasing after him, and...
I'm sorry to come here so late, Doctor.
No, you've decided to tell me everything!
Tell me what you have to say.
Back then, I saw it inside that kid...
And I realized it does exist in this world...
Pure evil...
That's why...
That's why I...
...shot and killed him!
Good, I'm glad you told me.
You've really gotten back on your feet now.
No, there is still more...
I understand now...
That thing I thought of the other day...
The many unsolved cases I left behind, they're actually...
...just one case.
Dear Dr. Gillen...
The literary work you sent me the other day...
"A Transcendental Criminal Psychological Outline."
I read it with great interest.
That one of my students from my days
of teaching at Düsseldorf University...
...is writing works like this fills me with great joy.
By the way, Dr. Gillen...
You once told me of your interview with
the serial murderer, Peter Jurgens...
At that time, Jurgens said to you...
...that he committed a murder because
a certain "friend" ordered him to, but...
...because I can't recall the details, would
you mind telling me the story again?
The name of Jurgens' "friend," that is...
P.S.
You were an excellent student when
you were in college, but...
...there was also another outstanding student who seemed
to be competing with you for the top seat.
He now walks the path of a neurosurgeon, but...
...he's a material witness in the case of the serial murders.
I want you to tell me anything you can about
him, no matter how little it may be.
What kind of person was he..
...and where he is now?
The man named Dr. Tenma...
Oh, you're that detective from before!
No, I'm just a poor private investigator now.
I know it's a painful story, but...
...may I ask you about the "Voice of God"
murder case your mother was involved in?
Of course!
It's been four years now, and the police aren't putting
any effort into the investigation anymore, so...
Schuwald...?
Yes.
I heard that your mother used to be
a maid for that wealthy man...?
Yes, but that was twenty years ago.
Did she quit for any reason in particular?
Poor health, mainly...
After that, she only did work around the neighborhood.
Any chance she didn't get along with Mr. Schuwald?
Oh, no!
Rather, my mother loved to read him poems.
And when Mr. Schuwald could still see,
the two used to recite to each other.
Oh, please come this way.
Here, take a look.
They remind me of my mother,
so I've kept them all this time.
Each poetry anthology on these shelves was
given to my mother by Mr. Schuwald.
I can't believe the officer in charge of the
case of Dolnach's president's murder...
...is a mere detective now.
There is something I want to ask you about,
since you were the president's secretary.
Regarding anyone who hated the president...
The president's enemies...?
I told you that we'd never stop
counting if we started, didn't I?
The list of companies President
Gauck sent into bankruptcy...
...should have already been analyzed by the police.
There is another wealthy, powerful
person in Bayern, isn't there?
What was their relationship like?
You mean Mr. Schuwald?
They were rivals, of course.
Lifelong, might I add.
Did you know?
Schuwald has declared bankruptcy twice in the past.
His second bankruptcy was the result of a fierce
competition between him and President Gauck.
In other words, Mr. Schuwald
was crushed by the president.
On the other hand, there were times when
the president was beaten by Schuwald.
The two hated each other?
Of course!
It would be bad if they saw other other at a party!
The two liked to express their feelings verbally.
Those two?
Yes, those two cold hearted people.
Those two were the only ones who could
match each other in an argument...
Rather than just rivals...
...they were actually friends.
Be careful!
Oh, Hans?
I knew him very well.
He was one of the two victims involved
in the "Voice of God" murder case.
He was a good person.  I felt sorry for him.
He was that good of a person?
Yeah, he used to treat me to drinks quite often.
He used to be Mr. Schuwald's driver, right?
Indeed.
But that was thirty years ago.
Do you know why he was fired?
Because Schuwald went bankrupt at that time.
Oh, I see.
He didn't cause any trouble?
Listen, I'm going to say this in honor of Hans.
It didn't matter if the person was an ass with
a boatload of money, or poor like us.
He was the type of person who
could get along with anyone.
He used to tell us...
...that he was the one who taught
that rich guy how to bird watch.
Bird watch?
Yeah.
Hans said that when he brought him to the forest, he
was as happy as a child, and didn't act like a vampire.
Even though it's been two years since the incident...
...I still remember what happened to my husband...
My husband was a very serious person.
He didn't do anything that people would hate him for.
And yet... the way he was killed...
You have my sympathies.
Excuse me, but I think your husband was...
Yes...
When he was young, he grew up in an orphanage...
...and went from foster home to foster home.
After a lot of hard work, he became an accountant.
Your husband received a request to become
Schuwald's financial adviser, didn't he?
Yes, several times...
But he turned them all down.
It's true that he was too busy with his current job, but...
...he said that his philosophy on money was different from Schuwald's.
My husband was very fastidious with money.
Thank you very much for your help.
Will you catch the murderer?
I'll try my best.
I'm sure he'll be caught!
Goodbye.
Excuse me...
Yes?
Do you happen to know how your husband
became acquainted with Schuwald?
Oh, he said they met in the forest.
In the forest...?
It was when Mr. Schuwald could still see...
They met in the forest by chance.
Why was he there?
He went to bird watch.
After that, they went together several more times.
Bird watching...
Happy like a child...
Recite to each other...
Friends...
Are you okay?
Y-Yes, I'm fine.  Thank you...
What a horrible driver!
It looked like he was actually aiming for you!
I've got it all figured out, Dr. Reichwein.
It's just like I told you the other day.
All the cases I was in charge of when I was still an officer...
...were related in some way!
"The Murder Case of the Voice of God."
"The Murder Case of the President
of the Dolnach Company."
"The Murder Case of an Accountant."
At a glance, these cases don't seem to be related.
The victims were murdered in different ways, too.
Also, the victims were unrelated.
On top of that, because there were no fiscal connections...
...the truth was never recorded.
They were all connected at one point.
The victims' deaths in every case...
...were all done to isolate Schuwald.
And there is another strange common point...
In the murder case of Dolnach Company president...
...right before the crime took place...
...President Gauck left, saying that he
had an important business meeting.
The name of the person he was going to meet...
And also...
...the name of God that was written
on the wall by the killer...
...in the "Voice of God" murder case...
And amongst the cases I was in charge of...
...the only case that seemed to be unrelated...
"The Murder Case of the Middle Aged Couple."
The name of the killer the Japanese doctor
spoke of during his questioning...
They are all the same name...
Johan...
A criminal psychological scholar who
used to be a student of mine...
...is studying a killer who said he committed his
crime because of an order from a "friend"...
He told me everything in a letter.
The name of that "friend" was also...
...Johan.
It's a common name.
The connection in every case may be mere speculation.
However, if you really are correct...
He planned each murder in the past
four years and committed each one.
This person calling himself "Johan"
has completely isolated Schuwald.
And luckily for him, the prostitute named Margo
Langer who gave birth to Schuwald's son is dead.
That Fahren student who claimed to be Schuwald's son...
...just happened to commit suicide right
before the appearance of his real son.
If he really does exist...
...where is this Johan right now?
I see.
So Johan is here, too?
Hi, Johan.
Nice weather today, isn't it?
Yes, very nice.
He's right next to Schuwald!