Everyone is dead...
A devil...
A devil came to this town!
Are you ready?
I'll go in first.
Watch my back.
Our first priority is to help Inspector Lunge.
Okay.
Dr. Tenma!
Wim?
What are you doing here?
A girl came asking about you.
A girl?
She went to the vampire's mansion...
She looked exactly like the twins in the drawings there.
The twins in the drawings?
Nina!
So, they call her Nina now.
She's called Nina now...
Yes.
Nina Fortner.
That's a nice name.
You've always said people should cherish
their names, right, Mr. Poppe?
Hey, have you seen my dad?
I've looked everywhere, but I can't find him.
Okay.
We have something important to do here.
Right after that, let's go find your father.
Dad hasn't killed anyone, has he?
No, Wim.
Your father isn't that kind of person.
Okay, go hide in the general store over there.
Take Wim and find somewhere to hide!
We finally meet, Dr. Tenma.
Let's die...
Let's die together.
Let's die.
The Landscape of the End
Wait, Nina!
We have to find him!
We have to find Franz Bonaparta!
Back then...
at the Red Rose Mansion...
he said to me...
Listen to me, okay?
Forget everything you saw just now.
Run far away from here.
As far as you can.
Because, you see, people...
can become anything.
You are both beautiful jewels.
That's why you can't become monsters.
That's what he said to me!
That's why I...
That's why...!
Mr. Poppe!
Mr. Poppe?
Franz Bonaparta...
Roberto!
R-Run, Wim!
Show me...
"The landscape of the end..."
You...
can't see it.
Wim!
Get back!
Dr. Tenma.
To you, all life was equal.
That's why I was revived.
But you should've realized it by now.
The only thing everyone is equal in...
is death.
You can see it, too.
The landscape of the end.
No!
You must not shoot, Dr. Tenma!
Please don't shoot.
I...
I forgive you.
Even if we were the last two people in the world...
I'd forgive you.
That's what I can do for you...
You can't.
Some things can't be taken back.
I can't turn back now.
Dr. Tenma is going to shoot me.
Isn't that right, Dr. Tenma?
Isn't that right?
Don't!
No!
A devil...
A devil came to this town...
and slaughtered everyone.
Wim!
Don't!
Not my son!
W-What the hell is that?
A monster!
What the hell is that thing?
No!
Get away from him!
Get away from my Wim!
This is the D-KMIF!
We've landed in the western side of Ruhenheim!
We've secured the eastern side of town, too!
Attend to the townspeople immediately!
This is terrible...
Are there even any survivors?
We of the DNN news crew...
have finally managed to make it into
town by climbing a hill to the east.
This case is unprecedented!
It appears that the town was nearly
wiped out in a mass slaughter.
WKat exactly happened in this quiet
town in southern Germany?
Yes.
Like I said, we've only taken one
suspect into custody so far.
Herbert Knaup.
Age 38, unemployed.
Dad!
Yes, he's admitted to the crime.
He said he shot at a young man.
My dad shot him trying to save me!
Well, it appears he has an extremely
high blood alcohol level.
And the reason he said he committed the crime...
was that a seven-headed monster
with horns was attacking his son.
He's spewing some nonsense here.
Dad!
Come in!
Damn it!
I got disconnected again!
Like I said...
I explained exactly what happened.
No, it's just that...
I don't understand what you mean.
A young man named Johan...
annihilated this town so he could commit suicide?
Can you explain it so that even
we can understand, Dr. Gillen?
It will be a long story...
No.
Even if I tell you everything, you
still might not understand.
We've found an injured officer in the Versteck Hotel!
What's his condition?
We don't think his life is in danger...
but he's drifting in and out of consciousness.
Shit!
Isn't there even one officer who
can explain this incident?
Right here.
I know everything.
Who are you?
I'm Inspector Lunge of the BKA.
I don't have my ID on me, though.
Try contacting the BKA.
Roberto.
He's dead.
He's the man who is essentially
responsible for this incident.
I tried to finish him off...
but he lost consciousness.
As I left him and headed downstairs...
I heard his voice behind me.
A moment later...
I received a blow to the back of my head...
and I passed out.
He said something to me at the time.
"I can't see it yet."
"The landscape of the end."
Anyway, we'll get more details after you've been treated.
Stop crying!
Everything is okay now.
Excuse me.
Can I see some identification?
I'm Hennich. I live on Erft Street.
This is my wife, Franka.
Do you have anything that can prove your identities?
Yeah.
What?
What's wrong?
I don't have the lottery ticket!
What?
I... I put it in my pocket!
I'm going to go look for it!
H-Honey!
I must've dropped it somewhere!
It's okay, honey!
We don't need it.
We can live like this.
That's enough for me.
Umm...
Do you have anything to prove your...
Feel free to show me later.
Let's see.
Any other survivors?
Oh, there we are.
Excuse me.
Do you have some identification...?
Check every single one!
There may still be survivors in the buildings!
E-Excuse me!
What's wrong?
I think...
What did you say?
Johan...
Is he alive?
Well, with that head injury...
Even if we had the best neurosurgeon...
No.
There is one person.
Please go get him.
Excuse me.
Might you be...
There's no doubt about it!
He's the fugitive!
Dr. Tenma!
You're Dr. Tenma, aren't you?
Would you please come with me?
Hey, wait a minute!
Inspector Lunge of the BKA is calling for you.
He told me to tell you that there is
a patient who needs you.
My dad isn't a killer!
Listen to me, kid.
There are a lot of things we want to ask your father.
Dad was...
Dad was only trying to save me!
You understand, don't you?
Dad!
I want to forgive him.
Tenma.
You weren't wrong.
What you did back then...
and what you're going to do now.
My dad..!
My dad isn't a killer!
All right, let's begin the operation.
Yes
Cherish what you know is true in this world.
Ima kono sekai de wakaru koto mitsumete
Yes
Please believe in the kindness of your eyes
Anata no hitomi no yasashisa wo shinjite
Make it home to your land of harmony
Make it home to your land of purity
Make it home