Munich
(Germany)
Thank you. We look forward to working with you.
No, we should be thanking you.
We would certainly like to enjoy a round of golf next time.
Oh please go easy on us.
We look forward to your cooperation.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you!
Thank you...
Thank you, huh?
What curious people.
Oh hello.
Sorry to make you wait.
Our business negotiations ran
a little longer than expected...
I'm Iwai, from the Munich branch of Kadofuku AC.
I'm Lunge, from the German BKA.
Nice to meet you.
Thank you.
A thank you and a bow?
Oh, my!
One coffee.
Oh, and another for this gentleman.
Regarding Yamamoto, the person
you wanted to see, Inspector...
He's on a business trip to the Czech Republic.
He's scheduled to return tomorrow.
You seem to be very busy.
Well, do you know of Mr. Schuwald, the
head of the great financial group?
Because he came out of retirement and
started economic activities again...
all the companies in Germany that are
affiliated with him have picked up.
The Japanese trading firms are all busy
making deals with Schuwald.
Why do you laugh...?
So anyway, Yamamoto can't help you today, but...
he and I both know Mr. Kenzou Tenma equally.
I see...
But I'm really surprised.
You're still investigating him?
Yes, because I haven't closed the case yet.
1 was really surprised when Mr. Tehma
was identified as a suspect!
You were surprised?
Was it really that unexpected?
It was beyond unexpected!
1 can't believe he killed someone...
Well, to tell you the truth, I didn't
think he'd do such a thing.
Although we only went out drinking two
or three times three years ago...
he wasn't a bad person.
If you say he's not a bad person...
does that make him a good person?
A good person...?
Actually, he was more...
He wasn't the type who likes to stand out...
So anyone who doesn't like
to stand out is a good person?
Well, it's more like he didn't seem the
uncivil type, is what I'm trying to say.
A Nameless Hero
The Japanese don't usually wear things like this...
The Japanese are skilled with chopsticks...
I am Japanese.
Thank you.
I am...
Tenma.
Hello?
Ah, Father?
How are you?
I'm fine.
I called because I heard you're in Munich.
That's where I'm living now.
The thing is, Father...
My child... was born, and he's perfectly healthy...
1 see...
Congratulations.
Even though a lot has happened,
I still want you to see my son.
Will you come see him?
Of course.
Then, are you free tomorrow?
Yeah, I should be free after six.
Where shall we meet?
Yeah...
The Marienplatz...
Okay, got it.
Goodbye.
Thank you.
You're good with chopsticks.
You think so?
Although lately, there have been many foreigners
who use chopsticks better than the Japanese.
So Dr. Takahashi...
From the perspective of someone in the same
business, what kind of person was Tenma?
What kind?
Let's see...
He wasn't too unsociable...
Although he was indecisive at times...
But...
He turns into a completely different
person when he holds a scalpel.
They called him a genius surgeon...
and that was definitely not an exaggeration.
What about his parents?
He didn't want to talk much about them.
But he did say that both his father and
his older brother are doctors...
Well, I guess he had no choice
but to become a doctor.
Speaking of which...
I heard he didn't return to Japan even once
after he became a doctor in Germany.
His parents didn't come to
Germany during that incident...
and they didn't seem interested
in proving their son's innocence.
I guess his family isn't all that close.
I'm terribly sorry.
1 received a call from Yamamoto.
He did arrive in Munich from Prague, but...
it seems he has to meet with a client right away.
He seems to be very busy.
Oh, he did say that he'll be coming to
the restaurant we're heading to now.
The restaurant...?
I know!
Why don't you come with us, Inspector Lunge?
This must be fate!
And we don't know when we'll
be needing your help again.
No, I can't today.
I guess his family isn't all that close.
1 am...
Tenma.
Sounds great.
Please let me go with you.
KARAOKE PUB
Ooedo
Farewell, Pleiades.
I will be going now.
Farewell, Pleiades!
Nice going, Iwai-chan!
How about it? Would you like to sing one?
Yeah!
Oh, the next song is mine!
Nice!
Let's hear it!
Love letter from Canada.
If you were here with me...
Nice! Nice!
Oh, what a wonderful trip it would be.
I am Tenma.
Love letter from Canada.
I can't blend into Japanese society...
I don't ask for help here...
I don't have a place to go home to...
1 am...
alone.
Oh, sorry for being late!
We've been waiting for you, Yamamoto!
This is Inspector Lunge. I told you
about him over the phone.
Oh, hello!
I'm Yamamoto, from the Munich branch of Kadofuku.
Hello.
How were negotiations with Mr.
Kohout in the Czech Republic?
Oh, he's a tough one.
Oh, by the way, I found it!
Found what?
The thing that Schuwald's right-hand man,
that blond-haired boy, was asking about...
You found it?!
Yeah, because getting on Schuwald's
secretary's good side...
is the best way of getting a good
contract from Schuwald himself!
I had to go through lots of used bookstores in Prague...
but I finally found a copy!
Oh, so this is that picture book?
The cover has fallen off, and it's
in pretty bad shape, but...
it'll look fine once we wrap it up nicely.
Excuse me!
Could I have a beer?
May I?
Oh, go ahead.
It's in Czech...
Oh, next is my song!
Nice! Nice!
We've been waiting for you!
Let's hear it!
Let's go!
Inspector, what are you looking
up in that dictionary?
Czech words.
Czech?
Does it have something to
do with your investigation?
No, absolutely nothing.
I can't believe you're looking, up things that have
nothing to do with your investigation...
It's a passage from a picture book,
and liked the picture.
And I wanted to know what the passage said.
The inspector reading a picture book?
This is rare...
"Look, at me! Look at me!"
"The monster inside me..."
"has grown this big!"
I see...
So Johan has finally gotten around to
manipulating that large financial group!
I've been hearing stories of Johan from
you for a while now, Dr. Gillen, but...
that Johan guy is a monster...
A monster?
Yeah.
I've killed many people myself, but...
he's become something I've always
wanted to be, but couldn't.
Man, Johan is my hero.
I see.
So there's something else I want to talk about...
What is it?
If you were Johan, what would you do next?
Next?
That's obvious!
I'd kill his current parents, the Lieberts.
Mr. Liebert?
Mr. Liebert!
Why would you do such a thing?
Why?
Because I'd have gotten bored with them.
Mr. Liebert!  Mr. Liebert?!
Mr. Liebert!
Yes, who is it?
A psychoanalyst?
What do you want from us, Dr. Reichwein?
I have no intention of wasting your
time with the whole back-story.
I want to ask you something about
your adopted son, Johan.
Johan?  Adopted?
What are you talking about?
He's our real son, and...
It's no use trying to play dumb!
The grave of your real son is in Bruntal!
You took advantage of the
town hall's files burning...
and turned in another birth certificate
as if your child were still alive.
Who are you...?
1 didn't come here to threaten you or anything.
I came here for your sake.
I want you to read this.
It's a collected report on Johan.
On Johan?
Yes.
A certain person has collected all of this.
This man...
came here once trying to sell us insurance.
He's a former detective, Richard Braun.
A former detective...?
He...
passed away.
Now, please read.
The story begins in 1986...
when a high official of the East was exiled to the West.
Is he after money?
Money?
He doesn't care about money.
Then why did he attach himself to this wealthy man?
You also did it when you were little, didn't you?
Did what?
You find a line of ants...
And you take that line of ants...
and you mess it up.
It can't be true...
I can't believe such a frightening story...
How can this be...?
I understand that you don't want to believe it.
You lost your son at an early age.
Afterwards, even though you weren't
blessed with another child...
a child who was about the same
age as your son appeared.
And he even had money.
He gave you a wonderful house.
He gave you a beautiful garden.
And...
he gave you love.
I understand very well that
you want to believe in him!
However!
What's written here is the truth!
Who is Johan?
Just who is he?!
Johan... is a good boy.
Johan is a kind boy.
He's smart...
and very skillful.
He's...
our reason for living!
Is that all?
You lived with him for nearly five years...
and that's all you can say?!
You don't know anything about him.
Please help me!
Because of him, my friend Richard is dead!
And right now, a man named Dr. Tenma...
is trying to do something that can't be undone.
Please, help me!
No, more importantly...
You will be...
like the middle-aged couples written about in here.
Like those who raised Johan as an adopted son...
you will be killed!
Leave here!  Leave with me!
Small apples are ripening on our apple tree.
Yeah...
Next year, we'll get bigger ones.
I look forward to it.
Yeah, I can't wait...
He's going to be killed by a Japanese man soon?
Johan said that to the children?
Yeah.
What do you think he meant by that?
Just for the record, he doesn't have a death wish.
Then what did he mean?
Who knows?
Heroes are always thinking of complicated things.
But...
But I can tell you this much.
Even if the world was burnt to
the ground in a nuclear war...
he'd still survive.
So he's saying that we can't do anything?
It's true that everything we've done
has been a fruitless effort.
I couldn't even help Richard...
Dr. Reichwein...
Nor have we found Dr. Tenma!
We can't even stop him from killing Johan!
Everything has been a futile effort!
Dr. Reichwein, let's calm down and think it out.
I'm sorry...
Mess up the line of ants, huh?
Even ants have souls.
Where are you going, Doctor?
My only option now is to risk my
life by fighting in close combat!
I'm going to tell him everything to his face.
To that great mogul, Schuwald!
Add another fifty chairs?
Man, they keep coming in!
You mean Mr. Schuwald's
donation ceremony tomorrow?
Yeah.
The higher-ups all want to attend.
Every time Mr. Schuwald makes
a move, it becomes a big deal!
The library will be closing shortly.
Excuse me...
I'm sorry.
Could you get that for me?
That Czech dictionary.
I can't reach it.
S-Sure.  This one?
Ah, I'm sorry.
Thank you.
It s nothing.
I borrowed a Czech picture bookr but
I don't understand anything it says...
1 see...
My friend suddenly fainted
after reading this picture book.
Is that so?
So I thought that maybe it had something
to do with what's written in the book...
Is your friend better now?
Yeah, all better.
Thank you very much.
It's nothing.
Let's see...
"Once upon a time, in a far away land..."
"there was a monster without a name."
"The monster wanted a name so
badly that he couldn't stand it."
"So the monster decided to go on a journey."
Strange book...
We re closing!
Okay.
We're closed tomorrow because of the ceremony.
Yes
Cherish what you know is true in this world.
Ima kono sekai de wakaru koto mitsumete
Yes
Please believe in the kindness of your eyes.
Anata no hitomi no yasashisa wo shinjite
Make it home to your land of harmony
Make it home to your land of purity
Make it home