Did you get the reception attendee list?
Yes, I got it.
We've got a handle on who was in attendance
and where they were at that point in time.
So he was after the governor?
The attendees were all important people.
I'd bet most of them have enemies.
Anyway, let's keep trying to find any connections
the governor had to the gunman.
Looks like Frankfurt Station is buzzing
with that convention center shooting.
Yes.
Even though we've identified the deceased attacker...
we don't know who he was after.
You've identified him?
Yes.
They said he was a dentist from the redevelopment area.
A dentist, huh?
Well, that's just great.
Something wrong?
Well, I was thinking of going to
a dentist right after I retire.
I haven't been to see one because
I've been so busy every day.
I don't want a dangerous lunatic as my dentist.
Inspector, this way.
I'm Inspector Weissbach from the
Nordrhein-Westfalen Police.
Reinhard Dinger, age forty two.
Taxi driver by profession.
Suspected of killing a passenger in
Gunther Forest Park, as well as...
the 1997 murder of a Bilker
Investment Bank employee...
the 1996 Hofgarten murder...
and the 1995 Rhine riverside murder.
Wanted as a suspect for all these murders that
occurred around the Düsseldorf area.
I now request that the suspect be transferred...
to the state of Nordrhein-Westfalen.
Hey, are you guys ready?
Yes, sir.
Step out.
Okay, let's go.
An Unrelated Murder
Want anything to drink?
No.
No smoking here.
The sign said this is a nonsmoking car.
If only you lived with that kind of morality.
How many people have you killed with those hands?
The notion that you can count their
precious lives on your fingers...
would make the people you killed turn in their graves.
This is my last case.
I'm retiring tomorrow.
Even though I led a simple life
as a detective, it wasn't bad.
Now I'll probably tend the garden
with my wife and take it easy.
That's what life is like.
I want you to realize the kind of lives you destroyed...
and I want you to regret it.
Even people who would spit on me?
The man I picked up on Adler Street
spit on me when he got off.
Don't tell me that's why you...
Isn't spitting on someone the
lowest thing a person can do?
The two people I picked up at Gerresheim
Station were even worse.
They started having sex in the back of my car.
In the back of my car!
So I killed them both.
A drunken punk kid with a foul mouth.
A prostitute who tried to pay her fare with her body.
A hag smeared with cosmetics who
insulted everyone she saw.
Many people have ridden in my taxi.
They were all trash.
That's why I killed them.
Then let me ask you something.
What about the employee from the Bilker
Investment Bank that you killed?
How was he scum?
He worked diligently.
He had a good personal life.
He was a banker who loved his family.
Because you killed him...
a certain corporate finance scandal
that he was going to reveal...
now remains shrouded in complete mystery.
That one...
left a bad aftertaste.
See?
You talk as if you're on the moral high ground,
but, you're just trying to justify yourself.
I didn't have a choice there.
Did someone ask you to do it?
I can't tell you that.
I said no smoking in here.
Don't ever put a cigarette in your
mouth in front of me again.
I'll kill you.
I wonder why you turned out this way...
I've always been correct in my thinking.
I just needed a little push, that's all.
On that day...
a man was walking his dog in the park.
Just because the dog took a crap, he kicked it.
The dog was scared while he was being kicked.
All he did was take a crap.
I stopped the man.
The next thing I knew, the police were holding me down.
Just then...
a little boy appeared.
He told the police...
that it wasn't my fault.
That the man walking the dog attacked me first.
Thanks to that, the police didn't take me away.
I thanked the boy and offered to
drive him back to his house.
But he said he had no home to go back to.
On top of that, he brought his sister
from the corner of the park.
His twin sister.
Well since I didn't have much choice...
I took them both back to my apartment.
The strange thing was, when they started undressing...
they were both wearing pajamas underneath.
It was as if they had just escaped
from a hospital or something.
Now that I think about it, the boy had
a bandage wrapped around his head.
After we ate dinner that night, we watched the news.
I started to mutter to myself like I usually do.
What a stupid world...
What stupid people...
Trash should just die.
Do you know what the boy said to me?
He said that I was right.
And then he said...
We don t need those people.
I was liberated.
That's enough!
You mean to say that that's when you started killing?
Thanks for your effort, Inspector.
Sure thing.
Your last case is closed, nice and tight.
Yeah. All that's left is to clean out my desk.
Thank you so much for all these years.
I feel a little depressed.
Well, there were a few unsolved cases...
What is it, Inspector?
he brought his sister...
His twin sister.
they were both wearing pajamas...
as if they had just escaped from a hospital or something.
Don't you remember anything about that night?
Anything is fine.
Anything you remember.
Your name is Anna.
Anna Liebert...
right?
Now that i think about it, the boy had
a bandage wrapped around his head.
The twin brother and sister!
They're gone!
Inspector?!
When did I meet them?
Let's see...
About eleven years ago.
W-What did those children look like?!
They were blond twins with very pretty faces.
My God...
The twins who disappeared that day...
The twins who hold a vital key to Dr. Tenma's case.
Oh, man.
I only have thirty hours until I retire.
A vampire, huh?
Isenburg Prison
(Frankfurt)
I see.
That's why you sucked the blood of those thirteen people.
You would have died unless you fed on their blood?
And they had to be virgins.
I see.
Then let me ask you a question.
The case from three months ago.
The girl from a general store in Frankfurt.
Frieder Schelling.
Did you suck her blood as well?
Well, as you said...
all the people you attacked so far were virgins.
And you even went to the trouble of researching
their behavior before attacking.
I can understand why you needed virgin blood.
However, this Frieder Schelling person...
She was twenty-one years old.
Even though she looked like she was still in her teens.
But that's not where the problem lies.
She had worked at a café on Seiler Street
in Frankfurt since she was sixteen.
It was very close to a famous school.
She was like a Madonna amongst the boys of that school.
However...
she had a child at the age of seventeen.
According to the rumors, it was with
someone from that school.
After she gave birth, her parents opened a general store.
The stories say that the boy's family was rich...
so they received a large sum of money
and were able to open the store.
You knew, didn't you?
You conducted extensive research on those other girls.
You'd even suck the blood of non-virgins?
That...
left a bad aftertaste...
Why did you go after her?
I met the real thing.
The real thing?
I finally realized it after meeting him.
I was only a bat flying around the vampire, nothing more.
He was the real thing.
That man asked you to do it?
Who was he?
Where did you meet him?
Outside of Frankfurt.
Griesheim.
There is a park, much like any other park.
In the sandbox at that park...
he wrote a woman's name in
the sand with a tree branch.
So I carried it out.
Who was he?
Like I said...
a real vampire.
Pinneber Prison
(Hamburg)
Isn't it strange, no matter how you think about it?
Your murder of Erich Klemperer four months ago.
All your other missions were in Niedersachsen.
So why was this the only one all the way out in Frankfurt?
Was this another signal from the aliens?
Did the aliens suddenly change their minds
and tell you to kill someone in Frankfurt?
Or was there another reason?
Klemperer certainly did have a sordid history.
He escaped from East Berlin during the Cold War.
It seems he was doing well in the trade
of food and such for several years.
However, there were rumors that he
smuggled children over the border.
Long story short, he was selling eastern children
to the rich, childless westerners.
It wasn't a signal.
I met one in person.
I was inspired.
A real alien was standing in front of me.
Where did the UFO land?
A park in Griesheim.
He spoke in a space language.
That's why he wrote in the sand...
so I could understand it.
I would like you to feel the same excitement I did.
Düsseldorf State Police Station
All done here, Inspector Weissbach?
Yeah.
You're now only seconds away from retiring.
You just want me out of here, don't you?
That's right!
That's why we're going drinking...
to celebrate getting rid of you!
Sounds like the beer won't taste too good!
Who is that man?
Dr. Gillen.
I hear he's a criminal psychologist.
He's here to interview that serial
murderer taxi driver, Dinger.
At someone's request?
No, he said if was for his paper or something.
He's got a lot of influence in that domain...
so he can convince the higher-ups
to give him permission.
And so, when the man got out
of your taxi and spit on you...
you ran him over.
Yeah.
I said the same thing many times during the
questionings, but all the people I killed...
were unnecessary.
It's just that you guys can't comprehend my righteousness.
Righteousness, huh?
Then let me ask you something.
You've always been very talkative
during the questionings, but...
you seem to have a hard time discussing your
murder of Mr. Overt, the Bilker Bank employee.
It's recorded that you claimed your own
righteousness in all your other murders.
However, you've never given an
acceptable reason as to why...
you murdered Mr. Overt.
I don't want to talk to you anymore.
How did it go, Dr. Gillen?
I'm Inspector Weissbach.
Did Dinger confess anything of academic interest to you?
No.
Nothing aside from what he's already said.
Excuse me.
Actually, there's something I really want to ask him about.
I'm retiring today, but...
I won't feel right unless I hear this.
What do you think about this from
an academic point of view?
If there were a child like a monster...
If he grew up and came to visit the man
who fed him in the past, and...
A child like a monster?
Well, I know it's a silly story, but...
Please, let me hear more about it.
Both of you this time?
I already said I'm not talking to that egghead anymore!
I'm still a detective until the end of the day.
This is an interrogation.
I asked you the same thing yesterday,
but about those twins...
You said the boy liberated you, right?
If that boy grew up and came back to you...
and asked you to do him a favor...
would you do it?
Well, I don't know...
Did you murder Fritz Overt who worked
at the Bilker Investment Bank...
at someone's request?
A hard-working guy.
A man with a good personal life.
That's the kind of man Mr. Overt was.
Quite different from the trash you so often speak of.
He was about to reveal a corporate finance scandal.
If you call him trash...
then the moralization of your crimes will shatter.
I wasn't asked to.
He and I didn't need to speak to each other.
"He"?
I'm sure that bank employee was trash to him.
That's what I believe.
Why?
Because he's right.
And who was he?
One of those twins?
When and where did you meet him?
Griesheim.
A park in that town.
Outside of Frankfurt.
Griesheim.
A park in Griesheim.
He wrote a name in the sand.
He didn't say anything.
But I knew.
I was to kill the man with that name.
We didn't need words.
We knew...
that we didn't need a man like that.
What do you mean?
All three men you interviewed killed someone
at the request of the same man?!
By having three completely unrelated
serial killers perform the acts...
he made it so that the three murders had no meaning.
The meaning of the three murders?
What does that mean?
Please, be more specific.
Both Tenma and Nina headed for Frankfurt.
Johan.
What is he...
trying to do in Frankfurt?
Yes
Cherish what you know is true in this world.
Ima kono sekai de wakaru koto mitsumete
Yes
Please believe in the kindness of your eyes
Anata no hitomi no yasashisa wo shinjite
Make it home to your land of harmony
Make it home to your land of purity
Make it home