Here you go. One Manhattan.
Hey, where is my red cherry?
What?
It is not a Manhattan without a cherry!
I-I'm sorry.
Man, you should pay more attention.
Business is better when I have this in my mouth.
Otherwise, I'll be jinxed!
Verden (Germany)
Springer Mansion
A Past Erased
Please let there be some valuables left.
Okay!  Okay!
It's just as I imagined!
Everything was left intact.
Man, they must have been loaded!
Now then, let's see if there is anything
worthy of the great Heckel.
Life sure is transient.
Even if you are a candidate for state governor...
...it is totally meaningless if you get shot dead.
Ah, back to business.
Their safe should be somewhere around here.
W-What is with this cold feeling?!
I've never had this bad a feeling in my life...
Is someone in this room...?
Y-Yeah, right!
What am I getting all scared for?  That's not like me.
Don't move!
Put your hands on your head!
Damn it, he was behind me?
This is the worst case scenario...
All because that bartender forgot my red cherry.
Hurry and put your hands up!
Okay, okay.
Hey officer, can't you cut me some slack?
I have not taken anything yet.
I'm not with the police.
What?  You are in the same business?
Then why don't you put that dangerous looking
thing down and talk this over peacefully...
Put your hands on your head!
What is with this guy?
He seems to be worse than the cops.
I-It's the police!
You must have screwed up!
I'm running away!
Stop following me!
Screw ups like you...
...only pull the rest of us down!
Screw this!
I told you to stop following me!
Man, today sure is an unlucky day!
I see...
No wonder you looked familiar.
Aren't you that doctor from the newspaper who is an
important witness to assemblyman Springer's murder?
You are a burglar?
That's right.
Unlike you, I don't do unnecessary
things like killing people.
Do you know anything about the incident
that took place in that house?
Who knows?
Hurry up and get lost.
Later.
Hey, Doctor!
I remember you were some super
first class surgeon, right?
I just had an idea with my brilliant brain!
Do you think people meet by chance, Doctor?
It is not like that.
Some people are predestined to meet.
You and I were destined to become partners.
There are tons of people who need someone
like you in the underworld.
Dying people who want to call for a doctor,
but can't, because it is too dangerous.
Leave all the management to the great Heckel!
I'll turn you into the world's finest underworld doctor.
You can earn much more in the underworld!
You will be a millionaire in no time...
Hey, where are you going, Doctor?!
There is something I have to take care of.
Hey, wait a minute.
You wanna know about the murder in that mansion, right?
Well, I did see the killer with my own eyes.
What?!
What do you mean?
You want to know?
Was the killer a blond male of about twenty?!
What are you talking about?
Just tell me about the killer!
I'll only tell you if you team up with me.
He's on the third floor of this tenement.
How do you know that?
I researched that assemblyman's mansion
for a month after I laid eyes on it.
Just when I decided to make my move, he showed up.
When I looked through a window, I saw their dead bodies.
I thought I could make some money if I shook
him up a bit, so I followed the killer here.
So, your innocence in this case has now been proven.
Go explain it all to the police or do whatever you want.
Then let's talk about our wonderful future
somewhere else over a drink...
H-Hey!
What good would it do to see him?!
He's a killer!
You will be killed!
Man, what the hell is he thinking?!
I can't keep up with him!
But someone like him, who I can make
money off of, is hard to come by...
Not crossing dangerous bridges
is one of my principles, but...
Hi.
It's hot today, isn't it?
I'm looking for someone.
Hey, Doctor!  Are you still alive?!
Doctor...?
Y-You idiot!  He's holding a gun!
I.. used to take walks with my mother...
...down the road by a sunflower field...
...on summer days like today...
But she died a long time ago.
You used that gun because someone asked you to, right?
A certain man...
A man...?
Oh, yeah...
He spoke to me one day at a bar.
A blond youth, about twenty...?
Yes...
Yes, Erich had a beautiful smile...
He called himself Erich this time...
We became friends after meeting several times...
Then he invited me to his house.
To assemblyman Springer's house...
He was living in that house until recently...?!
Yes, he said they loved him like a son for about a year...
Hey, I watched that house for about a month,
but I didn't see anybody like that.
They were a wonderful family.
This is a photo of me and the assemblyman's family.
But...
I just could not forgive them for that.
There was a sunflower garden on their property...
...but they tore it down to make room for parking.
When I said that was too cruel...
...Erich agreed with me.
D-Don't tell me you killed them just because of that?!
Also, Erich told me...
...that the assemblyman had a lover.
He also said that...
...he had stopped being the son of the assemblyman Springer.
That he wasn't a member of the family.
He asked me to do him a favor.
He asked me to eliminate that family.
Having an affair is such a horrible thing...
My mother... was also another man's lover...
H-Hey...
Leaving that aside, you wouldn't happen
to know where their safe is, would you?
I think it was in the study on the second floor.
O-Okay!
You should hurry and get out of here too, Doctor!
Did you know?
You can erase the past.
If you don't like it...
...you can erase everything.
You can reset your life.
I don't agree.
Even if you can forget, you can't erase the past.
You are right...
I wonder why I thought of it that way.
Why did I think I could erase my
past if I pulled the trigger?
Why... did I agree to his request?
That is all I have to say.
Please leave.
Oh, that is right.
You are Dr. Tenma, right?
Please take a look at his message.
He left you a message.
It is in the study of that mansion.
He knew you would come here.
Erich said it himself.
That your fate has already been decided.
Goodbye...
Doctor!
That is why I told you to...!
D-Don't you tell me you...
Oh, this is a suicide.
Oh, man...
What good is dying?
Everything is over if you die.
You have to stay alive, right, Doctor?
Yeah.
You say something good every so often.
What do you mean by that?!
So you are tracking down this dangerous
serial killer named Johan?
Why don't you forget about something
that absurd and partner up with me?
Speaking of which, when I tried to get into
this room earlier, I felt a sudden chill...
What is this?
Why are you shaking, Doctor?
"Look at me!"
"The monster inside me..."
"...has grown this big, Dr. Tenma!"
Johan is...
He's... enjoying this!
Hey, Doctor!
Hey, wait!
Listen to what I have to say!
Hey, Doctor!
I've arranged something good for you.
You should be thanking me.
You promised you would team up with me, right?
Who said I was going to team up with you?
H-Hey!
Even you need money to run away from the police, right?
Get in the car.
This is your customer.
He is gonna take you to the patient.
I'll be keeping your stuff.
If you want it back, do some work, get the money...
...then come to Frank's on Graschten Street.
See you later!
Go and make some big bucks!
This sure is a profitable business.
Now then, since they paid me in advance...
...guess I'll go have myself a drink!
"Lawyer," I brought you a doctor!
Thanks, Doctor...
Hurry... and stop the bleeding...
An artery in your armpit has been damaged...
Was this done with a shotgun?
Yeah...
Hey, the doctor is empty handed.
Did you get the surgical equipment?
N-No...
The city is dangerous, so I didn't go that far...
Even if I did have the equipment, I can't operate here.
You should have a real doctor take a look at him.
We would have done that already if we could!
Hurry up and treat him!
How long ago was he shot?
Don't ask stupid questions!
Four hours ago, huh?
You guys are the terrorists from this morning!
So what if we are?
I refuse.
What did you say?!
I have no intention of treating someone
who commits mindless terrorism!
Shut up!
Do you understand the position you are in right now?
Hey, hold it...
Hey, Doctor...
The other group members will be coming to help us soon.
Until then, please stop the bleeding at least.
What is with that attitude?
Do you want to die or something?
I told you to wait...
B-But... Lawyer...
In any case, my life is in this doctor's hands right now...
If I die, you can shoot him.
We're not running a charity here, you know?
Won't you return the 25,000 Marks you owe us, Heckel?
I... I do want to return the money I owe you, Mr. Gross...
I'm happy to hear that.
Just that feeling alone makes me happy.
For starters, break both of his arms.
O-Okay!
I'll pay!  I'll pay you back!
Good boy.
So please wait another month.
Regarding the terrorists who used small, automatic
weapons this morning at Erfurt Station...
Break both of his legs too.
...based on the testimony of a witness,
the suspects have been identified as...
...Max Steindorf and Karl Brandt.
Hold on a second!
The GWE...
...has announced that they will pay anyone
who provides crucial information...
...300,000 Marks as a reward.
It was them?!
I... I can pay back the money!
I... I know where they are!
You can forget about the debt!
I hope you are not lying.
I'll snap your neck if you are.
It's true!  It's true!
It's absolutely true!
Ah, but Tenma is there right now...
Oh, well...
You said that what I did...
...was mindless terrorism, right?
You have got to be kidding!
What I did definitely has meaning...
I...
...feel so good that I killed that bastard
president of the GWE...
...t-that I don't care if die...
Lawyer...
I was a lawyer in East Germany.
This guy was the secretary of a politician.
Nobody had a job once the wall came down.
Doctor, do you know how we feel?
That GWE company...
...right after the wall came down...
...invaded the east by letting their money do the talking.
They forcefully built factories... on our land...
Countless number of them...
That was our country...
I shot that bastard with pride.
I shot him... with pride...
L-Lawyer!
I'm cold...
H-Hang on!
The others should be here soon!
No one is coming...
No one is coming.
I have a feeling...
Stop the bleeding!
Stop it now!
Or I'll shoot you!
I-I'll kill you!
I don't want to die...
Are you scared?
Are you scared of dying?!
Everyone died like that!
All twelve of the people you killed died just like that!
That is what it means to kill someone!
Get me disinfectant and scissors.
You at least have that, don't you?
An arterial hemorrhage.
He is going into shock caused by low blood pressure.
I'm stopping the bleeding by applying pressure
to the severed arteries with my fingers.
I'm going to suture the wound!
Bring me a needle and some string!
W-We don't you have that.
Then a stapler will do!
S-Stapler?
Hurry up and get it!
O-Okay!
Okay.
W-What are you going to do?
I've given him first aid.
I'm carrying him to a hospital.
A... a hospital?
W-What the hell are you thinking?!
If you don't put him down, I'll shoot you!
Shoot me if you want!
If you are going to shoot me...
...then you will have to carry this man to a hospital.
Put me down... here...
You have to run away.
I just remembered...
I knew I saw your face somewhere...
You are that doctor who is suspected
of serial murders, aren't you?
Hurry up and put me down.
What I did...
...was not mindless terrorism.
I killed...
...the president of the GWE...
...his lackeys, and their bodyguards.
You are saying that nobody got caught in the middle?
You mean... that child in the store.
So you knew that you shot him.
Why did you save a guy like me?
It is not because you were afraid you would be shot, right?
Your eyes are not those of someone
who is afraid of being shot...
Why... did you save a killer like myself
who commits random terrorism...?
Because I believe that you are human...
Hurry up and go!
The police are coming!
You have to live.
You...
You are an excellent doctor...
So what happened to the money?!
Hey, Doctor!
Don't tell me you just treated him and came back!
The terrorists responsible for the attack
on Erfurt Station have been arrested.
Why don't you say something ?!
The police had the hideout surrounded...
...but unexpectedly, the terrorists showed no signs of resistance...
...and quietly turned themselves in.
We are not running a charity here, you know?!
Hey!