I don't like doing this to the elderly...
but you're important witnesses.
I can't have you dying or running away.
I've barricaded the back door and most
of the windows with furniture.
Though it wouldn't be hard to
break in if they were serious.
It's better than nothing.
Now then, let's go down to the first floor.
You know how to use a gun, don't you?
Y-Yeah, probably...
I'll go as well.
I have to go as well.
I can't let anything happen to you.
You have to live through this and tell the world the truth.
Stay in the room, Wim.
If something happens to you, Mr. Grimmer...
It's okay.
I've got a strong ally coming!
Really?
Yes, really.
He comes to help me whenever
and wherever I'm in trouble.
He doesn't forgive evil deeds.
He's the Magnificent Steiner.
The Magnificent Steiner's Rage
Now!
Run!
Head north through the woods!
I think most of the children have escaped now.
You should hurry and get out of here, too!
We haven't checked the town center yet.
Leave the rest to me!
Please look after the others!
O-Okay!
Oh, there's one thing I have to ask you.
Bonaparta...
No, do you know a person named Klaus Poppe?
Poppe?
He's the owner of Hotel Versteck.
What are you doing there?
It's okay.
I'm on your side.
I... I ran as fast as I could...
but the town is full of dead bodies...
I don't know where to run to...
Where did you come from?
H-He's giving orders from his room...
I overheard him...
"Him"?
Roberto!
I thought it was strange how he kept
coming and going from the room!
And he changed his clothes every time...
and took a shower...
Where is this Roberto?
He's in a room on the fourth floor of Hotel Bergbach!
I...
I didn't know he was like that...
So I...
Listen.
Everyone is hiding in the other hotel, Versteck.
Can you make it there by yourself?
B-By myself?
I'm scared!
Now, stand up.
Dr. Tenma.
Inspector Lunge.
My journey of the imagination...
has finally become reality.
With you here, reality finally makes an appearance...
and my vacation of following imaginary
threads comes to an end.
From now on, I have a duty as a police officer.
It's time to get back to work.
Take this girl with you.
Hotel Versteck.
The person you're after is there.
Franz Bonaparta...
Inspector Lunge, where are you going?
I told you.
I'm going to work.
We'll talk after I get back.
I have a lot of things I want to ask you.
Dr. Tenma.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay, Nina?
A memory...
is unfolding in my head...
In the deepest part of my subconscious...
In the deepest part of your subconscious?
I don't want to remember it, no matter what...
If Johan recalled this memory...
If Johan already remembered it, then...
Come out!
D-Don't shoot me!
I-I'm from this town!
Please don't shoot me.
Where is the man giving orders?
I'm asking you where Roberto is.
Please stand up!
We have to walk!
No!
There are dead bodies everywhere!
I'll go crazy if I stay in a place like this!
That's why we have to get to Hotel
Versteck as quickly as possible.
No!
Please open your eyes, Erika
Please, Erika!
She's your wife, isn't she?
Unfortunately, your wife is already...
I'm on your side.
It's dangerous here.
You should hurry and get to a safe place.
Let me borrow your gun!
I'm gonna shoot the guy who killed Erika!
Hurry! Give me the gun!
I'm gonna kill the bastard who ruined our happy life!
Your wife doesn't want that.
Your wife wishes for the safety of that child.
Isn't that right?
I'll lead the way.
There's an escape route to the north through the forest.
Let's forget about going to the hotel.
You should go to the forest, too.
No!
I don't want to go anywhere anymore!
Okay.
I'll be right back.
Don't go anywhere.
Okay?
It sure is quiet.
Hey, about their target...
You sure they're not after the
money we won in the lottery?
Yes.
I really didn't even feel alive these past few days.
To tell you the truth, there was something wrong with me.
Thanks to all that money, I even bought several guns.
Normal life really is the best.
Normal life, huh?
I have to tell my wife that it wasn't our fault.
Hey, can you hear me?
Hey!
Mr. Hennich!
M-My wife...
Ma'am!
I-It hurts...!
This way! Quickly!
They're shooting from the building across the street.
Does this hotel have a basement?
There's a storage room under the kitchen.
Are you okay?
What about you, honey?
My dad is doing this...
He's gone crazy because he ran out
of alcohol, so he's doing this...
That's not true, Wim.
My dad is...
Like how he hits me every day...
Do you really think your dad is someone
who would do such a thing?
I...
Everything will be over if I go outside.
Don't make me repeat myself.
I won't let you die, no matter what.
If you say something like that again...
I'll tie you up down here.
You guys stay here.
I'll take care of this.
Mr. Grimmer...
I told you before, didn't I?
When I'm in trouble, the Magnificent Steiner shows up.
I saw a case like that during an experiment.
By applying excessive amounts of anger or sadness...
or a great deal of stress...
another personality would arise within the subject.
Those children had a bizarre violent nature.
But most of them committed suicide.
I'm surprised you lived to this age.
Look!
I'm unarmed!
Let me talk to you, just for a bit!
Why are you doing this?
Who ordered you guys?
I don't care if you're from old East Germany...
or the former secret police!
I don't care who you are!
I'm a nobody, myself.
Can you hear me?
Please listen to me!
Not under orders, but with your hearts!
Ask your hearts what it is you're doing!
You can, can't you?
You can!
What are you doing?
I was so scared!
I came all the way here by myself.
I'm so glad that you're here!
The Magnificent Steiner!
Hey, kids!
Are you sitting in front of the TV?
Even though I was glued to the television
for that show every day...
I wonder what adventure awaits us today?
Even though I was glued to the television
for that show every day...
When you're in trouble, just call my name!
I don't recall ever watching the last episode.
No matter when...
Now, let's go.
N-No!
No!
I wonder if that weak young main character...
knew that he turned into the Magnificent
Steiner when he became filled with rage...
I wonder if that young man became happy...
I wonder if...
I wonder if that young man...
became happy...
We're almost there!
Just a little further and we'll be out of the forest!
You're residents of Ruhenheim, aren't you?
Who are you people?
Something is happening to the town, isn't it?
Some people armed with weapons appeared...
and the town became a slaughterhouse.
D-Don't tell me you're with them!
Calm down.
We're on your side.
Have you seen an Asian man?
A Japanese man with black hair?
Are you friends of his?
You know him, don't you?
Yeah.
He tried his best to help these children escape.
He stayed behind to continue helping the people in town.
When we left, he said he was going to the Hotel Versteck.
Nina!
I've parked my car right outside the forest!
Drive the injured and the sick away from here!
Hurry and call the police at once!
A-Are you planning on going into town?
You shouldn't go!
You'll be killed!
Tenma is...!
That Asian man is my friend!
I have to help him!
Hurry and call the police!
Hotel Versteck...
Mr. Grimmer...
I knew you'd come, Dr. Tenma.
Two people in the next building...
one on the floor below...
and another here.
I took out a total of four people.
The Magnificent Steiner appeared, didn't he?
No, he didn't come out.
I did it all on my own.
I did everything because I was engulfed in rage.
Anyway, we should treat that wound.
Oh, yes.
Before I forget.
Here, a letter.
I got it from inspector Lunge.
I heard he found it in the Red Rose Mansion.
Please help him.
He went to Hotel Bergbach by himself.
We have to treat you first!
I'm okay.
Let me rest for a while.
Let me introduce you.
This is Franz Bonaparta.
Mr. Grimmer...
I'm okay, Wim.
It sure has been raining a while.
This place is nice when it's sunny.
Right, Dr. Tenma?
Yes.
When it's sunny again...
let's take Wim here along with us...
and go on a picnic.
Sure.
With delicious wine...
I'm not sad because I'm going to die.
I'm sad because my child is dead.
It's impossible for humans to forget their emotions.
My emotions...
They were just lost somewhere.
It's as if...
a letter that was sent to me...
has finally reached me, decades later.
So this is true sadness...
So...
this is happiness.
The last episode of the Magnificent Steiner.
I'm sure...
he returned to being human.
Mr. Grimmer?
Mr. Grimmer!
I...
What have I...
Yes
Cherish what you know is true in this world.
Ima kono sekai de wakaru koto mitsumete
Yes
Please believe in the kindness of your eyes
Anata no hitomi no yasashisa wo shinjite
Make it home to your land of harmony
Make it home to your land of purity
Make it home