Before they came here, they were really alone.
Even when they were found near
the border of Czechoslovakia...
...I heard they were walking together, hand in hand.
Both shivering from the cold...
I heard the orphanage in East Germany
were horrible at the time...
Don't compare us to Kinderheim 511
Inge, that is not the way to the bathroom.
Okay?
Mama!
It's okay.  It's okay.
There is nothing to be scared of.
Now then, you can go to the bathroom by yourself, right?
These children don't know the love of their true parents.
You need love in order to mature as a human.
As you said, the orphanages in East Germany at the time were terrible.
This place used to be called Orphanage No. 47, as well...
But even so, we still tried our best
to make something happen.
Tried to go against the government, even slightly.
So we wouldn't turn out to be like Kinderheim 511.
That place was a special orphanage
under the cooperative jurisdiction...
...of the Ministry of Health and Welfare
and the Ministry of Domestic Affairs...
Do you know what that means?
No.
All the internal conditions were monitored by the Ministry of Domestic Affairs.
Because that place was old East Germany's...
...testing facility.
A Little Experiment
A testing facility?
It was a project to turn children into perfect soldiers.
Psychological conditioning...
Research into brainwashing.
They formed conspiracies among the orphans...
...and monitored how they hated and fought
each other under those circumstances.
An experiment for creating a cold-hearted
person, one without sympathy.
Can you imagine what kind of people those children
would turn out to be when they grew up?
But now we don't have any proof
of what went on in there...
...because it appears everything related to that matter was burned right before the wall came down.
The ones in the Ministry of Domestic Affairs who
were involved in the project fled as well...
But...
...I have heard one thing.
There was one person...
...who successfully hid his personal
history and settled in this country.
A supervisor for Kinderheim 511's demonic project.
His true identity...
...was that of a child psychologist who worked for
the ministry of Domestic Affair's police force.
Though on the outside...
...he said he used to work for the Ministry of Health
and Welfare and was in charge of this district.
Worked for the Ministry of Health and Welfare...
...and was in charge of this district...?
Are you done, Inge?
Yeah.
Sleep tight.
Come on.
Good night.
Every thing is in the dark now, thanks to that incident.
That... incident...?
What happened at Kinderheim 511?!
I guess I said too much...
I dredged up something I didn't want to.
Please tell me what happened at that place!
Where is my soccer ball?
What?
My...
Where is my soccer ball?
Oh!
See, it is right here.
But you can't play soccer until you are all better.
That man said he will be coming to pick you up soon...
...so sleep well until then.
Even I don't know what really happened...
Because at the time, the government of East Germany...
...issued a gag order regarding the incident.
At first, it was the unnatural death
of the director of Kinderheim 511.
Soon after that...
...a dispute broke out amongst the instructors
over who would succeed the director.
I heard anarchy ensured inside the orphanage.
It was impossible to control the conspiracies
of the children in that situation, as well.
I'm surprised Johan was able to get out of there alive.
So, what happened to Kinderheim 511?
Everyone died.
What?
Every member of the orphanage,
including the instructors...
...killed each other.
That the world is in an abyss is the biggest lie!
Tomorrow will definitely be a good day.
Dieter.
Someone is here to pick you up.
Hey...
Mr. Hartmann...
I thought we were going home?
No.
Let's stop somewhere first.
I... I don't wanna go there.
No!  I don't wanna!
Dieter...
You are a good boy, right, Dieter?
You what?
I told you not to give Dieter to anyone until I came back!
B-But...
That man was his foster parent.
And besides, he was such a gentleman.
You could take lessons from him!
B-But... that man is...
And that child...
He insisted on going with him.
Dieter!
Dieter?
They didn't come back...
This is Hartmann's study...
The seasons are all different, but...
...these were all taken at the same place.
Where is this place?
Johan!
Who is this guy with him?
Now I see.
All these pictures were taken at Kinderheim 511.
From ten years ago, to now...
Every member of the orphanage,
including the instructors...
...killed each other.
Dieter...
Could it be that he's...!
Dieter!
Hold on, Dieter!
I'm coming!
Looks like this boy can't see it...
Hartmann!
This boy can't see... what Johan saw from here back then.
No good...
Another failure.
This boy is not Johan, either.
Everyone...
Everyone died.
It was ten years ago.
The instructors, and even the orphans...
All fifty took their last breath here.
And Johan...
He just gazed upon it.
He gazed upon the spectacle from right here.
Johan just gazed upon it.
I asked Johan...
What...
I asked him just what he had done.
And he answered me.
He said he just threw an oil-soaked rag into a bonfire.
Well?
Do you understand what he meant?
"Hatred is born when people gather together."
"I merely poured some oil onto this."
That's what he said!
A boy of only ten years old!
And he did it!
He made fifty people kill each other without
lifting one finger of his own!
It is your experiment!
It is your experiment that turned
him into that kind of person!
Our experiment...?
Oh, no...
You have it all wrong.
It is true that Kinderheim 511 was a testing facility.
A project for turning orphans into perfect soldiers.
Looking back now, that was a
meager little experiment, too.
What about Johan?
Him, a soldier?
That is nonsense!
He was born to be a leader!
He was the one who should have stood at the top!
There is no way we could have created
a masterpiece like him!
He was more than human, a monster, from the beginning!
He made a prediction.
In the end humans just hate and kill each other...
What do you think Johan's objective was?
He told me.
To be the last person alive at the end of the world.
Dieter...
Tomorrow is in an abyss.
You have to be more like Johan because
of that, even just a little...
So then...
Why are you a failure?
Why can't you be like Johan?
Stop, Hartmann!
Make another move...
...and I'll shoot!
Get out.
This is our problem.
Get out!
Dieter!
Come down!
Dr. Tenma...
You want to know about Johan, right?
What are you going to do when
you know more about him?
I personally think it is impossible to find and kill him.
Well, it doesn't matter.
I'll give you one piece of information.
However, after you hear it, you have to leave us alone.
Find General Wolf.
He was the first to notice Johan's talent.
I'm sure he's alive somewhere.
That man in the picture in your study?
That man with Johan?
He is the one who brought Johan in.
I'm sure he knows something.
Now, leave!
Dieter!
Decide on your own whether you want
to come down from there or not!
Don't worry.
If Hartmann puts his finger on the trigger...
...I'll shoot him!
Dieter!
Decide on your own!
Decide with your own free will!
You can't leave me, can you, Dieter?
Because you are...
...my child, after all.
So that is how it is, Dr. Tenma.
Now, get lost!
Dieter...
That's it!
It's okay...
Just like that...
Slowly...
Dieter!
Come back, my precious little Dieter!
You think you can live without me?
Dieter!
That is enough, Hartmann!
I'll shoot if you move!
I love you!
Dieter!
The world is in an abyss!
Dr. Tenma told me...
...that tomorrow will be a good day!
Dieter!
Be brave!
There is nothing to be afraid of!
Dieter!
Listen to me.
Take a bus from here...
...and get off at Künen Street.
The orphanage will be right in front of you.
Give this to a woman named Erna Tiesche.
She may look scary on the outside.
...but she is really a nice old lady at heart.
Good luck.
There is a reason I can't go into town.
So this will be goodbye.
The bus will be here in another two or three minutes.
Take care.
Practice your soccer skills.
No, you can't follow me.
Here.
Dieter...
I told you no.
You can't come with me.
You can't come with me...