Dear God in Heaven...
It's okay now...
Never again...
will blood be shed in this forest...
Isn't that right?
Child's Play!
Another child falls to his death...
Is it an accident, or suicide!?
Dangerous children's game?
Yet another victim!!
And now, a fifth victim...
Further restrictions on rooftop access implemented!!
Ralf Ludwig Memorial Hospital
You don't remember anything?
What were you doing on the roof?
Tell me anything you can remember,
no matter how small it seems.
Talk to him, Martin!
If you hadn't hit the first floor awning and
gotten caught on the tree branch...
you could've died
Please, talk to the doctor!
We have to make sure you won't do
anything foolish like that again
Now, now...
But... if he had died, I...
Listen to me, ma'am.
I'm here to provide your son with counseling.
I know.
I know...
But, Doctor...
Let's talk outside, ma'am...
Dieter, just sit right there and wait for me, okay?
Don't go into the room or anything, okay?
Is he... your grandson?
Oh, no. I'm Just taking care of him.
H-Hi...
Hi.
I'm... Dieter.
I'm Martin.
Does it hurt?
Does what hurt?
You know, where you got hurt...
Under your bandages...
It was scary, wasn't it?
When you fell off the roof...
H-Hey, don't.
What are you doing?!
My shoes are in that bag right there.
Get them for me.
What are you talking about?
You have to lie down!
Get my shoes!
Where are you going?
They're gonna get mad at you.
So what if they get mad at me?
It's not like I'm afraid of them getting
mad at me or anything.
It's just like he said!
"Once you come back to life, go outside."
"The world will have changed..."
No...
It's not the world that's changed, it's me.
Because...
I was chosen.
I'm bored...
I didn't know the world was so boring.
Look out!
You should come, too.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
W-What did you do that for?
Hey, look! He's scared
Stop it!
I told you to look.
Help...
"I don't want to die!"
"Help me!"
Right?
Very well.
I'll let you live.
I'll answer your question.
You asked me if I was scared when
I fell off the roof, didn't you
Y-Yeah...
Of course I wasn't scared.
Because it was all a game.
A... a game?
B-But a lot of children died
It's fun.
Because it's a game.
We stand on the edges of abandoned
buildings' roofs, facing each other.
Then we close our eyes and move
towards each other, step by step.
It's a duel.
Whether or not you fail, as long
as you live, you're the winner.
Why would you do that?
To make a bet with fate.
The one who lives is chosen.
Don't you understand what I'm saying?
The one who lives can play the game again.
Game...
The game...?
Because this world is boring.
It's fun.
Only those chosen by fate can keep playing.
You don't get it?
1 thought you were one of us.
Come on, I'll show you.
You're a true idiot if you don't
understand after seeing it.
Hey...
Hey!
Don't tell me you're going up to the roof...
The chosen ones...
Only the superior ones will survive...
He's the one.
Who?
The one who taught us this game.
Who's he?
He's our friend, a friend of the superior children.
Come on, hurry up!
N-No thanks!
Just come on!
Let go of me!
You need to understand. Come on!
Stop it!
Who hurt you?
Your parents?
You're still siding with them even
after they did this to you?
You're still going to be buried
in this stupid world after this?
Come on! Come and see for yourself!
What do you think of the view?
How do you feel?
Stand up.
What are you scared of?
Stand up, close your eyes and try to walk.
Get up!
I understand...
I really understand what you're trying to say...
I thought the world was pitch black...
I thought the future was filled with darkness...
What do you like to eat?
I had a really good sausage the other day!
But if I die, I'll never be able to have it again!
You coward.
I love playing soccer!
But if I die, I'll never be able to kick the ball again
Weakling.
1 like Dr. Reichwein!
His secretary, Ms. Mehres, is nice, too!
But if I die, I won't be able to see them again
Scary things will never go away!
That's why he said we have to become adults!
Tenma said that tomorrow will be a good day!
If I die...
If I die, I won't get to see Tenma anymore.
I'm scared!
Don't panic...
Bend down, slowly...
I can't do it...
I can't be like Johan...
Johan?
Johan's playing a much better game!
Johan said that he'll be killed soon.
He said that he'll be shot and
killed by some Japanese guy!
I really walked on the edge of
the roof with my eyes closed!
It's the truth.
I really did it.
I wasn't scared at all!
And when I opened my eyes...
Joachim, who should have been walking towards
me from the other side, had disappeared!
I saw it!
I saw the moment a person
dies with my very own eyes
People really do die...
I brought some tea.
Oh, thank you.
Oh, that son of mine!
He doesn't seem to understand what he did.
It's good that he's alive but...
when I think about how Joachim's parents
must feel after losing their son...
Please say something to him!
He seems to listen to what you say.
She nags at me like that all the time.
She doesn't understand anything!
She doesn't let me out of the house.
She won't even let me watch TV or read comic books.
You sound bored.
I'll bring you something.
Really?!
Even if you're not allowed to read comic books...
picture books are okay, right?
Oh, picture books?
They're so boring.
Hey!
When is that great game you mentioned
the other day going to happen?
You said you might get shot soon, right?
I'm so excited!
When is it?
When is that Japanese guy going to shoot you?
Hey, Johan
Hermann Hesse...
The first printing of Steppenwolf
And look at this!
Another first printing of Hoffman's Nachtestücke
There's also a complete set of Goethe's poems
Dear God...
Even I, the director of the University of Munich's
Friedrich Emmanuel Library...
am dazzled by your collection of books.
I taught myself everything I know, because
I wasn't able to go to college.
So I thought I'd at least read books, and this is the result.
I can't believe you'd donate such a
collection of books to our library
I can't even find the words to thank you
I'm going blind, and can't read them anymore...
Rather than have them sleep in here...
they would be more useful in the hands of students.
Yes!
Although they're very valuable...
they're also meant to be read by the public.
Oh, yes, yes.
We've also decided on where to store them.
There's also the ceremony to plan...
so please come to the library and we'll discuss it.
How's the security?
What?
Ever since Mr. Schuwald started to appear in public...
we've been concerned about the activities
of certain dangerous people.
Please be thorough when you check the invited guests.
Isn't that right, Johan?
Yes.
Johan and Karl should go to the
library and check things out...
because they're the ones who came up with
the idea of donating this collection of books.
I'm the director, Germann.
Nice to meet you.
University of Münich Library
This will become the room that will house
Mr. Schuwald's collection of books.
An ordinary reader won't have access to this much.
You guys have never been in here, have you?
An optimal preservation temperature
and humidity are used.
It is also protected against theft and fire.
There are a lot of books here!
This is a treasure for humanity, don't you think, Johan?
Humanity's treasure, huh?
And right over here in the central hall...
is where we're planning to hold the
book collection donation ceremony.
Just like his butler said...
we'll put our full effort into the security.
So I want Mr. Schuwald to relax and
attend the ceremony.
Yes.
I'm sure Father will be happy to attend.
Right, Johan?
What's wrong, Johan?
Please excuse me.
Are you looking for something?
Yes...
I was wondering if there are any good
picture books for my friend...
For your friend?
Yes, my friend.
Let's see...
How about this one?
Well? Don't you think the art is wonderful?
Yes.
It's good.
But I think this is more suitable for adults...
Oh, your friend isn't an adult?
In that case, how about this one?
Oh, no!
Oh, thank you.
I-I'm pretty clumsy, so this happens to me a lot.
Oh, that's right. This one.
I recommend this book.
Do you like that one?
Oh, the pictures are nice!
I wonder who wrote it?
Please excuse me...
Emil... Sebe...?
The publisher is Moravian...?
Oh, it s a publisher in Prague, in the Czech Republic.
There are a lot of good picture book
authors in the Czech Republic.
But I've never heard of Sebe...
Maybe he's not that famous?
What's wrong?
S-Somebody!
Somebody help!
Man, the heat this summer...
It's unbearable...
Announcement regarding the donation of
Hans Georg Schuwald's book collection
as well as Mr. Schuwald s speech.
This is the place.
From here...
I'll...
Yes
Cherish what you know is true in this world.
Ima kono sekai de wakaru koto mitsumete
Yes
Please believe in the kindness of your eyes.
Anata no hitomi no yasashisa wo shinjite
Make it home to your land of harmony
Make it home to your land of purity
Make it home