Mom...
Don't let go of my hand.
Welcome Home
Male.
German-Czechoslovakian.
After World War II, as the eldest son in
his family, he remained in Bohemia.
A soldier who graduated from a military academy.
An elite who was the nation's future.
His name was...
names don't really matter.
Female.
The only daughter born to an elementary
school teacher in Moravia.
Blonde hair, blue eyes... a beautiful girl.
She attended Brno University, majoring in genetics.
A talented woman in whom her
professors saw a great future.
Her name was...
names don't really matter.
The two met at a café in Prague.
It didn't take them long to fall in love.
She soon became pregnant...
and he confessed...
that this was all a mission.
Race, brains, bone structure, athletic ability...
In order to create children between
the best and brightest...
experiments were conducted
involving dozens of couples.
They were one of them.
He explained that he carried out his mission
according to the scenario, but...
he no longer intended to see it through, and said...
Let's run away.
The couple ran.
Even though he said that he wasn't
going to stick to the scenario...
that very action was already taken into account.
The woman was placed in an isolated room.
Let me see him.
He's on a new assignment.
The woman said...
"Let me see him."
The woman knew...
that he was probably no longer of this world.
The babies within her were growing steadily.
They were twins.
Face this way.
She had started to realize that...
this man who often came by...
this man who sketched her...
this man was the mastermind behind the experiment.
I won't forgive...
I will never forgive you.
Even if I die, these babies, growing
inside me, will definitely have their revenge.
You say curious things.
Her nine months passed, and...
the time to give birth had come.
To prepare for the delivery...
she was moved to another room.
There, she made her move.
A space only a few centimeters wide...
Heavy with child and shaking with terrible contractions...
she escaped through the ventilation system.
She collapsed...
on the street, several meters from the gate.
Her water had already broken.
How beautiful!
How beautiful they are!
These are the babies who will lead
of humanity's future, aren't they
They're wonderful.
I came up with their names.
There's no need to think of such unnecessary things.
I came up with...
their names.
You don't need to bother.
Their names...
Please, I want to name them...
Name them...
No need.
There's no need for names.
Franz Bonaparta.
That's right.
Johan asked me where he is.
Bonaparta's still alive?
"I won't forgive. I will never forgive you."
"Even if I die these babies, growing
inside me, will definitely get their revenge."
Franz Bonaparta's still alive isn't he?
Ask Johan.
He's in there.
Some doctor you are.
There's a hospital up ahead.
If you tell me where Johan is, I'll take you there.
At this rate, you'll bleed to death.
I really don't know.
Out with it.
Some doctor...
You shot me, made me bleed this much,
and now you're threatening me.
Where's Johan?
Some doctor...
Just tell us!
Hurry!
I really don't know.
Eva...
There's a pay phone...
Call the hospital and tell them someone's
bleeding to death in a car.
W-What are you talking about?
This guy might tell us where Johan...
His life will be in danger if we keep him here any longer.
Hurry.
Call them.
You saved me again.
After all, you can't change who you are.
You can't kill someone.
He wants to see you.
I will tell you...
where Johan is.
Kenzou, an ambulance is on its way here.
Hurry, let's run away from...
Where's Kenzou?
He's gone.
He left a message for you.
"I can't get you involved in this any further."
"I ruined your life."
"I'm really sorry... Please be happy."
Why are you crying?
I don't understand.
I don't understand it at all.
Johan...
Welcome home.
Fire!
Fire coming from the Three Frogs!
Now, eat as much as you want.
If you eat that fast, you'll choke.
They must have been starving.
Where did you come from?
What's your name?
You won't talk at all, huh?
But that's all right.
Once you've eaten, we'll hear your story.
Wait!
Wait up!
Here!
What should we do?
What do you mean?
Those kids may not have any parents.
Even if they have parents, they might have
reasons for not wanting to go home.
We wanted children, didn't we?
Yeah...
We could take care of them...
Don't say such stupid things.
Sorry, that was harsh.
Anyway, let's call the police.
Huh?
What's the matter, boy?
Look!
Beautiful flowers.
I'm gonna go give these to the man and the lady.
It's fine.
Huh?
Didn't I say...
that I have a good plan?
Come on.
Hey!
Hey, wait up!
Wait! I said wait!
Wait!
I finally met you.
Back then, I ran away from the Red Rose Mansion,
went home to the Three Frogs...
and you welcomed me back.
So this timer I'll say it to you.
Welcome home.
Heidelberg...
Our twentieth birthday.
Since I went to get you, a lot of time has passed.
You came to get me?
You came to kill me.
Mr. Fortner... Mr. Liebert...
All the people who have been kind to us...
Everyone...
You killed everyone!
Come back...
Huh?
I said that it's nice out today, right?
Y-Yes.
Driver...
Yes?
Could you go a little faster?
You'll be okay.
Hang in there!
Shoot me.
Kill him...
I'll save you!
Will you shoot me like you did before?
Yes, I'll end everything.
End?
What is "the end"?
End...
End.
I've seen "the end of the world," time and again.
What is "the end"?
It will end.
You'll die, and I'll die, too.
You've seen it?
What have you seen?
Hey!
You don't know.
I'll tell you...
the actual, horrible story.
I'm home.
Yes
Cherish what you know is true in this world.
Ima kono sekai de wakaru koto mitsumete
Yes
Please believe in the kindness of your eyes
Anata no hitomi no yasashisa wo shinjite
Make it home to your land of harmony
Make it home to your land of purity
Make it home