Hi, Karl!
Hi, Lotte.
Do you have some time right now?
No, not really...
What's up?
W-Well, I just thought that maybe we
could go out for tea or something...
I thought we could also talk about the
incidents involving Mr. Schuwald...
We don't need to do that anymore.
But...
Sorry, I'm kind of in a hurry right now.
My father has to get to a meeting.
Later!
Um, about the dance party coming up...
Would you like to go... with me...?
Holy Ground
We're going to close soon.
O-Okay!
It's closing time.
That girl's here again...
What a pretty girl...
God is so unfair...
I'm sure a girl like her doesn't have any problems in life...
But that girl...
It's closing time!
O-Okay!
Sheesh!
I've seen that girl somewhere before...
A dance party?
Y-Yeah.
I don't really care about these things, but...
...my friends forced me to buy these.
I'm sorry, but tonight's no good.
The state legislature's holding a dinner meeting.
But it's not just a dinner meeting.
I'm sure there are a lot of people who would
want to go with you to the dance party.
Later.
Well, it's not like I really wanted to go, anyway...
Are you...
Oh?
Are you looking up information on Margot Langer, too?
Hey, you don't have to clear the screen like that!
I'm also doing research on her.
Oh, data for my thesis.
I'm a cultural anthropology major, Lotte Frank.
And you are?
This is pretty good, Ms. Nina Fortner.
This is "The Murder Case of the Accountant..."
This is a newspaper article on "The Murder
Case of the Voice of God..."
And this is "The Murder Case of
the Middle Aged Couple..."
You're pretty good!
Even though I'm pretty confident in my own
information gathering, I'm no match for you.
I'm currently looking into Bayern's unsolved
murders from the past four years.
Can you tell me more about the case of
the former prostitute, Margot Langer?
Just what I've told you so far.
The son born of Margot Langer and
the wealthy Hans Schuwald...
...was finally happily recognized by Schuwald...
...and has become his successor.
Any chance of the son being involved in the
incidents that occurred around Schuwald?
There's no way.
I'm 100% certain.
I see...
You seem enthusiastic about this.
You're digging pretty deep for just
a simple college research paper...
Y-You think so...?
It's not for a research paper, is it?
The truth is...
...I'm searching for someone...
Can I ask you a question?
Do people like you have problems, too?
What?
What I'm saying is...
Doesn't everything in the world go the
way you want when you're that pretty?
What are you trying to say?
For instance...
You've never had problems when
it comes to love, have you?
Never mind!
My problems have nothing to do with you, right?
God really is unfair...
Hey!
Do you want to hang out tonight?
Let's go to a dance party.
I don't really like these kinds of places...
Oh, don't say that.
Everyone will talk to me if I'm with you.
See, everyone's looking this way!
Hey!
I'll just take the leftovers.
Oh, Lotte...
See, here comes one now.
Hi!
I'm Konstantin, from the Transcendental
Phenomenon study group.
Nice to meet you.
Oh, crap.  One of those geeky ones.
I'm surprised he had the guts to talk
to you with that kind of face, Nina.
Wait, Lotte!
Will you be my partner for tonight?
M-Me?!
What's going on?
Way to go, Lotte!
I'll be going now.
Wait, Nina!
He's not my type!
Please stay with me, Nina!
Man!
We're kind of alone here.
You're right...
What do you mean by that?
Lots of guys have asked you out!
It's all because you're being too cold!
I wasn't being cold...
But it's been a while since I've had this much fun...
Since I've been together with students...
...and done stupid things with them...
It's really been a long time...
Nina, are you...
N-No, it's nothing!
You're pretty steadfast, despite your appearance.
Hey!  What do you mean, "despite my appearance"?
Hey, Lotte!
Please dance with me!
You again?
You're so annoying!
A short one's fine.  Just a short one...
And you're drunk, too!
Hey!
No, let go of me!
Cut it out already!
It's not like I"m asking you because I want to, you know?!
What do you mean by that?!
How rude!
Just dance with me once!
No, stop it!
Then I can get my money.
Money...?
What do you mean?
There's nothing to it.
Karl asked me to.
He asked me to be your partner for tonight.
Karl...?
So just dance a little with me.  That's all I ask!
Stop...
Oh, come on!
Stop it!
Just one song...
Ouch!  Ouch!
Okay!  I'm sorry!
I won't do it again!
Ouch!  Stop!
Let's go.
Because I like him...
Because I like Karl, I helped him find his father.
I... liked him...
But once he was able to prove that
he was Schuwald's real son...
He kept saying he had something to do with his father...
He kept saying he made a promise to his father...
"His father" this...
"His father" that...
It hurts...
It hurts!
I didn't think being turned down would hurt so much!
Yes it hurts...
Everything feels bad.
But it's okay.
I'm sure it's okay.
Bad things don't last long.
You mustn't let it last so long.
Right?
Well, I'll be going now.
Tell me where I can reach you, Nina.
I'm sorry, but I haven't decided
where I'm going to live yet...
Then give me a call at my house.
It's a promise, okay?
Okay.
I really had fun today.
I hope you find the one you're looking for.
Nina...
That girl...
I knew I'd seen her before...
She looks exactly like Johan...
You're pretty good shot, Doctor.
Though it's probably due more to the
efficiency of the gun, than your skill.
Even though it failed the German military's
test for being their official sniper rifle...
...you can still hit a 5cm circle from 300m with that gun.
Even as an amateur.
I don't know what you're trying to shoot...
...but the closer you get, the higher
your chance of hitting it will be.
All that's left is to pick a location free of
obstacles between you and your target.
It uses .338 Lapua Magnum bullets.
It can hold a maximum of four bullets.
However, you can't afford to shoot all four bullets.
If you can't finish it in one shot, it's over.
You've been coming here every single day recently.
Are you here to bird watch?
Y-Yeah...
Every Thursday, this forest gets a lot of visitors.
Those two young men with that old guy...
...and you.
Do you like this forest?
Yeah...
Um... what about you?
Me?
Me...
I'm apologizing to this forest.
And have been for the past sixty years.
I've never seen him around here.
What's with him?
I was proud of that dish, yet he didn't eat much of it.
Let's get to the question so they can earn valuable prizes!
Our first contestant, Mr. Weidlich, comes from Frankfurt!
And here's his prize!
It's a camper!
That's what his family wanted most!
Mr. Weidlich seems really happy!
It'll be great if he can go camping in this!
However, unless he answers ten questions correctly,
he won't be able to win this camper!
Now, the first question!
Are you going to leave without touching your food again?
You came here about a week ago, didn't you?
No matter how busy we get, I still
remember my customer's faces.
If you don't have an appetite, at least eat the soup.
It's on the house!
You look terrible.
Thank you very much...
This is the place.
I'll have to shoot him here in the forest!
You saved me.
I can't believe I slipped, after walking
the same road all these years.
I must be getting old.
I don't think you broke anything.
I've given you first aid.
Please have it checked out at a hospital.
Are you a doctor...?
I thought you were a hunter when I first saw you...
Looks like I was wrong.
Oh, this is a surprise!
What's the matter?
It's the birds...
The birds are gathering.
Long ago, wild birds would perch
on a certain man's shoulder...
When he stretched out his arm like
this, wild birds would land on it.
When he was little, he used to spend all
his time with the birds in this forest.
However, eventually, Hitler's era came.
The man was stationed with the police.
He truly believed that socialism and the Nazi party...
...would make this the ideal country.
One day, he was given an order.
An atrocious criminal ran into this forest.
He was chosen to chase after the criminal
because he was familiar with the forest.
To shoot and kill the criminal on sight.
He chased the criminal through the forest
that he knew like the back of his hand.
He chased...
And he chased...
However...
When he finally cornered him, he wasn't an atrocious
criminal, but just a normal foreigner.
However, no matter who the foreigner
was, he had no choice.
He carried out his order.
Since then, the birds have never perched on his shoulder...
He's been apologizing for sixty years.
I'm sorry...
However, the birds won't come near him.
Dear God in Heaven...
It's okay now...
Never again...
Never again will blood be shed in this forest...
Isn't that right?