Has the patient's condition changed?
Umm... but...
What's his blood pressure and pulse rate?
Excuse me, Dr. Tenma...
What about Mayor Roedecker's operation?
I'm beginning the operation.
Yes, sir.
Oh yeah. What's the patient's name?
Huh?
What is this boy's name?
Well, let's see...
We don't... know his name, do we?
It'll be okay.
Hang on.
I'll save you.
Kill... him...
Those kids!
The twins! I can't find them anywhere!
Did you really look everywhere?!
I did!
I looked everywhere!
Maybe they're playing hide and seek somewhere!
"Maybe they're playing hide and seek somewhere," huh?
Scaredy-cat Tenma! Scaredy-cat Tenma! Yaaay!
It's no use hiding, scaredy-cat Tenma!
If you force yourself to hide,
you'll wet your pants again!
You guys, it s getting late! How much
longer are you going to be?
Coming now!
See you tomorrow.
See ya!
Bye bye.
Bye bye!
What about me?
Everyone, I'm right here.
Come find me.
I'm right here!
Come find me!
"Scaredy-cat Tenma," huh?
A Monster of Chaos
What should we do?
The man who came earlier this evening
is still waiting at the gate.
Who is he?
He's the psychiatrist of Richard
Braun, that detective we hired.
I'll get rid of him.
Karl, I can't see.
What kind of man is he?
Well, he's an older man.
What do you think of him?
He doesn't look like a bad man...
and he looks like he's at his wit's end.
I see.
Thank you for seeing me, Herr Schuwald.
Let's skip the pleasantries.
It's late.
Anyway, let me hear what you have to say.
I don't have much time, either.
But how long this takes depends entirely on you.
Didn't you come to ask about him?
About Johan.
Looks like I'm right, huh?
I suspected someone like you would
come to see me someday...
in order to solve the mystery.
Mystery?
He's too perfect.
People who can see may not
understand this, but I feel it...
He's a man who is in perfect harmony with himself.
It's as though he doesn't really exist.
He does exist, I assure you.
Here, I've gathered fragments of his past.
I'll read it to you.
You'll find that he is neither a
phantom nor an illusion.
The story begins in 1986, when a fatally
wounded boy was carried into a hospital.
And then, he appeared before you.
According to the late... no, murdered Richard...
Johan had a student named Fahren
pretend to be your son.
However, as soon as your real son Karl appeared, he
changed his plans and helped reunite the two of you.
And Fahren committed suicide.
How did you come to accept your son,
who was apart from you for so long?
In these last few years, how many
people close to you have died?
The driver who served you for many years.
The maid who read books to you.
The accountant who had been your
bird-watching companion.
Everyone died.
Everything happened because
Johan wanted to isolate you...
so he could get to your heart.
Please, help me out.
Everything must be brought to light.
Otherwise, the Japanese doctor, Dr. Tenma...!
You said Johan was playing with people as
though they were ants in a line, right?
Ants in a line...
Do you know what people call me?
Yes, the Vampire of Bayern.
I accepted the nickname with pride.
If I try to master myself, somehow
it gets bigger and bigger.
The monster inside of me.
But how is it now?
The nickname sounds great, but I'm so feeble.
Come to think of it, I also wanted to play as
though I was toying with a line of ants...
like this...
He's trying to become what I wanted to become.
"Who is like unto the Monster?"
"Who is able to make war with him?"
Is that Johan's revelation?
I think only a greater monster can defeat this one.
Father...
Hmm?
What were you guys discussing?
It's morning already.
Yeah.
By the way, where is Johan?
He's heading to the ceremony hall directly
from the Ester Hohen office.
You look very tired. Should I
cancel today"s ceremony?
No, get me ready for it.
Kill... him...
Dr. Tenma...
It's not your fault.
You only performed your duty as a doctor.
Please stay alive.
And... please save as many lives as you can.
Nina...
That's too bad.
Are you really going to quit?
You just started to get used to the work.
Thank you very much for everything.
Come see me if you're ever back in the area, okay?
I will. Well, then...
She was a good girl...
Hello? Is Lotte Frank there?
Lotte is out right now.
I see. Could you tell her that I'm taking
a train out of Munich at three?
Okay, I will.
Oh, may I have your name again?
Nina.
Nina Fortner.
He's here!
His car just pulled up at the back entrance.
The Vampire of Bayern is finally here.
Shhh. He 'II hear you.
Did you see the guests in the hall?
Yeah, not just from Bayern, but company representatives
from all over Europe, America and Japan...
and so many ambassadors and politicians...
I can't believe that this is just a donation
ceremony for a collection of books.
Yeah. They say that every single thing Mr. Schuwald
does affects the whole European economy.
He rarely shows up in public, so
everyone came to see, I guess.
But he's suddenly donating his library now...
so it's like he's giving away his last will and testament.
Hey, don't say that!
He's a vital person to the European economy.
We need him to stay alive a little longer.
Karl.
Yes?
I forgot a document. Can you go get it for me?
What document?
Just go back and get it.
It's on the desk in my study.
But, Father...
Johan is coming soon.
He'll take care of everything here.
O-Okay.
What's happening with the investigation?
It's going well.
Going well?
I thought you were going to
put a lot of effort into this.
That's why I told you Tenma was in Munich.
But what are you doing?
Did you check up on Johan Liebert, who is
working as Schuwald s secretary?
There's no mistake that he's the real serial killer.
Are you listening?
If you don't hurry, Tenma may...
Tenma is trying to settle this on his own!
Don't worry. The investigation is going quite well.
Excuse me.
Johan is right in front of us?
Hurry, arrest him!
You are indeed a criminal psychologist.
That's a good way to put it.
Certainly, Johan does exist.
Johan exists...
inside Tenma's head.
Did you get anything new out of him?
Nope.
He's been saying the same thing.
The gun was a Mauser SR-93.
The person he sold it to was Japanese.
Should we question him some more?
No, that's probably all he knows.
Yeah.
The Mauser SR-93 is a sniper rifle, right?
Yes, it's a quality model.
I wonder who the target is.
I am Tenma.
1 am Tenma.
I procured a high-grade sniper rifle.
I am Tenma.
And I...
I am Johan.
Who would I shoot with this rifle?
I killed the hospital directors.
I killed several middle-aged couples.
Now who should I kill?
Chaos...
I love chaos.
You should eat something.
Yeah.
Thank you, Dieter.
I'm fine, don't worry about me.
I'm not going to give up.
1 may not look like it now, but when I was a cop and
a doctor for the National Border Security Patrol...
I was well-trained, both physically and psychologically.
I will definitely save your friend.
No matter what!
Don't underestimate an ex-police doctor.
Now, you kindly prepared breakfast
for me, so I'm going to eat it.
Can't fight on an empty stomach, you know.
This is it!
You found something?
Schuwald's library donation ceremony!
Tenma's there?
Dieter, wait here!
Don't follow me!
Schuwald!
Huh?
I want to see Hans Georg Schuwald.
Contact him.
Okay.
Oh I think he's at the Munich University library
donating his collection of books today.
We'll go there immediately.
What?
Tenma's target is Schuwald.
Now, please welcome Mr. Hans Georg Schuwald, who
gave us this huge and precious collection of books.
Where is Johan?
Is my secretary here?
Huh?
Yes, he's right there.
He came.
I brought him back to life.
I... brought that monster back to life...
Nina!
Lotte!
You came!
I'm sorry. I looked for him everywhere,
but he doesn't seem to be here, so...
Though we've become friends, it's too bad...
You guys...
are twins, aren't you?
Am I right?
I'm right, aren't I?
What does this picture book mean?
He suddenly collapsed when he saw this.
A picture book?
Kill... him...
Yes
Cherish what you know is true in this world.
Ima kono sekai de wakaru koto mitsumete
Yes
Please believe in the kindness of your eyes.
Anata no hitomi no yasashisa wo shinjite
Make it home to your land of harmony
Make it home to your land of purity
Make it home