Nice
Souther France
Barbara,
how about a Moscow Mule?
Thank you, Michael.
Fritz,
here is some juice for you.
where is the "thank you" for your father?
Thank you, Mr. Müller.
Fritz!
It can't be helped.
He will eventually get used to it.
The new antique art dealership I
started will eventually get rolling, too.
But for me,
it's still all very sudden.
What?
After all, suddenly I am able to live in this terrific place
and also have a nice husband
who makes tasty cocktails like these.
Hey,
do you sense anything?
What?
The house next door.
At times, I feel as though someone was
watching us from that second floor window.
Oh, please.
The house next door is vacant, isn't it?
I know.
Still...
To tell you the truth, I heard this from Mr. Dautry,
who lives across the street from us.
Heard what?
Twenty years ago,
a couple was slaughtered
in the house next door,
and ever since then, there have been ghosts sighted there.
What is wrong, Michael?
Don't tell me you actually believe that story.
Of course not.
Are you going out?
Yes.
I'll bring the car out front.
Oh, no.  Don't bother.
I think sometimes we should go
out just by ourselves, as a family.
I doubt we will need a bodyguard.
Is that so?
Well, I'm sure Fritz will get
used to you more quickly that way.
Yeah, that is exactly my goal.
Go for it,
Dad.
Well, let's get going.
Happy Holidays
So, detective, what did you find out?
Well, let's start with Dr. Tenma.
The police are after him as the
main suspect in the Fortners' homicide.
However, his current whereabouts are unknown.
When he was first taken in for questioning,
Tenma reportedly said something along these lines:
the boy whose life he saved
ten years ago had been on the run
ever since he murdered the director of
Eisler Memorial Hospital and two others.
The boy's name was Johan.
Later on, Johan showed up as a young adult
and committed murder again,
this time right in front of Dr. Tenma.
Next is Nina Fortner.
She is the daughter of the murdered couple,
but she is also still missing.
Here is Mr. Messner.
I traced him to Frankfurt.
What is he doing now?
He passed away.
What?
It happened about two months ago.
He was stabbed multiple times.
They said he got caught up in a conflict over drugs.
Messner was my partner
when I was with the police.
Is that so?
Mr. Messner was dismissed from
the force for his involvement with drugs.
The one who took Messner under
his wing was a man called "The Baby."
This man is a powerful figure in a fascist organization.
What does that matter?
This past winter, there was a series of arson
cases in Frankfurt's Turkish town, wasn't there?
It's rumored that "The Baby" was
the mastermind behind this incident,
that a certain Asian man prevented it from succeeding,
and that the Asian man's name was Tenma.
If this man was Dr. Tenma...
Oh, one more thing... It's said that
the fires were meant to be a festival
to welcome a certain youth
as the leader of the fascist organization.
A certain youth?
What was the name of the boy
whose life Dr. Tenma saved ten years ago?
Johan.
The name of the youth that "The Baby"
tried to set up as the organization's leader...
was also Johan.
Aha, so that's the move you chose to play.
Say, Roberto.
Isn't my life
like a chess piece?
Is something bothering you?
Up until that time...
when that phone call came...
my life was always about losing.
When we were detectives, my partner Messner and I
resold drugs that had been seized by the police.
The guy on the other end of the line knew everything.
If we wanted him to keep quiet, he said,
we would have to kill a certain couple.
The Fortners in Heidelberg...
If we killed them, we'd be let off of the hook.
That night,
there was some journalist there was well,
so Messner and I killed all three.
Afterwards,
a huge sum was deposited into our accounts.
The syndicate picked me up
after I quit the force.
In addition, they appointed me to a
really good post from the start.
The money I earned got laundered without any trouble.
Then you met your wife,
and washed your hands of the syndicate.
Why was I allowed to leave so easily?
Who was the person at the
other end of the line of that phone call?
The one who deposited that
large sum of money into my account?
The one who is controlling my life?
Who is he?
Roberto,
I am grateful to you.
You've been protecting me all the way until now.
Then, will you wait on that move?
Huh?
I can't do that.
You are a harsh one.
Okay, sweetie.  I'm going.
Yeah,
take care.
Hey, please buy me toys!  Please?
Fritz, how about tell your father, "I'm leaving"?
That won't happen...
his head is full of toys.
I'm leaving, Dad!
I'm leaving!
Roberto,
has the detective called?
He should be here by now.
Roberto.
Roberto, the detective is dead!
Please get over here!
Roberto!
Y-you're...?
I am the daughter of the Fortners, whom you killed.
Did you do this?
Roberto!
Your bodyguard, Roberto, is the one who killed him!
Roberto did?
I was watching everything from the house next door.
That's impossible.
Roberto is a friend whom I can trust!
B-but you...
You came here to get your revenge, didn't you?
R-Roberto!
Roberto!
I'll be taking this bag.
If you want to stay here, go ahead...
if you have anyone you can trust, that is!
What's wrong, Mr. Müller?
Mr. Müller?
Start the car. Hurry.
Hurry!
You were watching me for a long
time from the house next door, right?
What do you intend to do with me?
I hate you from the bottom of my heart.
Enough to make me want to kill you!
I-I did it because I was threatened!
I was told that unless I killed your parents,
I would be exposed for illegally reselling drugs.
That's why...
I did with Messner... because we had no choice.
We had not choice!
You had no choice...?
No...
choice?!
Stop!
Stop the car!
They were great people...
Really great...
My father and mother
loved me from the bottom of their hearts.
W-wait.
Even though I was not their real daughter...
my father and mother...
really loved... me...
really...
P-please!
Please don't!
But...
But they were killed by scum like you!
Barbara...
Fritz...
Oh, my...
Come here.
Barbara...
Fritz...
What...
What are you saying...?
What is with you?
So, this is what it's like...
to be killed.
Fritz...
that child... called me, for the first time...
He called me "Dad."
I have...
I now have things I don't want to lose.
Barbara...
Fritz...
Every morning in Düsseldorf
at 8:30, at that café...
When I joined the syndicate, my boss gave me an order.
He told me to act as though I was a normal
business man with a regular morning schedule.
Every morning, a mother would
pass in front of the café with her child.
It was my only contact with normal life.
H-hi.
Good morning.
What did you ask that private detective to investigate?
The whereabouts of you and Tenma,
and what happened to my old partner, Messner.
But Messner was dead.
He was apparently killed.
I asked the detective to
investigate his death further, in greater detail.
Last night, there was a phone call from the detective...
Things are becoming strange.
Strange?
Yes.  Messner was a drug addict.
He was no longer someone who would
get caught up in a scuffle with the organization.
Another thing,
the killer was not affiliated with the Frankfurt organization,
but he was with the Düsseldorf--
Düsseldorf?
Uh, let's discuss this in more detail when we meet.
Here it is,
the draft of his report.
"On Messner's death:"
"The killer..."
"Roberto..."
"who is he?"
Do you
understand what this means?
Hello?
I'd like the bag back, if you don't mind.
R-Roberto?
Your wife and Fritz are relaxing somewhere close to me.
H-hey, what did you say?
Put my wife on the line!
You should come back soon...
to your happy home.
A gun.
What?
Can you lend me a gun?
That gun can only be used at close distances.
Also, there are only four shots...
It's enough.
Despite everything, I'm still a former cop.
Be careful.
Because if I die,
I can't tell the truth to the police, right?
Yes.
You must not die, no matter what!
I will cover you from the vacant house next door!
Dad!
F-Fritz!
Dad, look!  It's a fishing rod!
Oh, this child...
He wouldn't stop talking about
how he will have his father take him fishing.
Barbara...
Where is Roberto?
Oh, now that you mention it,
several coworkers of his from
the security company are here.
It looks like something happened while we were out.
Coworkers?
But don't worry.
They said there was no damage.
Oh, Roberto,
Michael's back.
Don't worry, sir.
A glass pane was broken, that's all.
It must have been a prank by
one of the neighborhood children.
There is nothing to worry about.
Wh-where is the body?
The body of the detective that was here!
There was nothing here.
Roberto,
who...
Who are you?
That will make your wife and Fritz come over.
Please, don't make things more difficult.
Now...
That's good.
Now, with this we can call
say that nothing happened today.
Today was a peaceful day.
It will be peaceful from now on, too.
Nina!
Nina...
What a beautiful girl she was.
What did you do with her?
We are treating her extremely well.
She is a very important guest for a certain someone.
A certain someone?
The name of the youth... was also Johan.
Johan, Johan, Johan...
Who is this Johan?
Who are you people?
You wish to live happily ever
after with your wife and Fritz.
Why not let it rest at that?
There is
nothing wrong with that.
Thank you for having me for so long.
I must bid you farewell today.
What do you intend to do with Nina?
Are you going to kill her?
Have a happy life.
Dad, when will you take me fishing?
Oh, hmm...
Tomorrow,
if it's sunny.
Yay!
I no longer see ghosts, I guess...
You have marvelous eyes.
You are very much like Johan.
When can I see Johan?
I came without resisting
because you said I could meet Johan.
It is certainly true that he wants to see you very much.
Where is he right now?
He is living happily in Münich.
Münich?
You really do have marvelous eyes.
I really regret this.
Now, the only person left is...
Dr. Tenma...
Why...
Why did you come?
I told you, didn't I?
Despite everything, I'm still a former cop.
We'll reach your home soon...
Yes...
I made a promise...
to take Fritz...
fishing tomorrow.
I see...
I hope it will be sunny...
I'm sure...
I'm sure that it will be.