Dr. Tenma, it's not your fault.
You only fulfilled your duty as a doctor.
It's not your fault.
Please eat the sandwiches.
And please, get some sleep.
Please stay alive.
And... please save as many lives as you can.
Nina Fortner.
Nina...
What are you planning to do now?
Are you going to kill him again?
It was me who brought him back to life.
It was me who brought that monster...
...back to life!
Note:  A.V.M. = Arteriovenous Malformation
There are several blood vessels embedded in this A.V.M.
Cut all the influx arteries.
Deal with all the outflowing arteries afterwards.
Finished the extraction of the nidus.
That went very well!
Yes, it was amazing!
That clipping went very quickly!
That was a marvelous operation.
Even though that was your first operation
since your sabbatical...
...your genius has only grown!
It's over...
Never mind.
Pursued
That is amazing, Kenzou!
The news wasn't about me...
That is true, but...
It is because you performed a perfect surgery
with my father's team last night.
I'm sure my father appreciates your efforts.
You are responsible for improving the hospital's reputation.
I'm the one who should be thankful...
...since it is thanks to your father that
I can work like this in Germany.
Good luck, Kenzou.
I'm positive everything will work out fine
if you follow in my father's footsteps.
It is only a matter of time before my
father becomes the chief director.
Then you'll soon be the head of the surgical department.
And eventually, a director.
That will make me the wife of a director.
You better make me happy...
...because hardship doesn't suit me.
Should we leave?
Or should we...
P-Please, sir!
The madam is resting!
I won't take up a lot of her time.
I'll leave as quickly as possible.
B-But please, come back after you have
made an appointment to see her!
Shut up...
Please forgive me, Madam.
There is a policeman here to see you...
Policeman...?
It has been a while, Ms. Eva Heinemann.
Who are you?
I was investigating your father's death nine years ago.
I'm Lunge from the BKA.
Lunge?
You can go, Horst.
Y-Yes, madam.
I remember you now.
You're that worthless detective who couldn't solve a case.
What do you want with me now?
You're really something to have
maintained this large mansion...
...even after the death of your father.
No... if anything, the furnishings have
become even more extravagant.
You came to see how much I've made...
...from my father's inheritance and the alimony?
You can see for yourself.
I want for nothing.
If you see something you like, you are
welcome to take it home with you.
As long as I have my alcohol, that is enough for me.
I came because I have something to show you.
This necktie.
Necktie?
Do you recall seeing it anywhere?
You might not remember it...
...since it is an item from nine years ago.
It has a simple pattern...
...but if you look closely, the weaving is very elaborate.
It's a rather high quality tie.
What about it?
This tie gave me a hard time...
...since it was made nine years ago.
Luckily, however, this item...
...was a limited edition, made specially
for frequent clients of the store.
And on their list of clients...
...I found your name.
So what?
Might you have...
...bought this as a present for someone?
It will be an important key to solving a certain murder case.
Murder...?
Who knows?
I bought presents for so many men that I don't
have time to remember every single one.
All the men chasing me...
...are only after my money.
Please try to remember.
I told you, I don't know!
Every single one was a gold digger.
There is not a single human being who would
love me from the bottom of his heart.
That is why I robbed them all with divorce settlements!
All three times!
Serves them right!
Do you want something too?
Do you?
Talk to me.
But it will cost you big time!
I will come again.
Contact me if you remember anything.
Bring a  bottle of whiskey the next time you come.
Excuse me.
Eva...
Eva, can't you say something to your father about this?
I didn't do anything wrong!
I only performed the operation in the
order the patients were brought in!
That is... the engagement ring I gave you...
You really are a fool.
Eva!
Oh, that suit looks spectacular, Dr. Norden!
You look rather dazzling tonight yourself, Eva.
Horst!  Get the car ready!
You have gotten better, Mr. Hess.
You look really well.
At this rate, you might be able to
leave the hospital this week.
Thank you very much, Dr. Tenma.
My daughter's wedding is next month.
Do you think I'll be able to make it?
Yes, no problem.
But please take it easy at the reception.
Thank you.
I was about to give up...
It is all thanks to you...
No, it is all because you tried your best.
With you as my doctor...
...I feel like I'll see not only my daughter's wedding,
but my grandchild's wedding as well.
You really are a wonderful doctor.
Please continue your work at this hospital.
Excuse me, Dr. Tenma.
You have a guest.
I'm about to visit my other patients.
I'll be busy, so can you tell him to come back later?
B-But...
Eva...?
It's been a long time, Kenzou.
Yeah...
A lot of things happened between us, huh?
Are you asleep already, father?
I'm coming in.
Father!
Eva...
Eva!
I know it's hard, but pull yourself together...
Don't touch me!
Give me back my father!
Father!
Kenzou!
Please, I'm sorry!
Kenzou...
Kenzou!
Did you lose some weight?
No...
I heard you took a sabbatical.
Yes, you should take a rest like that from time to time.
You are a workaholic.
Did you lose some weight?
A lot has happened...
You heard the rumors, right?
Yeah...
It is spring...
Do you remember?
Springtime, ten years ago...
...we used to go driving a lot.
We were so young.
You tried to go swimming in the spring.
I got scared and stopped you...
You were so...
I'm sorry, but...
I don't have time for this, Eva.
Kenzou...
I want to start over!
I finally realized after ruining three different marriages...
The only one who really loved me...
...was you, Kenzou.
I'm sorry.
Kenzou!
Please, Kenzou!
I'm happy you feel that way about me, but...
...I can't accept it.
Goodbye.
Wait, Kenzou!
I didn't say anything!
The police came asking about your necktie, but...
You did something bad with that tie, didn't you?
That necktie was definitely the
one I gave you as a present.
I'll stay quiet as long as you do what I say!
I have something I have to do.
Then I'll tell them everything!
I'll tell the police about the necktie!
I'll tell them everything!
I'll tell them that the incident where my
father and the others were killed...
...was all your fault too!
I see.
Bring Dr. Tenma to me as a material witness.
B-But this isn't enough evidence to tie him to
the murders of the Fortners and Mr. Mauler...
I'm only concerned with the murder that took
place at Heidelberg Castle right now.
O-Okay!
Thank you for your cooperation.
We may be able to solve a number of cases at once now.
Resignation...?
What is the meaning of this, Dr. Tenma?
Please forgive me for my selfishness, Director.
There have been a lot of strange rumors
about you recently, but...
...I don't believe any of them.
Why don't you think this over and...
H-Hey!
Dr. Tenma!
Yes, it's me!
The police?
What?!
Dr. Tenma is suspected of murder?!
Close off all entrances to the ward!
Don't forget the rear entrances as well!
Yes, sir!
Where is Dr. Tenma?
I... I don't know!
What are you doing over there?
Hurry up and find him!
B-But, Inspector...
What is this?
Get out of the way!
This is obstruction of justice!
There is no way Dr. Tenma would kill anybody!
That is right!
He saved all our lives!
Dr. Tenma is innocent!
Go home, cops!
Yeah, leave!
Get out!
Looks like there is a huge commotion over there.
There are a lot of police cars out there, Dr. Tenma.
I-Is that so?
I wonder what happened?
Anyway, please drop me off in front of the station.
Okay.
You are busy as usual, Dr. Tenma.
I...
I have an operation waiting  for me in there.
Wait, Dr. Tenma!
Dr. Tenma!
You will be okay.
Hang in there!
I will save you!
I am not wrong!
I have an attitude problem, you say?!
What the hell are you, then?!
You are not a doctor!  You are just in it for the money!
People like him... People like him...
...are better off dead!
This is terrible!
We can't find the twins anywhere!
W-What is this?
What the hell... happened here...?!
It has been a long time, doctor.
It is me.
You probably already forgot about those two little twins...
Johan?!
Help me, Doctor!
I don't want to die!
Doctor!
I should have died back then.
But you brought me back to life, Doctor.
5 Months Later
It is gonna be another hot day today.
Aren't you hot, dressed like that in the summer?
What is that?  Is that newspaper three days old?
They said another middle aged couple
was murdered, this time in Verden.
They said a doctor did it, didn't they?
Speaking of which, you said you were
going to Verden, didn't you?
Do you know someone there or something?
Yeah...
I don't know if I'll meet him there...
...but I have to go.