Where did it happen?
In the basement!
The victims?
Three males!
I want you to thoroughly inspect
the area surrounding the scene!
I thought we'd wait for Detective Kratoky
to arrive and give us orders...
I'll take full responsibility!
Detain any suspicious people on sight!
W-What kind of people?
Anybody who looks suspicious!
But...
Do you have a problem taking
orders from a new detective?!
Hurry up and go!
Detective Suk of the Prague Police!
This is really nasty...
Inspector... Zeman...
He's been savagely beaten to death.
There's nothing left of his face...
If he hadn't dropped his badge...
we probably wouldn't have known who, he was.
There are two more dead males over there.
We still don't know who they are.
One of them was shot in the head.
The other was beaten to death, just like the Inspector.
P-Preserve the scene!
Detective Suk!
Excuse me...
What kind of people are suspicious...?
Detective Suk
You've gotta be kidding me!
They're making fun of me because
they think I'm a newbie!
Those officers won't even listen to me!
Well, that is coming from someone who's unreliable.
Yeah.
What was that?!
You vomited at the scene, didn't you?
Nobody wants to take orders from
an agent who's that weak.
Just because you're fond of detective stories
doesn't mean you're fit for the job!
Jan has always been capricious since our college days.
What do you guys know?
You don't know how nicely the late
Inspector Zeman treated me!
To a newcomer who didn't know his right from his left...
Inspector Zeman taught me how to be a detective...
I respected Inspector Zeman from
the bottom of my heart...
I will get revenge for Inspector Zeman!
I'll find the killer, even if I have to do it myself!
W-Well...
We have to get up early tomorrow for work, so...
What?
Stay a little longer!
The only reason you guys can work with peace of mind...
is because I'm fighting for justice!
Here, drink some more!
You should stop already!
Every day, we work for justice...
and we get killed...
I can't stand it anymore...
Such a thankless job...
What's wrong?
She's the girl from the supermarket...
Sometimes, after my night shift, I go to the supermarket...
I've seen her there twice.
That girl...
I wanted to say something to her, but I couldn't...
I can't believe she's here...
Hey, hey! Stop!
A girl as pretty as she is won't even look at you!
E-Excuse me...
H-Hello!
Do I look familiar?
But I know you.
Oh, I'm Jan Suk.
I'm definitely not suspicious.
Despite my looks, I'm actually a detective.
Oh, no.
Please don't be scared just because I'm a detective!
I'm off-duty right now.
So this is all private!
I think it's a futile effort...
Well, guess we'll lend him a hand today.
I'm sorry he's being so forward.
He's really depressed today.
Would you mind keeping him company?
The boss he admired was involved in an incident.
All he's doing is moping around.
W-Who's moping?!
There are no good people like him...
I wanted to be like Inspector Zeman...
That's why I'm never going to forgive the killer!
I'll definitely catch him, and then...
I'm sorry, I'm just rambling.
It's okay.
You have to work hard to catch
that person, for your inspector.
Oh, I've talked a lot about myself...
but I haven't heard anything about you yet!
What's your name?
I don't know my real name...
W-Whats that supposed to mean...?
Oh wait a minute!
I'll try to guess who you are.
I am a detective, after all.
Leave these kinds of things to me!
Let's see your name is...
If I don't know it myself...
there's no way you could know.
The only things I know about myself are...
Cedok Bridge...
and the Three Frogs...
That's all.
Hey, wait!
When can I see you again...?!
See?  It was useless after all.
Just think of it as a dream, and give up.
We've confirmed the identities of the two men
who were killed with Inspector Zeman.
Prague Police Station
One is Cestomil Malad.
The other is Jakov Shachek.
They were both ex-sergeants of the former
Czechoslovakian secret police.
After the collapse of communism...
they took shady jobs in the underworld.
After examining the blood traces at the scene...
we've discovered that some was not from
Inspector Zeman, Malad, or Shachek.
The blood was type AB, Rh positive.
Judging from the amount of blood, it's likely that the
unidentified person was also seriously injured.
We are currently trying to identify that person.
Detective Suk!
Suk!
Y-Yes!
What were you daydreaming about?
We re here busting our asses because
of the loss of Zeman, that great man!
What's with that attitude of yours, huh?
I-I'm terribly sorry...
Anyway...
Like I said at the beginning...
According to the stories told by the witnesses...
there was a man walking around
the area right after the incident.
We know that he's tall and thin...
and dressed like a traveler carrying
a large bag on his back.
Put all your efforts into locating this man!
That girl...
There's no way... that she'd come again...
Mr. Detective!
Have you found that killer yet?
N-Not yet.
I feel pathetic...
While I'm sitting in here like this...
that killer is out there, free...
Inspector Zeman...
The day before he was killed, he spent
the night investigating a murder case.
What kind of case was it?
There was an incident...
where an old man who ran an unlicensed orphanage...
and his female assistant were both killed.
Even the following morning...
he was questioning the first person
to discover the crime scene.
What kind of person was he?
The first person to discover the crime scene...
Let's see...
He seemed like a really nice guy.
Even though he was tall and skinny...
he was carrying around this heavy-looking bag...
Thin...
Tall...
Large bag...
Could it be...?!
Do you know where that man is?
I... I think I know!
I'll get the station to look it up!
Hello.
Good luck, Mr. Detective.
Oh, hello?
Ah, please wait!
Oh, hello.
Cedok Bridge...
and the Three Frogs...
Cedok Bridge is in the old urban Michalska area...
The Three Frogs?
This is the place...
I can meet that girl if I come here!
He checked out?!
When?!
Let's see... Mr. Grimmer... Mr. Grimmer...
Mr. Grimmer checked out two days ago, in the morning.
There's no doubt about it...
The one who killed Inspector Zeman...
was this Grimmer person who stayed here!
Damn it!
Why didn't I realize it sooner?
I'll catch him, Inspector Zeman!
No matter what!
Suk?! What are you doing here?
I could ask you the same question, Detective Patera.
I see.
So you got this far all by yourself?
That's quite impressive.
Thank you...
I was actually hoping to take most of the
credit for Inspector Zeman's case...
but if you're this far already, Detective
Patera, then that means...
Well, I'll give credit where it's due.
You did very well.
Thank you...
That's what I'd like to say...
but keep this case a secret!
Why is that?
Capturing Grimmer ASAP should be our...!
This case is more complicated than it seems.
What?
You don't know about the top secret investigation
Zeman was entrusted with, do you?
Inspector Zeman... was on a top secret investigation...?
It was to root out all of the...
former Czech secret police officers who
still work at the Prague station...
and hide themselves by altering their personal histories.
Former Czechoslovakian secret police...?
The two men who were killed...
were also former secret police, weren't they?
Only the chief of police, myself, and
a few others know about this.
If you get in too deep, you might also get yourself killed.
Keep quiet about this case.
Got it?
T-Then what should I do...?
Let's see...
Well, Grimmer might show up at this hotel again.
Be on the lookout.
Y-Yes, sir!
By the way, Suk...
Did you get yourself a girlfriend or something?
You're daydreaming during meetings
and while sitting at your desk!
S-She's not my girlfriend or anything!
She's just a girl... who comes to
the bar I go to sometimes...
Is she pretty?
W-Well, yeah...
Hey, hey! Introduce me to her!
Where is this bar?
Introduce you...?
That's...
She's not your girlfriend or anything, right?
W-Well, that may be true, but...
Suk isn't coming today.
This is a surprise!
You really are good-looking!
Who are you...?
Oh, me?
I'm Suk's boss.
The name's Patera.
He said there was a really pretty girl at this bar so...
He's on a stakeout tonight, so he can't come.
Would you like to drink with me?
Oh, hey, wait!
Just a little wouldn't hurt, would it?
Hey, Suk!
Good morning Detective Janacek
I heard it from Mr. Patera.
The girl you found is pretty hot, eh?
You went to that bar, Mr. Patera?!
Yeah.
Y-You didn't do.anything to her, did you?!
Now, now, Suk.
Don't get so worked up!
B-But Detective Patera is famous for being a player...!
Don't worry.
She completely ditched me.
She must be really hard to get if even
Mr. Patera couldn't seduce her, Suk!
T-That's not...
I... I was just... talking to her...
That was fun enough for me, so...
What are you muttering about?
Section Chief Farobek wanted you
to go to Inspector Zeman's office.
O-Okay!
Oh, that's right.
Someone gave me these.
Would you like a whiskey bonbon?
None for me.
How about you, Suk?
Oh, no thank you.
Hey, Suk!
Yes?
Keep that suspect who looks like a toothpick a secret.
Yes, sir.
We've emptied most of Inspector Zeman's desk.
Only his personal belongings are left.
Pack up all these things and take
them to the Inspector's wife.
Yes, sir.
This is a gym locker key.
Oh, this is bad!
There are so many sweat-stained
shirts and towels in here!
Files...?
What's this?
These are detailed files of all the station
employees and their personal histories...
Even my profile is in here!
You don't know about the top secret investigation
Zeman was entrusted with, do you?
It was to root out all of the...
former Czech secret police officers who
still work at the Prague station...
and hide themselves by altering their personal histories.
What does this mean...?
How come only Detective Patera and
Detective Janacek aren't in here...?
This really is an abnormal sum of money.
Y-Yes, Chief!
So, Suk.
What do you deduce from this?
Well...
Inspector Zeman was investigating the station.
A-As a result...
he learned that both Detective Patera and Detective
Janacek were former Czechoslovakian secret police...
It is...
It is very unfortunate, but...
I believe Inspector Zeman accepted money...
in order to conceal the truth!
That is a very alarming problem.
l-lt is very unfortunate...
Detective Suk.
Yes, sir!
Please don't speak to anyone about this case just yet...
I will contact you later.
Return to your regular duties.
Yes, sir!
Oh, man...
Yeah...
This is becoming a problem...
We made a mistake by underestimating
someone as young as Suk...
We still haven't solved the case of
that toothpick killing Zeman...
And now another problem shows up...
Should we go with money again,
like we did with Zeman?
If that doesn't work, there's only one thing left, right?
Whatever the case may be...
I would like to avoid causing myself any trouble...
for letting,you both in, even though
I knew of your personal histories!
Hopefully, we can hush everything up...
I sure could use a drink right now!
I've got some whiskey bonbons!
Hey, don't be like that.
I got these from a very hot chick!
Here.
What's wrong?
You look depressed...
I can't trust anyone now...
What's wrong?
You can tell me, if you want...
I believed in him.
I never thought that Inspector Zeman, of all
people, would do something like that...
What happened?
I believed in him, and yet...
Right now...
the only peace in my heart...
is you.
Yes
Cherish what you know is true in this world
Ima kono sekai de wakaru koto mitsumete
Yes
Please believe in the kindness of your eyes
Anata no hitomi no yasashisa wo shinjite
Make it home to your land of harmony
Make it home to your land of purity
Make it home