Yes?
I'm sorry for disturbing you so early in the morning.
We're from the county police.
You are Dr. Tenma?
Can I help?
Excuse me for asking, but have you been here all night?
N-No, I was out drinking until morning...
Did something happen?
The truth is that Director Heinemann, Surgical Director
Oppenheim, and Dr. Boyer of Eisler Memorial Hospital...
...have all passed away.
In any case, we can't let anyone besides
the police enter the crime scene!
A Murder
But that'll hinder the management of the hospital!
Please, no media inside the hospital!
Please refrain from disturbing the patients!
So was it an accident, or murder?
Three people died at the same time.  Of course there's something behind it!
Are you part of the hospital staff?
Do you have any information regarding this incident?
Move!
Please let me through!
No one's allowed to enter!
I'm a doctor here, Kenzou Tenma!
Oh, please go ahead.
So, did you see anybody suspicious?
Please wait.  This is not the time to be...
Dr. Tenma!
Dr. Tenma, the director and the others are...!
Doctor!
Everyone, calm down!
Are the emergency cases under control?
T-Thing this is...
We're swamped with emergency cases right now!
At the moment, two patients are
waiting to be operated on.
Okay, I'll help out too.
Please take care of the car accident
victim with the head contusion.
I'll look over his pictures in the X-Ray room first.
What about the other case?
The patient suffered a stroke.
Oh, doctor!
May I ask for your cooperation in the investigation?
I don't have the time for that right now!
I understand, but the initial investigation
is the most crucial part of the process.
Do you know anyone who holds a grudge
against the director and the others?
A grudge?
The path of being the doctor you
dreamed of is closed to you.
Do you know something?
Uh... no.
Dr. Tenma!
This is terrible!
Those kids!
The twins!
I can't find them anywhere!
Is the sister's bed also empty?
I've already checked!
But I can't find her anywhere!
W-What is this?
What the hell... happened here...?!
He reached out to offer people the hand of salvation.
We will commend his lifetime
achievements for all eternity.
Farewell, Dr. Heinemann.
May you rest in peace.
Amen.
Father!
Eva...
Eva!
I know it's hard, but pull yourself together...
Don't touch me!
Give me back my father!
Father!
This is unbearable, Dr. Tenma.
Yeah...
She led an easy life as the daughter of a director.
But now, she's suddenly just a normal person.
It must be a pretty big shock for her.
How can you say that at a time like this?
Oh, excuse me.
You're Dr. Tenma, correct?
I'm Inspector Weissbach from the Nordrhein-Westfalen
Police Department.
Thank you for all your efforts.
You have my deepest condolences.
Let me introduce you two.
This is...
Inspector Lunge
Bundeskriminalamt
Note: The Bundeskriminalamt (BKA) is the German Federal Police, the German FBI.
I'm inspector Lunge from the BKA
I've heard rumors of the genius doctor.
No, I'm still young and inexperienced...
Umm.. you still don't have any leads as
to whereabouts of the children?
No, but we've discovered the cause of
death of the director and the others.
We've extracted a small amount
of nitric acid from their bodies.
Nitric acid?
You mean a muscle relaxant
As expected from a doctor, you're very familiar with it.
But how did something like that end up...
From candy.
Candy?
The same candy wrappers were found beside each body...
...and the same substance was found
in each of their stomachs.
So, do you have any ideas where
the three obtained the candy?
How should I know?
More importantly, how is the investigation of the twins progressing?
Jurisdiction on the investigation has been
passed down to us from the local police.
Please don't worry.
If we work back from this incident...
...we might find that it all leads to the moment of
the twins' parents were shot and killed.
After fleeing East Germany...
...their parents were shot, and the hospital
staff that treated were killed.
So there's a chance that it was a political terrorism.
Those children may hold a huge key to this case.
Please find them somehow.
We'll give it our best effort.
Excuse us.
The Japanese doctor...
...who was removed form his position
as chief by the director...
...and had his engagement to the director's daughter
canceled right before the incident, eh?
But that man has an alibi, since he was drinking
at a pub at the time the crime was committed...
Umm, may I ask you something?
Why does your hand move like that?
I'm hitting the keys.
I'm inputting all the information into the disk in my head.
If I hit the keys to retrieve the information...
"No, I'm still young and inexperienced."
Dr. Tenma was blushing and didn't know what
to say when I called him a genius doctor.
Inspectors, huh?
You sure you're not a suspect for the murder?
Well, they do have evidence that implicates
me, so it can't be helped.
Hey, don't worry about it.
They were bugging me with questions, too.
I feel tired for some reason.
Once this case cools off...
...I'm thinking of going back to Japan.
I came all the way to Germany intent
on doing some research, but...
...thanks to this string of incidents...
...I think I've realized that the primary
job of a doctor is to save lives.
Hey, don't say something sad like that.
I'm just tired...
So very tired...
Your progress looks excellent, Mr. Buchner.
Thank you very much, Dr. Tenma.
Will I be able to work again?
Yes, of course.
My store will be forced to close if I'm not there.
However, you mustn't push yourself too hard.
I'll stop by for a few drinks once you've been discharged.
So I can check to see if you're overworking yourself.
Dr. Tenma...
Yes?
Are the rumors about you leaving the hospital true?
Please, don't quit.
There aren't any other good doctors like you.
Please don't say that you're quitting.
Please!
Mr. Buchner...
Dr. Tenma, the board chairman is calling for you.
Right now, they're holding a conference
regarding the personnel reorganization.
Until now, the director's faction has always decided the major appointments...
...so I think there's going to be
a fairly big staff cleanup soon.
Rumor has it that Dr. Eckener is being
sent to a small hospital in Bayern...
I see...
Umm, Dr. Tenma!
Please try your best, no matter
what the chairman says to you!
We'll be cheering for you!
Please don't leave the hospital!
What?
Let me repeat.
I place merit on talent and ability.
Dr. Tenma...
I'm appointing you as the head of the surgical department.
What a life!
After disobeying the director's orders...
...being removed from my place as chief...
...having my engagement to Eva canceled...
...and choosing a path as a normal doctor, not caring abut promotions or anything...
What a...
What a life!
I'm sorry for calling you out like this.
I heard you were appointed as the
head of the surgical department.
I'm so happy for you!
Thanks...
Kenzou, at my father's funeral...
...you tried to comfort me, didn't you?
No...
I was so happy!
A lot of things happened between
us, but I want to start over.
Kenzou?
Kenzou!
Please, I'm sorry!
I want to start over!
Kenzou...
Kenzou!
Nine Years Later
About the patient with the spinal cord tumor...
His paralysis suddenly took a turn for the worse.
Understood.
I'll do the operation myself.
We're counting on you, doctor!
Prepare the operation.
Yes, sir!
Man, when will this flood recede?
I thought the world would change
once the Berlin Wall fell...
Köln,
Germany
...but nothing good ever happens.
They talk about the unification of Europe...
...but all that floats down here are piles of crap.
Yeah, the rate of unsolved crimes keeps rising.
Inspector, we're here!
Both of their bodies had their throats cut with a knife.
Their identities?
The Reichmann couple that lived on Stich Drive.
They were killed in their apartment.
We believe they were hidden in a closet, but
were washed out because of the flood.
Another middle-aged couple murder case...
In the past two years, there have been
four other cases across Germany...
...all done in the same way.
Probably just a thief going after
wealthy middle-aged couples.
No, it's too early to dismiss these as simple robberies.
For some reason, according to the data, none of the couples had any kids.
Right, this couple didn't have children, either.
Don't you think that assuming it's just
a robbery is a bit short-sighted?
But all the victims had their valuables taken.
Even so, the amount taken was minimal.
Although, it would make sense if this was the work of a single person.
Then you're saying that it wasn't
the work of a single person?
There were two incidents that occurred
inside locked houses with alarms.
However, the perpetrator bypassed them easily.
And none of the couples showed any signs
of struggles before they were killed.
On top of that, the neighbors, didn't hear a single
sound during the time of the murders.
Don't you think it's a bit too well-executed
to be a solo job?
Yeah...
Are you familiar with this man?
No.
Adolf Junkers, 23 years old.
Arrested twice on suspicion of theft.
His specialty is picking locks.
In other words, a so called locksmith.
During the previous middle aged couple murder cases...
...he was spotted near three separate crimes scenes.
Then he's the one who...!
I wonder...
Either, way this is all you local police need to do here.
Leave the rest to the BKA.
O-Okay...
Oh, I guess it can't be helped.
I've never flown a kite before.
You were so close.
So, how was the girl last night?
What do you mean by that?
She was nice.
Hey, hey.  She's the director's daughter.
Don't tell me you just left after dinner!
The truth is, I received an emergency call during dinner...
...and was called back to the hospital.
You what?!
Look, you have to forget this "work
is number one" ideology!
You're gonna regret it when you
let a fine girl slip past you!
Hey are you listening to me, doctor?!
Flying a kite, huh?
Good morning, doctor.
Is this yours, Karl?
My grandfather gave it to me.
But it just won't fly.
I wonder if the center is misaligned.
You know how to fly a kite, doctor?
I used to fly them a lot when I as a child in Japan.
Try raising it higher, Karl.
Like this?
Yes, that's it.
Now then...
I hope this works...
It flew!
All right!
Man...
If I were in his position, I'd have at least five lovers.
Seriously...
You're amazing, Dr. Tenma
You should try your best to get better.
Next time, you're going to fly it yourself.  Okay, Karl?
Yeah!
Today's operation will be a parasellar
meningioma extirpation
We're going with the right pterional approach.
Okay!
Watch carefully.
It's an operation done by the chief
surgeon himself, Dr. Tenma.
What an amazing operation!
The brain is barely retracting!
He really is a genius neurosurgeon.
You resident doctors should treat the brain with love.
Remember that well.
Oh, no!
This is horrible!
Ambulance! Somebody call an ambulance!
I-It wasn't me!
It's not my fault!
This man just jumped into the street!
This is the patient?
Yes.
What's his current condition?
Well, we can't really do anything...
He's an important witness in a case.
Depending on his testimony, we may
be able to solve a serial murder case.
We can't have him die on us like this.
But the patient in in critical condition.
We can't do anything at our hospital...
The best neurosurgeon is at Eisler Memorial Hospital.
If he comes here, then maybe...
A neurosurgeon?
Dr. Tenma, is it?
I'm sorry to have you come all
the way out here, Dr. Tenma.
What's the patient's condition?
He's currently in a state of delirium.
One of his pupils is dilated, as well.
It's been a while, Dr. Tenma.
I'm sorry, but who are you again?
It's been nine years.
We haven't met since the director's funeral.
Oh, you're from the BKA...
Inspector Lunge.
Please perform a successful operation
for the sake of the BKA.
The patient must live in order
for us to solve a murder case.
I'm not operating on him for the sake of the police.
I operate for the sake of the patient.
That's fine.
Now, I have an operation to conduct, so please excuse me.
I heard you've become the head of the
surgical department, Dr. Tenma.
You rose pretty high.
What about it?
No, it's just amazing, considering your age.
The position of director isn't far off, is it?
No, I still have a long way to go.
Regarding the murder that took place
at Eisler Memorial Hospital...
...the investigation is going rather slowly.
The only clue we have is the poisoned candy.
From this, we can only determine that
it was done by an intellectual.
An intellectual crime occurs when there's a connection
between the victim and the perpetrator.
What are you trying to say?
Nothing, excuse me.
In my line of work, I think about
this kind of stuff all year round.
However, please rest assured....
Not a single case I've been involved
with has gone unsolved.
Not a single one.
I'm looking forward to seeing the results.
We're going to open the skull and remove
the intra-cerebral hematomas.
If we don't hurry, the brain herniation will
advance and the patient will be in danger.
After the murder at Eisler Memorial Hospital...
...I can see only one person who benefited from the
incident, no matter how much I think about it.
Dr. Tenma, you're the only one.
Thank you for coming all the way out here.
Not a problem.  How's the patient doing?
He's conscious, but his right pupil is dilated.  The anesthesia is still affecting his left side somewhat, too.
He's already started to rehab routine, hasn't he?
His paralysis will eventually wear off.
Everything is going smoothly.
Also I think some police officers want to talk with him...
...but please turn them away for now.
But that Lunge person is very persistent.
The patient's recovery is top priority right now.
How are you feeling, Mr. Junkers?
Mr. Junkers, do you know who I am?
Can you see this finger?
How about it?
Can you answer me?
Yes?
What is it, Mr. Junkers?
...nster... coming...
Coming?  What's coming?
The monster... is coming...
Monster?