I must say, sir, that you have laid
eyes on a fine piece of property.
The best thing about this place is that it is only
twenty minutes from the center of Berlin.
Berlin
(Old East Germany Side)
Also, it has fine transportation facilities
and is in an excellent location.
You'll never find another estate quite
like this in old East Germany.
Excuse me...
I believe this is East German Trade
Adviser Liebert's former house...
Huh?
What?  You only came here to inquire about Mr. Liebert?
I thought you were a customer...
I'm sorry.
There is something I have to know, so...
I don't know anything about the government
official who passed away ten years ago.
The Lieberts took twins into custody when they lived here.
I told you, I don't know anything.
What about the man who owns this place...?
Can you introduce me to him?
Listen...
Most of the old East
German properties belong to
the wealthy Jews who
fled during the Nazi regime.
The Eastern government is paying foreign countries
as well as the West to rent the land.
This place's owner also resides in another country.
Besides...
Our real estate company in the West
expanded after the wall fell.
So we don't know anything about the old tales!
I'm locking the gate now, so please leave!
Does anyone know what happened ten years ago?
Would anyone remember Mr. Liebert?
Like I told you earlier...
...this was the residential district of the
former top government officials.
Once the wall fell, most of them fled for their lives.
Those who worked in the Ministry of Domestic Affairs
were especially threatened...
Oh, now that I think about it...
There should be a former East German Department of
Commerce official living ten houses down from here.
Oh, Mr. Liebert?
He didn't need to risk his life the way he did.
If he only had waited a little longer, East
Germany would have destroyed itself.
I don't understand why he went to
the country of freedom, anyway.
He was even murdered...
Did Mr. Liebert have twins?
Twins...?
Oh, I remember!
The twins Mr. Liebert adopted from the orphanage!
Orphanage?
They were such cute children...
Mr. Liebert always wanted children of his own.
W-Where is this orphanage?!
Uh, I think it was...
511...
Yeah, that is it.
I think it was Kinderheim 511.
Kinderheim... 511...
Kinderheim 511
This place used to be an orphanage,
but soon it will be a supermarket.
I feel so relieved knowing that this disturbing
building will finally be torn down.
Umm, excuse me!
Do you know where I can find the orphanage employees?
Employees...?
There aren't any left, of course!
I don't want to discuss this place.
Ah, this place gives me the chills!
E-Excuse me...
If you really want to hear about it...
...a man named Hartmann who used to work
in the Ministry of Health lives in No. 47.
Hey, does a man named Hartmann live around here?
What happened?
You are injured!
Let me see.
It is alright.  Don't be scared.
You got hurt in a place that was still healing.
It's festering.
Bear with it.
It stings a little, but this will help you get better.
Alright, you are all set.
Don't trip now!
You will get hurt again.
Hartmann...
I took all those children in and became their
foster parent after the wall came down.
Foster parent...?
Yes.  I raised those children until they were adopted or could live on their own.
The child in the middle was adopted by the president
of a company that makes clothing and accessories.
The child on the left is currently in the military.
I'm taking care of one right now, as a matter of fact.
It must be hard work.
I don't know if I would call it work or what...
I was a government official and in charge of the Ministry of
Health and Welfare in this district for a long time.
...and I worked with the orphanage a lot.
I've been against the government since that time.
Ever since socialism collapsed, I thought
I could help the children in my own way.
Since I'm poor, though, it is not going as I had planned...
However, they are still much better off
than when they were in the orphanage.
Kinderheim 511 was...
...a special orphanage under the cooperative jurisdiction...
...of the Ministry of Health and Welfare
and the Ministry of Home Affairs.
Well, the orphanages of the Old East
Germany were mostly like that.
Amongst them, the special orphanages were the worst.
It wasn't just a facility for children
who didn't have a place to go.
It was a collection of children with criminal records...
...children of parents who committed political
crimes when they tried to escape...
...and children of parents were charged
with rebellion or espionage.
That is why they were subjected to discrimination
and treated inhumanely.
The children couldn't fight back, no matter what was inflicted.
That place was the very contradiction
of socialism and totalitarianism!
In their propaganda, the government said...
...that they would re-educate the children
to become the models of socialism.
But in reality, they treated them like criminals.
On top of that, the director and educators were horrible.
the worst would even confiscate and
sell packages sent to the children.
I wonder who the real criminals were...
Fear and violence controlled the special orphanages...
It was impossible to raise a normal person there.
And then... that incident occurred.
Incident?
What happened at that orphanage?
You said you wanted to ask me about those twins, right?
You know something about them?
I don't know much about the sister, since she was
placed in an orphanage in another district.
However...
...I know a good deal about her brother, Johan.
Johan...
That is right!  I want to ask you about Johan!
T-That was...
That was top secret.
The government of East Germany
issued a gag order regarding it.
W-Well, it is all in the past now...
So I don't think it would matter it I
talked about the incident, but...
What happened?
Johan...
What did Johan do?
He led an uprising.
I'm home.
Oh, Dieter. We have a guest.
Say hi.
What is with that attitude, Dieter?!
Greet him properly!
I-It is fine.
We met in front of the house earlier.
Right?
Anyway, about what we were just talking about...
Please, I don't want to discuss that in front of the child.
Yes, you are right.
It is getting late, so I will stop by again some other time.
Dieter!
Would you like to have dinner with us?
S-Sure.
Mr. Tenma, since you are a freelance journalist...
...you are going to write an article about
the things you are researching, right?
Y-Yeah...
Then please make sure you write down this point.
The growth of a child depends entirely
on the adult raising him.
We must lead our children down the right path.
And then, for the first time, the children
can have wonderful dreams.
Dreams, huh...
What kind of dreams do you have, Dieter?
A soccer ball...
What?
I want a soccer ball.
I see.
Thank you for the food.
I would like to continue our conversation
at another time, if you don't mind.
Sure.
Our conversation was interrupted.
I'll stop by again.
I'll contact you tomorrow.
Dieter...
Excuse me, sir.
Mind if I take a look around?
Mr. Hartmann!
It's Tenma!
Mr. Hartmann.
Mr. Hartmann!
What is wrong, Mr. Hartmann?!
Mr. Tenma!
Dieter?
What happened?!
He fell.
He was on the chair, and then...
Oh, Dieter!
It hurts...
It hurts... it hurts!
Where does it hurt, Dieter?
It hurts!
Mr. Hartmann, call an ambulance!
O-Okay!
Let me take a look, Dieter.
What are all these bruises?!
Here?
Does it hurt here?
He's broken two of his ribs...
On top of that...
...he's dislocated his left shoulder.
How can all of this occur from falling off a chair?
The ambulance will be here shortly.
So everything should be alright now.
O-Okay.
But what are these injuries from?
I said everything is okay now, didn't I?
So please leave.
But...
And you...
...the way you touch the injuries...
It is as if you are a doctor.
No, I...
Tenma...
No wonder that name sounded familiar.
You are a doctor, aren't you?
The one wanted for murder.
These injuries...
Where did he get all these injuries?!
More importantly, Mr. Tenma...
Don't you think you should start running?
I called the police along with an ambulance.
Mr. Hartmann!
I'm asking you how Dieter got these injuries!
It doesn't matter to a murderer and a fugitive
like yourself, does it?
I expect nothing less from a fugitive.
You have a short temper.
You did this to him, didn't you?
Did... what?
You are abusing Dieter.
Abusing?
I wish you would not phrase it like that.
Right, Dieter?
What are you planning to do?
I'm taking him to a hospital.
First murder, now kidnapping?
Don't move!
You know you will be caught quickly if you do that, right?
Don't worry, Dieter!
I'm taking you to a hospital now!
I'm scared... of hospitals...
There is nothing to be scared of.
The doctors will help you.
Mr. Hartmann always... treats the pain...
Even though you are hurt all over...
...you haven't been to a hospital?!
I'm scared...
The world is full of bad things...
That is why I have to be strong.
I have to be strong...
Did Mr. Hartmann tell you that?
The world is in an abyss...
That is not true.
That the world is in an abyss is the biggest lie!
Really?
Yeah, it is true.
Oh, I forgot.
Here, I got you a soccer ball.
Tomorrow will definitely be a good day.
I'm sorry for asking, this late at night.
That is fine, but we are bogged down with emergency
cases, so it will take some time to treat him.
Please, can't you do something about that?
But there was a really big accident, and...
The bus driver died instantly.
We would like to ask the truck driver about the accident.
He can still talk even with both feet broken, right?
His treatment comes first.
Please conduct the investigation later.
Then we will wait right here.
I will be back in about two hours.
Please take care of that boy.
Also, if someone other than myself
comes to pick up the boy...
...don't release him.
Please.
H-Hey!
Is the scene of the accident all cleared up?
No, it is still congested.
Now then...
...what should I do...?
First, I have to find a place for Dieter to stay.
Even if I turned him over to the police...
...I can't go with him.
I don't know much...
...about the sister, since she was placed
in an orphanage in another district.
Another orphanage?
That's it!
You have a child you want us to take in?
So, who are you?
Why did you come at such a late hour?
I know what I'm asking is absurd.
But that child is...
I understand that he is being abused.
But if I don't who you are, then...
Umm, that is ...
We can't take in a child from someone we don't know.
E-Excuse me!
But could this be the orphanage Anna Liebert attended?
Anna Liebert?
You know Anna Liebert?
S-So Anna was here?!
Yes, it brings back so many memories.
How is Anna doing?
Is she well?
Y-Yeah...
She is currently attending Heidelberg College.
I see!
So she found happiness!
Anna was such a good girl.
I knew her only until she was taken in
by Foreign Trade Adviser Liebert.
Along with her brother, too.
Let's see, what was his name...
It is Johan.
Yes, it was Johan!
The two got along very well, but...
...they were sent to two different
orphanages.  I felt sorry for them.
Before the came here, they really were alone.
Even when they were found near
the border of Czechoslovakia...
...I heard they were walking together, hand in hand.
Both shivering from the cold...
When Mr. Liebert said he was going to take in a child...
...it was only being to be Johan at first.
But Johan would only go if his sister was with him.
Thanks to him, Anna was able to find happiness.
I heard the orphanages in East Germany
were horrible at the time...
Don't compare us to Kinderheim 511.
Inge, that is not the way to the bathroom.
Okay?
Mama!
It's okay.  It's okay.
There is nothing to be scared of.
Now then, you can go to the bathroom by yourself, right?
These children don't know the love of their true parents.
You need love in order to mature as a human.
As you said, the orphanages in East
Germany at the time were terrible.
This place used to be called Orphanage No. 47, as well...
But even so, we still tried our best
to make something happen.
Tried to go against the government, even slightly.
So we wouldn't turn out to be like Kinderheim 511.
That place was a special orphanage
under the cooperative jurisdiction...
...of the Ministry of Health and Welfare
and the Ministry of Home Affairs...
Do you know what that means?
No.
All the internal conditions were monitored
by the Ministry of Domestic Affairs.
Because that place was old East Germany's...
...testing facility.