No matter how many times you come, the answer will always be the same!
The MP never had relations with that prostitute!
MP is Member of Parliament
Furthermore, there is no way he would ever kill anyone!
Please leave!
If you keep pestering me, I have
ways of keeping you quiet.
You have ways?
Are you going to charge me with slander or something?
No, a secretary like you wouldn't do such a thing.
I'm sure you don't want Dr. Borzmann's
name to come up in a case like this.
Are you threatening me?
Of course not.
I just want to know the truth.
He's a tough nut to crack.
The Only Man Left * The Only Woman Left
No wonder he's a major politician's top secretary.
No we just need to pursue this further.
But I don't think a big shot like Borzmann would
lay his hands on a prostitute like her.
The victim wasn't your ordinary prostitute...
Several figures in the financial world
can be connected to her.
But only one person saw her at
the hotel Borzmann stayed at.
With that much to go on, I don't think we can
prove anything was going on between them...
How is decoding of her client list progressing?
The truth is, the floppy has an enumerated
password, so it's giving us a hard time.
I'll do it.
Give me the floppy.
Okay, but aren't you busy with
other cases as well, Inspector?
Does not matter, just give it to me.
Umm, there is something I've been meaning to ask you...
What is it?
When do you sleep?
What does that have to do with this case?
That is an irrational question.
When are you going to talk to him about it?
He has never listened to us before.
But the sooner the better!
Hey, you are being too loud.
He is in his room, you know...
Oh, that is unusual.
The Bundeskriminalamt (BKA) is the German Federal Police (German FBI counterpart)
Hey, Lunge!
I heard you are still poking about
the murder of that prostitute...
...and her relationship with MP Borzmann.
Is there a problem?
Yeah, a big one!
We are bing pressured by the higher ups from
the Ministry of Domestic Affairs.
Then please take care of your side as usual, chief.
No, I can't cover up the case this time.
I'm counting on you.
Hey, Lunge!
What if this investigation turns out to be a mistake?
You have led a distinguished career up until now.
You don't need to be so aggressive on this one.
Or what?
You are thinking of doing this for justice?
Aggressiveness...
Justice...
I'm not interested in either.
A woman was killed.
I am only interested in the killer.
Lunge!
Excuse me, Inspector Lunge.
You have a guest.
Finished.
I've deciphered the password to her list of clients.
Now I can convert the list to real names.
Oh, okay.
So anyway she is here again...
That Eva Heinemann person...
Hey, don't come back here without permission!
Just when will Tenma be arrested?
Looks like you have been drinking heavily again.
How could I not drink?
Regarding Dr. Tenma's case...
...I consider it solved for the time being.
He says that everything is the work
of a man named "Johan," but...
...this "Johan" is actually another personality inside of him.
Even though that case may seem unreasonable at first...
...it can be solved rationally if you think about it like this.
All that is left is to wait for the police to
capture him somewhere in the country.
You mean your job is finished once
you put out an arrest warrant?
I have many things I would like to ask him if we meet.
Because Dr. Tenma is a fascinating character.
However, there is a pile of cases on my desk that need me.
Excuse me.
You are too persistent!
Like I have always said many times...
...the MP has an alibi for that night!
An alibi?
Of course.
Because that was the work of a pro.
Then, what?
Are you trying to imply that the MP
hired a professional?
That is absurd!
I've deciphered the murdered woman's client list.
The MP's name was included.
So what if his name was on it?
What would his motive have been to murder her?
Well, that is as far as we have gotten so far...
I'm tired of this!
Go away!
So that wasn't evidence, huh?
Are you familiar with the Scherhon Publishing Company?
That company releases books exposing scandals
from time to time, as it helps them get by.
On top of that, the company's methods
are rather unscrupulous.
They hire indecent women...
...to develop relationships with famous people,
...and then have them document about it.
You should be more cautious.
If felt like checkmate.
Even that secretary was speechless.
I was really surprised, myself.
It is as if he is superhuman.
Superhuman, eh?
Perhaps, he is not really human.
Oh, that is right.
It is checkmate if I go there!
Hey, hey!  Don't interrupt someone's game...!
Don't waste your mind a stupid game.
The president of that publishing company...
...spit everything out after that little scare.
Get the preliminary memo.
Y-Yes, sir!
Do you know what this is?
It is the memo about that prostitute.
Every little detail has been documented
about her secret affair with a man.
I don't know the name of that man...
...other than that it starts with the letter B.
Also, the Scherhon Publishing Company...
...had a contract with her to publish her life story.
Oh, I almost forgot.
Have you ever had contact with a man named Janker?
I believe he is an assassin.
Get out.
Get the hell out!
We are moving out.
You didn't know I was pregnant, did you, father?
You are going to your man's place?
I'm going with her.
You didn't know I had a lover, did you?
Yes.
Inspector, it's me.
Borzmann's secretary, Mintach.
I'll tell you everything.
Please come over.
Oh, is that so?
That is good to hear.
I'm going out.
I'll listen to the details when I get back.
I-Inspector!
What is the commotion?
The secretary committed suicide!
"MP Borzmann is innocent..."
This is the note the secretary left.
Lunge, Inspector Kaminsky will be taking over this case.
The Reik Park case and the President
Garland murder case, too.
In that case, what should I do?
You don't have anything left.
Looks like you are all I have left.
E-Excuse me, Inspector...
You have a guest.
That Eva Heinemann person is here again.
Let her in.
I had a good time, Eva.
When can we see each other again?
Let's see...
I'll stop by again after my next business trip.
No, I don't want you to go back to your wife!
Anyway, I'll call you.
You might never come back again.
Because I put a handkerchief soaked
with my perfume in your bag.
What an insignificant man...
You were looking at me again, weren't you?
Are you wondering why I always bring
different men into my house?
N-No...
You wish you could be like them, don't you?
Of course not...
How disgusting!
N-No, I was just...
Oh, it is so beautiful.
I love this garden.
If I just drift off while looking at the garden...
...I feel like I can forget all the bad things.
I'm glad that you like it!
I'm going to plant a mimosa here.
And I'm going to make an arch of roses over there.
When summer comes, it will be very...
Perhaps a man like you can do it..
Do you have the confidence to make me happy?
Dad?
Dad, are you listening to me?
Hey, Dad!
H-How is your dad's cooking today?
You haven't heard a word I have said.
That is why mom left for some other guy.
I'm sorry...
No, it is okay.
The thing is, Coletta...
What if your dad...
...I ...I liked someone, and...
Ah, nothing... it is nothing!
Tonight's dinner isn't that good, is it?
It's not bad.
I see.  It's not bad, huh?
Sorry to trouble you.
Sorry for making a gardener like you do this.
No, it is okay.
All my other servants left me, complaining
that they wanted more free time.
If I can help in any way, feel free to ask me.
So, how about dinner tonight?
W-Well, I, uh...
S-Sure...
Why are you so nervous?
I'm not comfortable in these high class places...
If you want to become a man worthy of me, you
need to be confident everywhere you go.
Just like when you are working in my garden.
O-Okay.
Y-You are right.
I'm really confident about myself when I'm in the garden.
When the garden is how I imagined
it to be, I become overjoyed.
I'm happiest when I'm in the garden.
Anyone who likes gardens can't be bad.
You said you loved that garden also...
Are you saying that I'm a good person?
Yes, of course!
It is just that...
What?
No, it is just that you...
...seem very lonely...
You, too.
You are lonely also, aren't you?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I think my daughter might be worried about me, so...
Kenzou...
It is almost Christmas, Coletta.
Santa Claus better not push himself too hard this year.
Hey, hey.
You don't have to worry about something like that...
A Christmas party with just the
two of us is gonna be lonely.
You don't have to push yourself.
Well, it might not be just the two of us.
That is the man who ruined my life.
I-I'm sorry!  I was just cleaning, and...
His name is Kenzou Tenma, my former fiancé.
Y-You're drinking this early again...
How can I not drink?
I just came back from the BKA.
I went to see an inspector named Lunge.
That man!
Despite being worthless, he dared to turn me away!
When are they going to arrest Tenma, huh?
The BKA?
Arrest?
He killed my father and ran away!
He said he was falsely accused,
but don't give me that crap!
I was the daughter of the director of a big
hospital, and had my future planned out!
My three failed marriages are his fault, too!
"It was all Johan's doing," my ass!
Look at this!
The kid with my father is Johan!
You think a kid like that could kill my father?
Tenma said that?
That is just a stupid excuse!
Did you show this picture to the police?
Of course!
It might be crucial evidence!
Tenma is the one who did it!
It is just as Inspector Lunge said!
Tenma has multiple personalities!
Then...
Why are you displaying his pictures like this?
Deep down, you don't think Tenma is the killer.
And you still love Tenma...
I think you have watched too many soap operas!
He was just the man who was most worthy of me.
An elite neurosurgeon who was said to be a genius...
He had enough praise heaped upon him.
And more than anything, this man didn't talk back to me.
He listened to all my selfish needs!
"Yes!  Yes!  Yes!"
He was a man who said "yes" to everything!
This man was supposed to make me
the happiest woman in the world!
I... can't be a substitute for him...?
I can make gardens for you for the rest of my life...
If that will ease your heart, then I...
Don't get so carried away just
because I slept with you once!
You are just something to help pass my spare time!
I was just messing around with you.
Don't get so full of yourself.
You are so stupid!
Who do you think you are?
You really are...
You really are a lonely woman...
You, too!
I'm having a party with my daughter
at my house on Christmas.
You are welcome to come.
This dinner is amazing!
Did you make all of this yourself?
Yeah, though I can't guarantee it will taste all right.
But isn't this too much for the two of us?
Y-You think so?
Mom is coming back!
That is it, right?
That has to be it!
Coletta...
Mom is home!
Cha...
Charlotte...
Mom!
Honey, I'm sorry...
I'm so sorry...
A mimosa, my ass!
Screw the roses!
Look at your beautiful garden now!
And to hell with a hospital director's mansion!
Everything should burn!
Everything!
Welcome.
Looks like you have finally decided to seriously listen
to what I have to say, Inspector Lunge?
I just happen to have some free time.
This is the only man for me!
Until I stop this man's breathing...
...I can't be happy!