Now then, ladies and gentlemen...
What was the basis for the ruling the judge made
regarding the events in Stuttgart in 1986
My, my.  Silence?
Is this some sort of Oriental Zen temple or something?
Mr. Eimer!
I would like to hear your answer.
Well, that is, uh...
All right, can anyone break this silence?
Looks like the criminally late has decided to show up.
You're thirteen minutes late today.
It appears your part time pizza delivery
job was especially busy today.
I'm sorry, Professor Kronecker.
Now then...
Before you take your seat, let me ask you a question.
Do you have enough stamina left to analyze...
...the basis for the judge's ruling
on the events of Stuttgart in 1986?
What?
Oh, yes.
That is...
...the defendant claimed that the
kidnapping was the objective...
...and the death of the victim was accidental.
After carefully examining the situation...
...it was concluded that the murder was indeed accidental.
Therefore, because the murder was a crime of passion...
...I believe the murderer was merely
sentenced to fifteen years in prison.
Excellent.
Go ahead and take your seat, Ms. Nina Fortner.
Yes, Professor.
Heidelberg,
Germany
You saved us.
It's all thanks to you, Nina.
The Girl From Heidelberg
If nobody had said anything...
...that demon Kronecker would have
assigned another fifty page essay.
Fifty pages may be underestimating him.
We should treat Nina for saving our lives.
How about today, Nina?
Just the two of us!
Nina Fortner
I'm sorry, Peter.
I have to go to my club.
See you later!
You were rejected again.
How many times does that make now, Peter?
Shut up!
I'd like to meet the man who can catch Nina
I give up!
Oh, no!
The boss is really gonna yell at me again if I'm late on the delivery!
I'm home!
Oh, I'm so hungry!
The neighbors can hear you.
Don't you think you're too old to be saying things like that?
Go wash your hands.
Okay.
Huh?  Did you dye your hair, mom?
Doesn't it look good?
Seriously...
Why did you have to dye it blond at your age?
Don't say that, Dad.  It suits her.
It's not like she's in a costume parade or anything.
Don't you like how Mom always looks so young?
I'm back, Dad.
Oh, speaking of costume parades...
...the children were all dressed up in costumes today.
Oh, that must be for St. Adrian's costume parade.
I wanted to dress up like that when I was little.
It looks so cute!
You did dress up.
Right, honey?
O-Oh, yeah.  That's right.
Let's see...
It was around here somewhere...
Oh, I found it.
Here it is.
You're right.
You made such a big fuss, since you were so excited.
Right, honey?
Yeah, that's right.
A costume parade, huh?
"The distant spring."
"I am tired of waiting for the spring that will never come."
Hanna.
Hanna should just get over her breakup already.
"I will give you the world's most beautiful flower."
"I was born to bury you with flowers."
Wow!  I wonder who sent that one?
You're pretty slick, Peter.
How have you been feeling, Nina?
I'm doing really great thanks to you, Dr. Geitel!
That's good to hear.
Although I saw you were in a good mood from the look
on your face when you entered the counseling room.
So...
You've stopped having that dream?
The dream where a monster rises out of the darkness.
Yeah.
Lately, I've been sleeping so soundly that
I haven't even had time to dream.
I wonder why I was haunted by that dream everyday...
Everybody becomes insecure during
their time as a student.
One's dreams and anxieties about
the future mix together...
...and one's identity becomes lost.
You can spend a lifetime searching, but
you'll never know who you really are.
We do our best to live for the future...
...while trying to look for the answer.
Right!  I'm doing my best!
My dream is to become a prosecutor!
That's the spirit.
All right, let's end our counseling session here for today.
Thank you very much!
Sure.
Nina Fortner...
She's such a bright girl.
But I can't shake the feeling that her brightness is only
an indication that she's running away from something.
From a great darkness...
What?
What do you mean, "what"?
Quit playing dumb.
What are you talking about?
"I was born to bury you with flowers."
I never thought you had the talent to write such poetry.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Those words wouldn't come out of me even
if you flipped me upside down and shook.
Then who...?
I've only given my email address to friends.
Who knows?
Damn it!
All I know is that another rival has
appeared in pursuit of my love.
I wonder who?
Regarding the bizarre murder case in München...
...the perpetrator, after first shooting
the parents with a gun...
...strangled the two children to death with a rope.
Now then...
...can you give us an analysis on the judge's
ruling from the trial records...
...Ms. Nina Fortner?
Do you not understand my question?
N-No...
Umm, the focus of the trial was the verdict...
...and the massacre..
...of the... entire family...
...the... evidence...
Even you can't answer a question sometimes, Nina?
Nina?
What's wrong, Nina?
Nina!
Are you okay?
Do you want to go to the infirmary?
I-I'm okay...
I just felt a little sick, that's all.
I suddenly felt dizzy... after hearing
what the professor said...
You mean the family massacre case?
Stop it!
Oh, I thought you were pretty strong, but...
...you turned out to be kind of delicate.
Did you watch a really scary movie
when you were little or something?
I bet that counselor of yours would say something like...
"If you trace it back to its roots, it is nothing big."
"Now, try to remember your childhood."
Something like that.
I...
...don't have any memories...
I don't have any memories from before I was ten.
My memories...
...of my childhood...
Memories...
Köln,
Germany
Yes...
Both parents were really nice people.
I can't believe they were killed like that...
Their children?
Now that you mention it, they did have a son.
I think his name was Michael.
He lived with them for about two years.
A boy?
Was there such a child?
Yes, there was.
I think his name was Michael.
He was about fourteen.
Michael?
I think there was a boy by that name.
So, what about him?
Are you with the police or something?
Yes, Michael Reichmann.
He was indeed in my class.
But...
He wasn't a very impressionable child.
I'm embarrassed to say this, but
I don't remember him very well.
I don't even know if he had any friends...
Also, we don't have any records of him.
Unfortunately, there was a fire six years ago.
It seems that a child named Michael...
Did actually live in Köln until six years ago.
And Michael's real name is...
Johan, huh?
I guess there were times when I was called by that name.
Who are you?
But... what good does knowing that do for me?
Even if I knew, he's still the elder of
the twins, and a mass murderer.
Nothing else.
What am I doing?
Twins?!
Where's his sister?
Where is the younger sister?!
"I'm coming to pick you up soon."
Who is it?
Coming to pick me up?
What does that mean?
A boy?
Oh, yes. There was one.
I think it was about seven or eight years ago.
Mr. and Mrs. Heinau were raising a
boy before they were killed, right?
What kind of child was he?
What do you mean?
It was a long time ago.
And they lived together for only about a year or so.
I don't remember anything.
Did he have a younger sister with him?
It was only the boy.
Anyway, I just want to forget about
the incident with that couple.
I almost moved away because of it back then.
I know about that boy.
Why don't you come up?
I'm about to make some tea.
Have a seat.
O-Okay.
Please excuse me.
I am...
Have a seat.
Have some tea.
Thank you.
You're a doctor, right?
I heard it from that boy.
You're Dr. Tenma, right?
Someone is coming to pick you up?
Who?
I don't know.
Someone sent me an anonymous email.
You look happy.
I hope you're not hoping for a prince on
a white horse to come pick you up.
Jealous?
She's got her head in the clouds again.
"I was born to buy you with flowers."
I didn't think anybody wrote like that nowadays.
Hey, speaking of which...
There's been a new guy sitting in our lectures lately.
Oh, yeah!
He sits in the legendary seat in room 12 where
the professor will definitely call on you.
And yet, the professor never calls on him.
Right, right.  And do you know what?
He's been staring at you the whole time, Nina.
It must be him!
What?
Isn't it obvious?
He's your prince on the white horse!
He was very grateful to you, Dr. Tenma.
He said you saved his life, and were therefore
more important than his parents.
What did he call himself?
Franz.
But he said that wasn't his real name.
He opened his heart so much that he even told you that?
He just appeared out of nowhere.
He was raised for about a year by the Heinau couple, who
didn't have any children, in the place across from here.
No, to be more precise...
It was fourteen months, from March
of 1987 to April of 1988.
Then one day, he suddenly disappeared.
He was an extremely smart child.
He was also very polite.
He came to this room?
Everyday.
Since I live alone, I always welcomed him.
He used to sit in that chair...
...and just continued with his studies.
He quickly mastered the English
and French that I taught him.
He was able to speak both languages
fluently by the time he disappeared.
And he was only twelve.
Can you recall anything else about him?
He diligently listened to everything I had to say.
What type of stories do you think he
showed the greatest interest in?
Stories of war.
War?
In World War II...
...I served on a U Boat in the navy.
The story he wanted to hear the most...
...was the one about the time when we
were attacked by an Allied destroyer.
Traveling at 120 meters below the sea...
...after being attacked by the enemy...
...we still continued to dive deeper
after sustaining critical damage.
Within the ship, under pressure by
the water, we endured our fears.
Thirty-eight hours later, we returned from that living hell.
Any normal child...
...would have enjoyed this story as an adventurer.
But he was different.
What he showed the most interest in...
...was the fear.
The ultimate fear.
They kind of reactions people have when
they are on the brink of death.
That was all he was interested in.
He was toying with fear.
What kind of...
What kind of expression did he have
while he listened to your story?
He probably had sparkling eyes and a grin on his face.
Probably?
Well, I can't see.
That's right.
I don't know that child's real name,
nor do I know what he looks like.
You said that he opened his heart
to me earlier, didn't you?
He will never open his heart to anyone.
There is only one person he truly opened his heart to.
And that is his younger sister.
I... I'm looking for that girl!
He said he was going to get her when she turned twenty.
Where?
Heidelberg.
I'm going!
Be careful on your bike!
Okay!
Dad, I'm going now.
Okay.  Be careful.
I'm going!
It's about time, huh?
But...
We decided, remember?
That we'd tell her on her twentieth birthday.
That she isn't our daughter.
H-Hey, I don't like this.
What are you talking about?  You
said you wanted to meet him.
We talked him into meeting you here.
I hope you do well with your prince on his white horse.
See you later!
Hey, Clara!  Baerde!
Why did they do this without asking me first?
Hey, look!
Here he comes!
H-Hello, are you Nina Fortner?
Y-Yes.
Umm, I'm Otto Huberman.
H-Hello.
Who?
Who are you?
Where have... I seen him before?
Who...
...are you?
Nina!
Nina?
What's wrong?  Are you okay?
Nina!
Hey, hang on!
Hang on, Nina!
Nina!
Nina, are you okay?!