What is it?
What happened?
Over there, too?!
A short circuit?!
Fire!
Get the fire extinguisher!
Hurry!
What's going on?
My job was to shoot Schuwald.
What's with this fire?
I get it now!
You must have changed your mind Johan!
This is better!
This is much better!
Ants...
They're all like ants running away from the fire!
Amazing! This is amazing, Johan!
This is marvelous!
Why don't you take a look, too?
The books!
All the books will burn!
They're all running around...
They're trampling one another, as if each
is more important than the rest...
Can you feel it?
The fear in the air?
Whether he can kill his first person or not...
that is where the path splits.
Between whether he can use a gun or not, that is.
Were you taught how to shoot a gun?
No...
So you were self-taught.
I've never fired a gun before.
Not even once?
No.
Always pull the trigger twice!
Your chance of killing your
target will rise dramatically!
if you can't do that..
don't expect to survive.
I have to shoot...
That's impossible for you.
You can't shoot.
I have to... shoot...
You're just a doctor.
You can only give life.
Taking life is my job.
You can't do it.
Always pull the trigger twice!
The Monster In My Sight
I... wasn't shot...
The trembling... has stopped...
Johan!
There's too much smoke!
Hurry!
I have to hurry!
He won't get away again...
I won't...
Help me!
It won't open from this side!
Open up!
Please open!
Please calm down!
Everyone, please calm down and act rationally!
Please listen to the security guards and line up...
I-It's no use!
The doors are all locked!
What?!
O-Okay, escort Mr. Schuwald
out of here, at least!
Yes, sir!
Have you secured an evacuation route?
Or are you going to take Mr. Schuwald
through the sea of fire?
Knock down the doors!
Yes, sirl
So many books are burning...
The flames are trying to engulf everything.
Is that all you wanted to do?
Are you satisfied with simply presenting
this image of hell to me...
the same way you showed me things
when you read books to me?
Wasn't your aim...
to become my replacement?
I decided against that.
Something else came to mind.
You're not scared, are you?
Where did you come from?
Who are you?
Can you see me?
Even though you can barely see
if I get this close to you...
Can you see...
what's reflected in my eyes?
I was born in a fairy tale country.
So many people were dead.
I was walking through that place,
holding hands with my other half.
It was like we were the only
two left in the world...
We didn't have names.
Nina!
You are...
Dieter...
Do you know this girl?
A fire...
Karl...
I forgot a document.
Can you go get it for me?
Go back to the mansion and get it for me.
It's on the desk in my study.
Here it is.
Mom...
T-This is...!
Inquiry report concerning the
death of Margot Langer.
Helfrich Detective Company.
Margot Langer...
Real name, Helenka Novakowa.
Born on August 1955 in
Prague, Czechoslovakia.
In 1970, at the age of fifteen she illegally immigrated
to the former Federal Republic of Germany.
She worked as a so-called
high-class call girl in Munich:
Her clients consisted mainly of
politicians and businessmen...
and her name became secretly
known among the upper class.
Her clients included the one who ordered this
investigation, Mr. Hans Georg Schuwald.
Father...
I see you're still investigating Mom...
At the age of twenty-two, she gave
birth to Mr. Schuwald's child...
The name of the boy...
was Karl.
Listen closely to what Mom has to say, okay, Karl?
Take this money and take the train on track five.
What about you?
I told you, I can't go with you.
I want to stay with you!
No!
If you stay with me, you'll be put in a foster home!
If you stay here, people will say
you're the son of a prostitute!
Now, hurry!
What about my dad?
She said I was abandoned by my father...
You weren't abandoned...
I don't hate him.
Mom!
The boy went from one foster home to another.
He suffered a good deal.
He had wonderful foster parents...
but he was lonely.
He was always lonely.
I guess they didn't mention
anything about that in here...
Afterwards, Margot Langer remained
a high-class prostitute...
but retired in '92.
Also, before she withdrew from the business...
there are indications that she became involved
with the president of the "Bank of Darkness"...
but this has not been confirmed.
As a side note...
the Bank of Darkness laundered money for the
German underground for five years starting in '91.
In other words it was a nickname
for a black market organization...
that, held, a monopoly on the process
of taking large sums of dirty money...
and exchanging it for safe, legal money.
After retiring from being a prostitute...
Margot Langer lived in Offenbach, Hesse.
This is a photo of her apartment at the time.
It is said that she lived together with
an eighteen year old man...
but the details of their relationship are unknown.
On November 2, 1995...
Margot Langer's body was found on Heide Street.
According to the police file...
it was a random murder...
and the killer was never arrested.
Mom...
Now...
Three months before Margot Langer's death...
she sent a letter to her friend,
and I was able to obtain it.
I've attached a copy with this report.
So this...
is my mom's handwriting?
I've quit my job and am now living
a quiet, peaceful life.
The only things I think about in this quiet life...
are the son I had to part with...
and my friend who tried to cross the
Czechoslovakian border with me.
She was caught at the border...
and was forcibly dragged back to Prague.
Afterwards, she gave birth to twins,
and is now living happily.
Oh, yes.
Recently, I met a young man about the
same age as the son I left behind.
He looks exactly like my Czechoslovakian friend.
When I'm with that young man
it's like I'm talking to my son...
I'm sure he's grown into a fine man like him.
I'm sure he's living happily somewhere.
That's what I believe.
I'm okay, Mom...
I'm not lonely anymore...
Dad wanted me to read this letter.
The reason she said she didn't hate Dad...
I finally understand now.
I'm okay now, Mom.
I now have...
How is this possible?
Every door is locked!
Dieter, did you call the fire department yet?!
I already did!
Damn it!
What's going on in there?
Move.
Move away from the door!
It opened!
Don't rush!
One at a time! Slowly!
Form a line and go out one by one!
Let the women and the elderly go first!
Thank you!
I don't know how we can ever repay you...
Two bullets left...
Hey, you!
Johan!
Don't!
You mustn't shoot, Dr. Tenma!
Nina?!
D-Don't, Nina!
Don't!
Shit!
Don't shoot...
Don't shoot, Nina!
Nina!
Yes
Cherish what you know is true in this world.
Ima kono sekai de wakaru koto mitsumete
Yes
Please believe in the kindness of your eyes
Anata no hitomi no yasashisa wo shinjite
Make it home to your land of harmony
Make it home to your land of purity
Make it home