Those Neo Nazis are trying to burn down the town!
That Turkish woman had already been killed.
We will be arriving shortly at the place indicated by Johan.
I don't know what will happen...
You know how to use a gun, right?
Go to Frankfurt!
Take me to Calvin Street!
I thought you were going to kill Johan?
That is for later.
Hurry up and go!
I'm sure General Wolf will be disappointed...
...since after acknowledging your skills, he
commissioned you to eliminate Johan...
Commissioned?
Nobody commissions me.
I'll kill Johan of my own volition!
Just go to Calvin Street for now!
Reunion
I've just received word that preparations for the fire are complete.
Good work.
This celebration of our superior race must
be wreathed in glorious flames.
Yes, sir!
Now then...
What should we do with them?
There are people like them even in a superior race.
One is a thief...
As for the boy...
...he tried to inform the Turkish people about our actions.
They are both trash.
We must purify them.
I completely agree.
Since we are going to burn this place down anyway...
There, there.  Don't cry.
I'm sure your mom will come back.
Ayse?
Ay...!
Y-You are alive?
How did you know about this place?
Dieter gave me some general directions, so...
Dieter...?
So you are that Tenma guy he was talking about.
Where is Dieter?
He came here, didn't he?
No...
He didn't come here?
Anyway, what about Ayse?
This is Ayse's son.
I want to see her son in her arms again...
Don't tell me...
I won't believe it!
What is this child going to do?
He is still so small, and now he doesn't
have his mother anymore?
What is he supposed to do now?
I won't...
I won't let anyone else become a victim!
Let me see the town leaders!
What do you guys think?
Setting fire to the town, eh?
Those fascists have been threatening to do that all year.
We can't keep wasting our time with them.
Besides, this Japanese person...
It is even more suspicious that he showed up
here, even though he is being chased himself.
You guys!
Ayse died because of this!
She was killed because she tried
to warn you all about this!
Oh, I wonder...
Ayse was a hooker like yourself, right?
It is normal for people to go missing after doing
business with the Germans in that area.
It is a disgrace to the Turkish people.
Who knows whose child that is...
You especially should know that we all
do what we need to survive!
If you want to live, please listen to what I have to say.
I've had enough!
Do whatever you want!
I hope you all burn!
Well, hold on a minute.
Are you asking us to become vigilantes?
Let's try doing what this Japanese man proposes.
Mr. Deniz...
You are going to listen to this suspicious Japanese person?
He is indeed suspicious...
But you know what?
There are Japanese that can be trusted.
Like General Nogi.
General... Nogi...?
What?  You don't know him?
Long ago, a Japanese general named Nogi...
...saved Turkish navy men when they
were stranded in the Pacific Ocean.
Assemble all the men in town!
That looks delicious!
Tonight's dinner seems special!
Wait, wait.  Don't be in such a rush to eat!
Or else you will finish eating before show time.
By the time the main course is served, the
show should be reaching its climax.
As we taste the '76 Chateau Latour that
I've specially ordered for this evening.
...and then wrap our tongues around
my favorite, raw halibut caviar...
Eventually, as we do that...
See!
Look at that!  The first fire has started.
But that is merely an appetizer.
When is the main course?
I told you not to rush, didn't I?
We should just enjoy the meal and
gaze upon the show with...
Where is the main course?
If that fire is just an appetizer...
What are you going to burn for the main course?
This way!
Water!  Bring more water!
Put out the fire!
We don't have enough fire extinguishers!
Don't all go in at once!
Anyone who is not doing anything, come with me!
So the fire did start upwind!
Then that means this side will be in danger, too!
Split up into three groups!
Oh, my.  Yet another beautiful guest
has joined me for dinner.
You little...!
Don't move!
I'll really shoot!
Why don't you just put that dangerous thing away?
How about it?  We will enjoy this together.
Unfortunately for you, your appetizer is disappearing.
Well, that was just an appetizer, anyway.
But it is your favorite, isn't it?
Too bad.
Why don't we enjoy this moment together?
After all, this festival is about accepting
your brother as a member of the family.
This is not what Johan wanted!
How do you know that?
I saw it.
I went to the place he indicated.
Johan didn't wish for this!
W-What did you see?
He...
He didn't wish for anything!
O-Okay.
Relax.  Calm down.
You killed Ayse!
I won't let you do any more awful things!
Where is the main course?
What part of town are you going to set on fire?
Damn it!
They are setting fire to places the fire trucks can't get to!
Get the injured out of here!
I'll be there shortly!
Tenma!
Did you find Dieter?
I found a guy who said he saw a boy who looked
like him in the park this afternoon, but...
Dieter...
You are not going to chase her?
No...
Continue on with the dinner.
But that girl...
No wonder she is Johan's sister.
Her eyes just now...
She really was willing to kill me.
Because of that, I almost told her
where the real main course is.
Then, shall we continue with your dinner?
No.
Before that, bring me a change of underwear.
She is a very frightening girl.
Hold on!
I'll put it out!
You did well.
Everything is alright now.
I don't know who you are, miss, but thank you.
Why were you guys...?
Because...
It is all that brat's fault!
Man, that was close!
Now then, I'm outta here.
There is no way they are gonna stop
with these simple little fires!
What?
I know about it since I used to live
in this town when I was little.
If I was gonna burn this town down...
...I wouldn't set fire to a place like this.
I'm saying this place was just a decoy!
The three places upwind have all been put out...
We owe you one, Mr. Tenma.
Right, everyone?
Yeah.
Thanks to you, it didn't turn serious.
Forget about that.
We must treat the injured first!!
I won't let there be any more victims...
...no matter what!
What do you mean by a decoy?
The direction of the wind is gonna change.
This time every night, the wind stops for a bit.
But then, a breeze starts blowing in off the river.
The wind...
It stopped...
Now then...
It is finally time for the main course.
Okay.
You are all set.
Thanks a lot, Doctor.
Shall we have a toast?
What are you talking about?
You need to rest, since you are injured.
Hey, don't be so strict.
Right?
Yeah, he is right.
Thanks to you, the town didn't have any major fires.
Those fascists are probably pissed
that the fire isn't spreading.
Damn right!
They shouldn't underestimate us Turks!
Where were the other injured people taken?
The mosque by the river.
Hey, Dr. Tenma!
Why don't you take a break and have something to drink?
Treating the injured comes first.
If the fires have only been decoys so far...
...then where are they going to set the real fire?
Just forget it.
Who cares what happens to a town like this?
More importantly, I have something to take  care of first.
Wait!
Please tell me!
If it were you, where would you set the fire?
I told you already!
The breeze will be coming in off the river shortly.
So if you set the fire to the abandoned
factory by the river, it would be all over.
There should be enough chemicals left.
It is finally time.
It is time for the main course.
Now, sate my hunger.
The plan is proceeding accordingly...
It is time for the festival of the superior race.
Why did you follow me?
I have to put out the fire.
I made a promise to Tenma.
Tenma?
This is the place.  This is the warehouse!
Thank goodness.
It looks like they didn't know about this place.
Are these all the chemicals?
If this many chemicals went up in flames...
...the town would be done for!
Okay, I'll protect this place!
I'll never let them set this place on fire!
A-Are you alright?
I slipped...
What is this?
Gasoline...?
Someone is...
...here...
It is okay.  I can walk by myself.
Well, just go to the shelter over there
and I'll take a look at it.
I'm sorry about this.
I sprained it while trying to save
some important heirlooms.
As long as I have this carpet...
...I don't need this town!
800,000...
No, this is a first rate item worth
at least 1,000,000 Marks!
Heckel!
Oh, crap!
What happened to Dieter?
Well, that is, uh...
Tell me, where did Dieter go?
O-Oh!  The kid went to the abandoned
factory by the river.
Factory...?
Soon, the breeze will blow in off the river...
If the chemicals in the factory catch fire...
...this town will be finished
See, this is the breeze I was talking about.
Please tell everyone at the shelter
to get away from the river!
Hurry!
What?
Let's go, Heckel!
Huh?
Who is...?
Who is there?
Don't move!
So, you are Johan's sister?
Throw away the lighter!
If I start a fire, the gasoline will ignite...
...And this warehouse will instantly
become a sea of flame.
I'll shoot you in the head before that can happen!
If I sever your cranial nerves...
...I can stop you from moving!
Can you?
I've been training for half a year.
At this distance, I'm a perfect shot!
I will not be intimidated.
This is the festival for the superior race.
It is to accept Johan as a member of our group.
Johan doesn't want that!
Johan did come to Frankfurt.
But he killed one of your leaders
and his subordinates, then left.
He left a message.
A message?
He is not the type of person you think he is!
He is more more complicated...
What are you trying to say?
He is much more frightening than that...
He is... writhing in pain, in an abyss of grief!
Oh, man, I hope you don't get on their bad side.
Where is the warehouse?
Hey, hey.   Haven't you had enough?
I'm getting out of here...
What are you talking about?
Are you just going to let Dieter die?
Where is the warehouse?
F-Fine, I'll tell you!  I'll tell you, damn it!
You said your friend's name was Tenma, didn't you?
I know someone named Tenma, also.
Really?
Is he really a brave man, also?
Yes.
But I didn't want him to fire a gun.
I didn't want him to kill anyone.
You should never kill anyone either, no matter what!
No matter how bad the person is?
That is right!
Don't do what I'm about to do!
Close your eyes!
Don't look!
Don't shoot!
Tenma!
Heckel, put out the fire!
The carpet!  Hurry!
Wait, you idiot!
My... 1,000,000 is...
Nina...
Tenma...?
Crap!  It is the police!
Run!
Leave that man to me!
There is a boat by the river!
Hurry up and run, Tenma!
The main course...
...got cold...
Thank you for your cooperation.
Could you please come to the
station for a more detailed..
W-Wait a minute!
I'll be right back!
H-Hey, you!
Tenma!
Nina!
Nina, promise me!
Don't shoot!
You must not shoot people!
I saw Johan's message!
I saw it too!
I'm going there right now!
Back then...
...ten years ago...
...when I shot Johan...
...I finally figured out why he wanted
me to shoot him in the head!
Johan...
...isn't alone!
There are two Johans!
So... Dr. Tenma...
That is why... it is not your fault...
I...
Once again, I'll...
...aim at Johan's head, and...
Hey, let's quit wasting our time here...
Let's hurry up and get going!
Man, I can't take this anymore.
I'm so hungry...
I don't have any money...
If only I still had that carpet...
Dammit!
What is this?
T-This is...
"Help me!"
"The monster inside me is about to explode!"
Then, inside Johan...
...there are two personalities?