I've never seen you before.
Get a state permit if you want to do business here.
Unlicensed prostitutes cause trouble.
I can't make much money if I abide by the law.
Hurry up and go home.
I need his permission, right?
Introduce me to him.
Him?
Who are you talking about?
I'll come here as many times as I
need to until you let me see him.
The man they call the Baby.
Be My Baby
You can't use your hands to catch it,
because you are not a goalkeeper.
Rules don't apply to me!
Anyway, where did he go?
Who?
Tenma, of course!
He told me to stay with you for a while because
he found the man he was looking for.
With me?
He thinks I'll look after you?
You have got to be kidding!
I can't stand kids!
Man, that Tenma!
He is out of touch for a while, and
he goes and picks up a kid!
Whatever happened to our plan of him becoming
an underground doctor and making a fortune?
He should get serious...
Here!
Nice header!
Why you little...
What did you do that for, brat?
Hey, I said you can't touch the ball with your hands.
That is a yellow card for you.
Shut up!
How am I supposed to live my life
if I am scared of things like that?
You are gonna get a red card if you
keep saying stuff like that.
Shut up!
Frankfurt Central Station
You are late...
Hurry up and give me the stuff!
Come on, give it to me!
It has been a while, Detective Messner.
D-Dr. Tenma!
Yes, you called me that back then, too.
Even though it was our first meeting, and you
never asked me what my profession was.
But now I am no longer a doctor.
Speaking of which, you are no longer a detective, either.
"Officer discharged for possession of narcotics."
I was very surprised when I found
this article from six months ago.
I don't recommend getting up.
I have a gun pointed at you under my coat.
W-What do you want?
I want to ask you about the event that took
place in Heidelberg ten months ago.
As well as who hired you for the job.
I... I don't know anything.
You took the lives of the Fortners
and the reporter, Mauler!
I didn't do it!
I was only the lookout!
The one who did it was my partner, Müller.
Detective Müller quit right after that incident, didn't he?
Y-Yeah...
He got a lot of money for that, and should
be living the high life right about now...
In your case, you used up all your money on
narcotics, and this is your current situation.
He is the one who accepted the job!
He is the one who committed the murders!
And he is the one who received most of the reward!
Someone once tried to kill me
to keep my mouth shut, also.
I'm surprised you survived.
I was saved by a certain syndicate...
A certain syndicate?
Haven't you heard enough?
I'm sorry!
I talked too much the other day, also!
The other day?
To who?
Just leave me alone!
I don't have time for this!
You are suffering from withdrawal symptoms.
But...
...as long as I'm sitting here...
...I don't think the dealer will come near you.
I... I told you!
I was saved by the Baby!
The Baby...?
Go to the bar named Candy!
You can meet him there!
Who is the Baby?
A big time extreme rightist.
He has high positions in both parties.
The Baby went to the east side
after the Wall fell...
...and tried to build a town of pure Germans...
...but he failed, so he came back here.
Why did a man like that save you?
Darkness...
When the Berlin Wall fell...
...a great darkness was born...
A monster... was born...
A monster...
Please, just go already!
I told the rest to that girl!
That girl?
She came at me, pointing her gun, out for revenge!
The daughter of the couple we killed!
You mean Anna...?
Did Nina...
Did Nina Fortner come to see you?
T-The Baby told me...
If she should ever show up, I had
to point her in his direction.
Because she is...
...very important bait.
Important...
...bait?
You again?
You have guts, coming here every night.
If you want, I'll buy you at a good price.
You are the one who said I would get hurt if  I did
business without the Baby's permission.
What did you say, you little...?
What the hell is with that look?
Is she the one who wanted to see the Baby?
Y-Yes!
Please come this way.
Please wait over there.
Please wait on top of that seal.
Oh, no, no.
On top of that.
That's it.
Do you know this song?
It is "Be My Baby," by the Ronettes
Miss Nina Fortner.
The Baby said it himself.
This country would be okay if a second Hitler was born...
That girl is the bait.
Nina!
How do you know about me?
I know everything.
Your other name is Anna Liebert.
But neither is your real name.
Names have so very little meaning.
My name is the Baby, after all.
Now, let's dance.
I heard you know where my brother is.
Oh, you mean Johan?
That is a good name.
You know, don't you?
What are you doing to do once you meet
your brother, dressed, like that?
I have to kill him.
Please don't wave a dangerous thing like that around.
Don't worry.
I'm sure Johan will show up to see you.
Since I used to live here when I was a kid...
...I know all the back roads in this place.
There is a pawnshop up ahead.
We are going to trade in this carpet for some cash.
What?  You don't have money, Mr. Heckel?
Shut up!
I'm trying to get some cash for your dinner here!
You should be thankful!
What is wrong?
This entire area has turned into a Turkish district!
This is a fake.
W-What are you talking about?
This design!
This texture!
This is clearly hand-woven silk
no matter how you look at it!
It is synthetic.
But since I feel sorry for you, I'll take it for 100 marks.
This is why I hate this.
If this store was still owned by a German,
he would have paid me at least 10,000 Marks!
Then take it back.
Don't come looking for me after you
realize that it was actually real!
This is what you call the real thing.
This is a Hereke 100% silk carpet.
Take a closer look at it.
Even the small, fine details are elegantly done.
This is worth 150,000 Marks.
I-It has to be a fake...
...if your discerning eyes can't even tell that this is real!
Let's go, Dieter.
Hey, I'm hungry
It was real...
That thing was the genuine article!
It is worth 150,000?
If you know where to sell it, you could get 800,000 Marks!
Hey, lets go eat something.
Shut up!
If we can make that thing ours, we will
be able to eat all we want.
Make it ours?
How?
Leave it to me.
W-What is with that glare?
Thief!
You idiot!
Your voice is too loud, you little brat!
Hey, what do you think you are doing?
Sorry, but if you are looking for a
customer, look somewhere else.
I'm not talking about that.
If an Asian guy like yourself walks
in there, he might get killed!
That place is a den for the right wingers!
You are a Turkish woman, right?
You sure you are okay doing business around here?
Don't be ridiculous!
Who would do business in a dump like this?
My friend was kidnapped by some people in there.
I heard she found out their secret or something...
Secret?
I don't know what it is.
But I have to save her soon.
Who knows what they have done to her by now...
A girl that I know is in there as well.
What kind of girl is she?
Could she be a girl with long, blond hair...?
Who knows...
I don't know what kind of hair style she has now...
That girl was just taken away in a car.
To where?
I don't know!
But since she was with the Baby, probably to his mansion.
The Baby?
What kind of car was it?
What color?
A big, bright red Benz.
Okay.
I guess I'll have to find that car and go after them.
Hey, can you save my friend, also?
Please!
She has a child waiting for her at home
Oh?
He is not dead.
Please, this way.
Before that...
...I'll take your gun.
Now please, go right in.
Sit wherever you want.
You are the girl the Baby brought in?
Show me your face.
You are quite a beautiful girl.
I'm not surprised that you are Johan's sister.
I am professor Göderich.
The one in the picture with Johan is General Wolf.
There are two others...
The syndicate is composed of us four.
How about some fruit?
Would you like some?
My brother...
Let me see Johan.
Of course.
Once he knows that you are here, he will definitely show up.
Because he needs you.
So you don't know where Johan is either, do you?
We are in need of him.
So he can be at the top.
Do you know how Hitler obtained so much power?
He was very smart, with a head for business.
And he knew three points.
He controlled the banks, commanded the defense
industry, and seized the military...
Right now, Johan is doing one of those three things.
Well?
Don't you think my deductions are correct?
What are you trying to do with Johan?
However, it was his charisma that allowed
him to achieve all of this.
Hitler failed his art school entrance exam, and
was stuck as a corporal in the military...
If was some time after the age of thirty
when he finally became charismatic.
But what about Johan?
He has had monstrous charisma since he was a child.
Just like Jesus Christ.
But what you must not forget...
...that the first ones to put faith in Christ were the
three wise men from the east and John the Baptist.
The existence of these four amazing people...
We four have paid close attention to
Johan's talents since he was a child.
Isn't it wonderful?
What should I do?
I want you to stay here for a while.
Until Johan shows up to meet you.
I hope you won't try to run away.
You have already taken one step inside.
You don't have to worry about that.
I came here because I wanted to.
I'll wait for Johan here.
Very well.
Now, have some fruit.
Looks like you have finally come around.
You have nothing to worry about.
You have no broken bones.
What were you doing around here...
...Dr. Tenma?
H-How do you know about me?
I'm doing the questioning here.
You just have to answer.
What are you trying to do?
What are you going to do after you find Johan?
Where is Nina?
I told you, I'm doing the questioning!
What are you going to do with Nina?
I told you not to ask any questions!
Nina is an important guest.
She is not trash like you.
Then she is okay?
For now...
But she is very dangerous.
Even though she has a cute face, she is trying to kill Johan.
People like that must be disposed of eventually...
So Nina is just a tool to lure Johan.
Who are you people?
What are you people trying to--
You asked another question!
You foreign races don't have the right to ask us questions!
That kind of impertinent attitude is the
reason the entire town will be burned!
T-The entire town...?
That is right.
Tomorrow night, the sky will be dyed a beautiful color.
If I stay here, I'll meet Johan..
Help me...
W-Who are you?
H-Help me...
Where are you?
On the third floor...
Your German is kind of awkward...
What country are you from?
I'm Turkish...
I'm... going to be killed...
I have to get out of here...
You are being held by the people here, aren't you?
Help me...
But...
I have to stay here no matter what.
Please help me!
If I don't hurry, my child will die also...
Tomorrow night, we are throwing
a welcoming party for Johan.
Superior races like our own should be
the only ones to exist in this world.
The rest should burn.
I... heard them... talking...
They are going... to burn the entire city... tomorrow night...
The Turkish district... they are going to burn it down...
Help me!