I bought the bus ticket for you in advance.
Tenma,
there is the option of giving yourself
up, and then proving your innocence.
I'll help you.
I...
I am not pursuing Johan in order to prove my innocence.
What?
Thank you, Rudy.
Tenma,
you aren't possibly thinking of...
Oh, right.
I wasn't looking down on you.
I thought you looked like an interesting guy,
but I didn't get a chance to get to know you.
However, we've finally become friends.
But...
you saw me cheating...
I was cheating too.
Tenma...
Did you see that road sign just now?
I'm sorry.
I'm having a little trouble with this map...
This way?
Or this way?
I wonder which way we're headed.
Where did you get that map?
Oh, please.
At the car rental counter, of course.
I knew it.
Probably while I was in the restroom, right?
It's of no use anyway.
This map is too complicated for someone my age.
It's because you forgot your reading glasses at the airport.
Nippenhausen...
Anwertzhausen...
Gartelzhausen...
Huh?  What's up with all these unpronounceable names?
It's it funny?
I wonder if Germans think the
same thing when they come to England.
More importantly, where is the next crossroad?
Oh!
There's someone there.
We can ask them for directions.
We're fine.  Let's just keep going.
Oh, my...
But they are hitchhikers.
We should let them in.
Hmph!
What if we get into trouble
because we picked up God-knows who?
But, see?
He has a small boy with him.
Don't you feel sorry for them?
Why don't we give them a ride?
That's great, Tenma!  They stopped for us.
Yeah.
Journey to Freiham
Guten Tag.  Bitte...
We don't understand German.
Can you speak English?
Oh, are you from England?
We'd like to get to Freiham.  Can we get a ride?
Let me see the map.
Okay.
Where is that place?
Huh?
The place you want to go.
Oh...
Uh...
We're around here right now, so...
down south from here.
Oh my,
it's in the same direction we're going!
Hop on, little one.
Danke schön!
Bayern
(Germany)
How are your two related?
You're definitely not family.
You are Asian,
but he looks like he's German.
Uh, well...
He's my friend's child.
Judging from your looks, you're in some
kind of specialized profession, aren't you?
Huh?
The way you talk, your mannerisms...
Honey.
Stop that.
It's a bad habit.
I'm sorry.
He just can't get rid of his old habits.
He used to be a policeman.
What did she say?
He used to be with the police.
Let's get off, Tenma!
No.
U-
U-um...
Then the two of you are taking a
trip now that your husband has retired?
Yes, in a manner of speaking.
He was such a hard worker,
so it used to be impossible to take trips together.
I'm sorry for interrupting your private vacation like this.
Um, if we're too much trouble, we can--
No.  We managed to rent a car at the
airport, but we can't read the damn map.
We're having a hard time even ordering food.
I'd feel better if someone were here to act as a translator.
Really.
Honey,
what should we do?
There's not much we can do about this.
We'll have to go to a nearby gas station.
Oh!  There is a car coming!
Hey!  Stop!
Stop!
Is something wrong?
We're out of gas.
Oh, man!
That can't be good, way out here.
Well, I can take up to two people.
Mr. Jones...
It's fine.  You two get on.
But...
You don't have to be concerned about us and stay.
Then we'll let people know that you are stuck here
when we get to a gas station.
Yeah.
I'd appreciate that.
Whew...
This is good, Tenma.
We got to switch cars just when we needed to.
Yeah.
Please stop at a gas station.
There aren't any around here.
They are very late.
Yeah.
The people at the gas station will come
once that man tells them we are here,
right?
Yeah.
That man...
Maybe he just kept going.
Honey?!
How can that be?
I think he was a good person.
I wonder.
What a beautiful sky.
You've mentioned the sunset many times.
I've seen it plenty of times, so I'm fine.
Oh no, not the sunset.
It's gone already.
See?
Take a look.
The color of the sky after the sun has set.
I wonder if Robert is seeing this sky also.
Oh?
That's...
Hey, honey.
Look!
Someone is coming.
Oh, I knew it!
See?  I knew they would come!
They gave us some gas and a lamp at a nearby farm.
Oh, my!
See, honey?
That was delicious.
Right, honey?
Huh?
Yeah...
Thanks to you, translating the German menu,
we had a great dinner.
Right?
Huh? Yeah...
Especially that wine...
The Forst Ungeheuer.
It's a wine from the Pfalz region.
Oh, yes.  And that dish with the liver, too.
Leberknödel.
That's it!
My, it was so great!
Without you, we would have missed
out on all the good food in Germany.
It was nothing.
I must thank you for dinner.
Dieter?
Would you like another ice cream?
Oh no, he's fine now.
Do you think this guy did it?
Huh?
Oh,
I'm talking about this man who is
being charged with his wife's murder.
What do you think?
Wh-
Wh-who knows?
I may look old now,
but when I was a detective,
I made a pretty good name for myself.
Oh, no...
Don't start your stories here.
Oh...
I used to be able to tell if a man was guilty...
whether he was a truly evil man
or not, just by looking at his face.
Stop it already.
Maybe you drank too much wine.
But...
when you do that for so long, you can't really tell anymore.
A good man and a bad man;
a criminal and an innocent;
you become unable to tell the difference.
Well, it just means I wasn't a great detective.
Maybe...
I did drink too much wine.
What did you say it was called again?
The Ungeheuer.
It was great.
My, how cute.
It'd be nice if Dieter made some more
friends at his new home, wouldn't it?
Huh?
Oh, yes.
Everyone has their own happy childhood, after all.
It brings back memories.
Yeah.
Oops.
I think it was around here somewhere.
What was?
Here, honey.
Sorry,
but would you mind if we made a little stop?
Go ahead.
Here it is.
The police...
We'll be right back.
You two can just wait here.
Wh-what should we do, Tenma?
Tenma...
Let's run.
What's wrong?
Well, there is someone parked in a cruiser's spot,
but it looked like they are foreigners.
Can't be helped, I guess.
What should we do?
Excuse me,
but this is the opposite direction from Freiham,
which is where we were headed.
Yeah,
I'm sorry.
We won't take too much of your time.
We want to stop at Castle Steinbach.
Honey...
Castle Steinbach?
There is something I'd like to see first.
Are you all right?
Yes.
Thank you.
Our son's letter mentioned this.
That the view from the castle was spectacular.
That he would like us to see it also.
Then your son is here?
We're on our way to see him,
but we just keep making stops along the way.
He was looking at this view.
Our son...
He killed a man.
We came to this country to visit him in prison.
Then, we'll be leaving you here.
Thank you very much.
No...
You have our sincere gratitude as well.
Thank you.
Stay well.
He was a nice man.
Yeah.
He is wanted for multiple homicides.
What?
No, how can it be?  Him?
No, I'm sure of it.
I've seen him on the wanted list in the past.
But--
In fact, when we went to see
the detective who arrested Robert,
his picture was posted inside the station.
I can't believe it...
Such a good man...
Yeah.
I was doubtful myself, when I first saw his picture.
Then, I became certain when I met him.
He is innocent.
He definitely is not an evil man.
Robert...
Our son committed murder.
I couldn't even see the signs within my own family.
When I realized this, I quit being a detective.
But, I want to have confidence in my own intuition again.
Robert committed a crime,
but he is not evil.
Now,
let's go see him...
Robert.