Hey, clear the way, people!
Why not?
Please don't obstruct our investigation.
What happened?
Please, at least tell us how the police are viewing this case.
Are you considering this case
as part of the serial murders?
We've heard that the murdered Jopp
couple did not have any children either.
No matter how you look at this,
the circumstances here match those throughout Germany
of the serial middle-aged couple homicides perfectly.
No comment.
We've also heard that the BKA
investigator in charge of the serial murders is coming.
So then this is related to the serial homicides?
No comment!
Sounds like it would be better to
ask that BKA investigator directly.
Leave it to me!
I'll be sure to get a better story than the other papers.
Please save a nice big space for the headline.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
I'm Kipper, from the Hamburg Tag.
You must be the investigator from the BKA.
Can you give a statement?
Is there a connection between this murder
and the serial homicides of middle ages couples--
Mr. Kipper, from the Hamburg Tag...
I will tell you, and only you.
You are correct.
This case is one of the serial homicides.
I knew it!
Then the suspect is the Japanese doctor?
I just read the report.
It has been executed in an identical
manner to all of the other murders.
Thanks for the special exclusive!
I'll be leaving.
Hold on a second!
The Hamburg Tag is a major
newspaper around here, is it not?
Meaning, your story will
circulate among other major newspapers
around the country.
Of course.
Thanks for your cooperation.
Runge's Trap
I am the murderer.
Right now, I have become the murderer.
Do I knock?
Yes, it would be better not to make the Jopps suspicious.
Hmph...
what a friendly couple.
I am invited in without a hassle
and they show me the parlor.
They don't suspect anything at all.
That's the husband's chair.
Of course, I sit in the guest chair.
The husband dies over there
on the floor, several minutes later.
However, I have not made my move yet.
Where is the wife?
No...
she is not in this room yet.
She must be getting tea ready in the kitchen.
Tea will not be served.
The wife was stabbed from the back inside the kitchen.
Then that means I must begin soon.
I take out my knife and stab at the startled husband,
who quickly attempts to stand up.
No, I don't get him.
The husband runs away from an injury on his left hand.
The next attempt gets his right shoulder.
I screw up again!  What an amateur I am!
The husband is screaming for his wife,
but she doesn't hear him.
The wife had become hard of hearing lately.
Yes...
I happen to know that.
Scream!  Yell and cry!
I can take care of the wife after I finish you off.
I've got you cornered!
It's the husband's left hand print.
I've cornered the husband in front of this sideboard.
I'll finish you off!
No.
I didn't finish the husband off here either.
It's five meters from here to the
floor where the husband finally dies.
Why?
Why didn't I finish him off here?
This...
This man killed the Jopps?
No,
that's not necessarily the case.
I'm just asking a favor of the neighbors.
I'd like you to greet and treat this
man normally when he appears.
Then, call me as soon as possible.
That is all I ask.
Uh-huh.
There is no danger involved.
I guarantee it.
In any case, it's terrible that such a thing
happened in a quiet residential neighborhood.
Really.
The Jopps were so nice.
Mrs. Jopp would always greet me cheerfully
whenever I called out to her in the morning.
When you called out to her?
Her hearing has been poor for about a year now, actually.
What?  No way!
It was written by her doctor in her patient records.
She probably barely heard your greetings.
Oh my.
Knowing Mrs. Jopp, she must have
sensed my presence and greeted me.
The neighbors weren't aware of her hearing difficulties?
No,
probably not.
Well, this is quite a company.
It's an extraordinary feat
to be doing so well at your age, Mr. Ziebel.
Oh no,
it's only because the car manufacturer we
contracted with happened to do very well.
I am truly sorry for the loss
of your aunt and uncle.
Yes...
They were the only real family I had left.
They didn't have any children,
so they must have loved their nephew very much.
Yes, like a real son.
Well, I hope you catch the murderer.
Yes,
we're almost positive of his identity.
Then it's that former Japanese doctor?
You are well informed.
Of course!  There were
similar incidents like this in the past.
How much
will you be inheriting?
Huh?
Oh, I'm just curious since the Jopps were very wealthy.
What does that have to do with the case?
You are the sole beneficiary of their will,
I presume?
What are you implying?  This is not the time for such talk!
It is often the case, when a company appears
to be doing very well on the outside,
it is actually in dire straits on the inside.
Who do you think you are?
You make it sound like I did it, for the inheritance!
You're fine.
You have a perfect alibi.
You went out to dinner with your
secretary and employees after a business meeting,
and you even have witnesses.
Wh-what are you trying to say?
You are not the murderer.
Isn't that right?
Detective Runge!
Oh, you.
What's going on here?
About what?
Don't play dumb.
I've been looking into that nephew these past few days.
His company appears to be in good standing,
but their stock investments have failed,
so internally, they're in quite a predicament.
On top of that, look at your actions...
You are thoroughly investigating his company.
What is the real story here?
Do you truly believe that this case
is connected to the serial
homicides involving middle aged couples?
Because of our exclusive story,
the other papers are going along with that theory.
If it has nothing to do with the serial murders,
then our story would be a total mistake!
It's just as you say.
It's the work of a copycat.
One done to make it look like the serial homicides.
I knew it!
We need to change the article immediately.
No.
It's fine as it is.
What?
Keep it as it is...
that this case is one of the serial
middle aged couple homicides.
Are you joking?
Why should I write a lie like that?
I don't care. Just do it.
I-I may not look like it, but I'm still a journalist.
It's no use to trying to intimidate me.
Mr. Kipper, correct?
Quite an enticing woman, isn't she?
Even though you have a warm household
and a lovely wife and daughter,
with such an enticing woman,
I can't blame you for being unfaithful.
Keep it as it is.
Actually, it would be better if you wrote a
special on it, with regard to the serial homicides.
With that,
he will surely come.
I'm counting on you.
Yes?
There are a few questions I'd like to ask.
I see...
They must have been a wonderful couple.
Yes, they were.
Uh,
did they ever have a foster child?
No...
Did they ever live with a child.
even if it was only for a short amount of time?
They didn't.
They were quite fond of their nephew.
Oh, would you like another cup of tea?
Oh, no, thank you.
Please, allow me.
I'm sure of it; it's the man from the picture!
He's at my house right now.
I see.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Detective Runge,
there is someone here to see you.
Who is it?
It's the Jopps' nephew.
You think I did it, don't you?
Isn't that right?
You think that I killed them for inheritance, right?
It's true that I owe some money.
The money they left me
will probably save me from this crisis.
However, I am not that kind of person!
You came just for that?
"Just for that?"
You treat me like a criminal, and this is what I get?
I must be going somewhere.
Stop!
I want you to take back the
disrespectful comments you made the other day!
The man the police had following you...
has been called off.
The police here have deemed you innocent.
Isn't that good enough?
Then who do you think is the murderer?
The murderer...
I could care less about that.
As long as
I manage to capture that man...
Since there is blood over there...
He screwed up?
Then you don't think
that this murder was committed by that Japanese doctor?
Let's see...
I suppose it is a copycat case of the
serial middle aged couple homicides.
How can you be so sure?
There is something in this case
that wasn't found in all of the others.
The murderer cornered the victim here,
and yet, he didn't finish him here.
Rather, it was farther away, all the way over there.
Why?
Why did he hesitate?
This isn't him!
There is emotion.
Emotion?
The scenes of the crimes committed by the man I am after
are made to seem like a robbery,
but no emotion can be detected.
However, in this particular crime scene,
there is an overwhelming amount of emotion.
The murderer became flustered, just because he
saw his face and that of the victim's in the mirror.
But please, don't worry.
The police here are incompetent.
This is nothing more than
the work of a copycat who tried to imitate Johan.
How long is this going to continue?
How long?
It has been a while.
We finally meet again,
Dr. Tenma.
I've been searching for you all this time.
For such a long time.
I've wanted to have a nice, long chat with you.
It's no use running now.
Let's sit down and talk.
How long do you intend to continue this,
Dr. Tenma?
Let's end this.
If you die--
Out of my way!
I-I did it!
I killed the Jopps!
I'll turn myself in, just don't--
I have no interest in you.
Don't get in my way.
D-Dammit!
What is this wound?
At this rate, he's going to bleed to death.
Who would do this to Detective Runge?
I can only leave him in front of the hospital and leave.
Damn!
Have you regained consciousness?
Where is the key to these cuffs?
You won't find your gun there.
I have it.
More importantly, where is the key?
I can't do anything like this.
I just checked your wound.
Fortunately, the knife didn't penetrate the abdominal cavity.
However, you are bleeding too much...
If I don't stop the bleeding, you will die!
Confess,
Dr. Tenma.
What...?
The murder of the three men,
including the director, at Eisler Memorial Hospital...
And the murders of the middle-aged
couples during these past three years...
Confess that it was all your doing.
You are really going to die!
"It's all Johan's doing?"
"I'm looking for Johan, the real killer?"
There is no Johan.
Johan is you, yourself,
Dr. Tenma.
Confess.
I wasn't able to find anything of
much use in the abandoned warehouse,
but I did find enough for first aid.
Now, I just need these hands!
If my hands were free, I could save you!
As Dr. Tenma, you're an excellent doctor.
You play the virtuous man without a single fault, huh?
How many have you killed with those hands?
You...
are wrong.
When are you going to become Johan?
When is the virtuous man going to
transform into the heartless murderer?
You are wrong!
I do not make mistakes.
You are becoming delusional due to the loss of blood.
In your crime scenes...
You shouldn't talk any more.
In your crime scenes,
there is no emotion.
Don't speak.
I suppose you lose emotion when
you handle people's lives every day,
Dr. Tenma.
There it is.
That calm is always there in the crime scenes.
You are truly calm.
You are wrong!
In every surgery,
I've wondered, "Am I going to make a mistake?"
"Can I pull it through?"
"Will problems spontaneously arise?"
I was really terrified!
Lives...
were in my hands!
In my hands...!
How could I stay calm?
Don't...
move...
I will save you.
I will... shoot...
I will stop the bleeding.
Where is the key?
In your pants pocket?
I'm relieved.
You seem to be well.
You look better than you do when you are at work.
I'm sorry for causing concern.
They say that the first aid was perfect.
The doctor said that you wouldn't be alive
now if it hadn't been for the prompt treatment.
I suppose it means...
that I owe Tenma my life.
Well, even though Tenma got away,
Ziebel confessed to killing the Jopps.
Great job, Runge.
Thank you.
What do you think?
Huh?
Runge had his life saved by Tenma.
It may affect his ability to arrest him.
Maybe I should remove him from the case.
Oh,
thank you for taking good care of Detective Runge.
Oh, you are quite welcome.
He is a very nice man.
I told him that he didn't have to start rehab so early,
but he's already begun working with the
squeeze ball and walking in the hallways.
I don't know why, but he says he's having a lot of fun.
Fun?
Yes, he says it often.
That there is nothing more fun.
What was his name, that criminal..
Oh yes, Tenma.
He says it's most fun to go after a criminal like Tenma.