You found a job as a waitress...
and we found a place to live, but...
this bed is really bad.
Look how much it tilts when you sit on it!
It won't stay up if you lie down on it, Nina.
I'll sleep here on the bed...
so you should sleep on the sofa over there.
There's nowhere for you to sleep.
Go back to Dr. Reichwein in Munich.
Why?
What do you mean, why?
Because you need to go to school.
I don't have to go to school.
What are you going to do about your studies?
You're teaching me now.
There's more than that.
You won't make any friends at this rate!
I do have friends.
You and Tenma.
Besides, I know you'll be lonely without me.
Anyway, just go back to Munich.
No way!
I'm not going to Munich.
H-Hey, Nina!
Are you going there again?
Hey, wait!
Man, you should just give up already.
Coming and going to the same place every day!
It's not gonna make any difference, no
matter how many times you go there!
You're not gonna remember anything.
Nina!
The Door of Memory
This is where...
we used to live.
Mom, me...
and Johan.
On that day...
Johan was taken down these stairs,
as if being dragged away.
No, stop it!
Let go of me!
Mom!
Nina!
No...
Nina is my name now...
What was I called back then?
Nina?
Anna?
What was...
my name?
The car that Johan rode in went down this road...
You mustn't hide anything from him.
They gathered the children here...
and held book readings.
Here at the Red Rose Mansion.
The lock's broken.
They were trying to create him here.
An excellent student...
What's an excellent student...?
Johan?
And then...
Who would do such a thing?
He ran.
Johan ran away.
He ran through the rose bushes.
Are you okay?
This pain...
Could it be...?
I was waiting in this room.
Waiting for Mom to return.
Waiting for Johan to return.
Reading this picture book.
Human beings can become anything.
Franz Bonaparta.
Bonaparta was holding book readings
at the Red Rose Mansion...
and I was reading his book in this room...
waiting for Johan to return.
Smiling, I said it...
when the door opened.
Welcome back.
Now, come with me.
The door won't open!
Even if I say "welcome back," the door won't open!
It won't open!
It won't open! Because I...!
Because I...!
I remember!
It was me who...!
Stop it, Nina!
You don't have to remember!
You don't have to remember anything!
It's the same with me!
I have lots of horrible memories!
But I don't have to remember those!
Fine!
I'll go to Dr. Reichwein's place!
You too, Nina!
Let's go back together!
Let's do what Tenma said!
We can make happy memories...
starting now...
Prague Police Static
(Czech)
Please wait a minute, Detective!
What do you mean, all I can do is sit
next to a detective and listen?
We're giving you all the help we can.
All the help?!
You've limited me to thirty minutes with each person!
Isn't listening to their stories enough?
The amount of cooperation we're giving
you is unheard of you know.
It's a miracle that we even have these
five witnesses for questioning.
That's why...
we must use this opportunity to collect as much...
Naïve.
They probably don't want to talk about their past.
Those children from the book readings, I mean.
However, the Czechoslovakian secret
police must have been involved...
with the case where we found
a massive number of corpses.
Though...
the truth usually stays in the bushes...
in incidents like these.
This is the detective in charge of the case.
This is Mr. Verdeman, a lawyer from Germany.
I'll leave the rest to you.
I'm Detective Suk.
Nice to meet you.
I already have a list of questions.
Please do as I tell you.
You're joining me merely as an observer.
Number 3 Cerveny Street.
Also known as the Red Rose Mansion.
It burned to the ground...
and this is what it looks like now, but...
you undoubtedly attended the
book readings in 1968, right...
Mr. Erno?
Well?
Do you know of a person named Franz Bonaparta?
Would you please keep quiet?
You don't have much time, right?
I just want to be careful.
So careful that you won't get any
useful information in the end.
Do you know how hard it was for us to find them...?!
I don't feel sad.
I thought my heart relied on this mansion.
But looking at what remains of it...
I thought it would be more, how should I say it...
I thought I would feel sad, but...
Do you feel nostalgic?
Nostalgic?
That's right.
This place was like a school to you, wasn't it?
Mr. Verdeman, please be quiet!
I still haven't asked him the questions I prepared!
I don't really know...
Sadness...
Nostalgia...
I don't know...
Mental wounds?
What do you mean?
Well, what I mean is...
do you feel anything now...
because you attended the book readings?
No, not really.
Do you have a family?
You don't have to answer.
You have the right.
I'm divorced.
No, I didn't have any real problems with my wife.
Our children...
Our eldest and youngest sons...
both committed suicide.
It's not that they had any real problems, either...
but for some reason, they both...
I wonder why they killed themselves...
What are you trying to say?
I'm saying that the way you're asking your questions...
is too... by the book.
How much have you learned so far?
It's common among kids these days.
You probably hit on women by the book too.
You act like a father.
I don't have a father, but...
I certainly wouldn't want one like you!
Next person, please come in.
Memories of the book readings, huh?
Anything is fine.
No matter how trivial it may be.
"The God of Peace is always busy."
W-Why are you suddenly...?
"He is too busy to look in a mirror..."
"and blows his horn every day."
"The God of Peace," by Klaus Poppe.
You know this book, right?
Yeah, I remember some of it.
Aside from that one...
I also liked the one about a monster from the west
and a monster from the east or something like that.
What parts of these works were attractive to you?
How should I say it...
They take you to another world.
Another world?
That's right.
Crying, rejoicing, being afraid...
All those things disappear.
Why did these books make you feel that way?
I don't know.
But it's true that I didn't feel those things.
You didn't even need your own name.
That was real freedom.
That's what I felt.
Why did it make you feel that way?
You were taught by Franz Bonaparta, weren't you?
I think that was the name of the
person who read us the books...
That's what you remember clearly
from the book readings, right?
Remember clearly?
No...
One day...
a man came to visit that mansion.
He said he was from a radio station.
He said he loved the song "Somewhere
Over the Rainbow..."
and read us "The Wizard of Oz."
What kind of person was he?
Tell me!
Tell me about that man!
What are you thinking?
That's enough!
Please, tell me!
Please! Anything!
What are you trying to accomplish?!
You seem to have a personal reason for questioning them!
It's personal with you, too.
The young detective who was falsely accused...
for the slew of cases where the
secret police were involved.
That's you, isn't it, Detective Suk?
You're desperately trying to clear your name.
Isn't that right?
I'm the same.
My father was imprisoned because they thought
he was a spy for old East Germany.
I continued to believe they were false charges.
However, my father really was a spy.
I couldn't believe in anything after that.
I couldn't believe in anything in this world.
But right now...
by pursuing a certain case of
another falsely accused man...
I'm trying to find something I can trust again.
The man from the radio station that
witness was talking about...
That was my father.
My father may have been involved with the brainwashing
experiments conducted at the Red Rose Mansion.
I mustn't look away...
so I can learn the real truth.
Hey, can I go now?
No, just a little more.
If you want to talk about the man I just mentioned...
he once told me...
He told me to hurry up and run away from that place.
He told me there must be a better place
somewhere over the rainbow.
And my family would be in that place.
He also told me that Dorothy in "The Wizard
of Oz" was able to go home...
so I should hurry up and get away from that place.
So since then, I've broken my ties with that mansion.
Can I go now?
My wife and kid are waiting for me.
S-Sure...
We mustn't look away.
Yeah...
There are only two people left to interview.
Okay, let's continue.
Hey, Dieter!
Stop spacing out and hold it steady!
This is your study desk, you know.
O-Okay.
Nina doesn't want to talk about what
happened to her in Prague.
From what you told me, it looks like...
she has recalled a lot of memories.
But it looks like she applied the brakes just
before she could remember the last bit.
Thanks to you.
I wonder if I did something wrong...
No.
You did well, Dieter.
Now, let's hurry up and finish this...
so I can have my white sausages with some beer!
We finished eating all the white sausages last night.
Oh, that's right!
What should I do?!
Doctor!
We brought your favorite, white sausages.
Oh, you guys are so considerate!
How are you, Dr. Reichwein?
I'm sorry for not contacting you in such a long time.
Nina!
Lotte!
I'm sorry to have made you worry.
I'm fine.
The truth is, Dr. Reichwein, I have a favor to ask of you.
You know the woman named Eva Heinemann, correct?
She's being targeted by a certain organization right now.
I told her to go to you.
Please look after Eva for me.
And Nina and Dieter, too.
It will all be over soon.
I think this is the only way to end
this entire chain of events.
"Sincerely, Kenzou Tenma."
I got that letter about three days ago
I haven't seen any sign of Eva coming to see me though?
I wonder where this letter was sent from...
You can't really read the postmark, either.
Can,you look into it, Karl?
Yeah, probably.
Then we'll know where Tenma is, right?
Although...
this last sentence worries me.
"I think this is the only way to end
this entire chain of events."
Now then...
Guess I should go finish that study desk!
But my hands might slip, since
I've had something to drink.
Dr. Reichwein.
I think I want to remember everything.
Are you prepared for what might happen when you do?
Yes.
So...
do whatever you must to help me regain my memories!
To be honest, I don't want to do anything.
But if that's what you really want, then...
Are you sure, Nina?
Yes, Dr. Gillen.
However...
what I'll say when I'm hypnotized...
may be something truly terrifying.
Will you be able to handle it, Doctor?
Yes, I'll be fine.
Let's tackle this together.
Now, please close your eyes.
Take a deep breath and let your entire body relax.
What kind of person was your mother?
My mom...
My mom... was kind...
Singing...
Singing voice...
A beautiful singing voice...
The smell of bean soup...
What about your father?
My dad...
My dad was...
a soldier for the government.
A soldier for the government?
Have you ever met him?
I've never met him...
My mom told me...
my dad...
was killed...
My mother...
an anti-government activist...
So your father was killed...
and your mother, who was an anti-government
activist, ran away.
Ran away from whom?
The Three Frogs...
We hid there...
But...
My brother was caught...
by a man with black sunglasses.
Your brother was caught?
The Red Rose Mansion!
So many people were dead!
That's what your brother saw?
It hurts!
The thorns hurt!
Welcome back.
Nina?
I found out where Tenma sent that letter from!
Where?
Frankfurt.
Nina?
You remembered everything, didn't you, Nina?
I...
am not Nina...
Then who are you?
I don't want to tell you.
It's okay.
Don't be scared, so tell me.
Who are you?
I don't want to tell you.
It's okay.
Don't be scared.
I don't want to tell you.
Welcome home.
I-I'm going to clap my hands...
and you will...
wake up from the hypnosis.
Nina!
S-She's okay.
Did I...
say something terrible just now?
No.
You didn't want to talk about it, even
when you were hypnotized.
But you remembered everything, didn't you?
Two Days Later
Dr. Reichwein, Dieter.
Forgive me for leaving so suddenly.
I'm going to Frankfurt, where Tenma is.
I understand everything now.
Who I am...
where Johan came from, and where he's heading.
If I go, I can resolve all of this.
If I go...
I can save Tenma.
Yes
Cherish what you know is true in this world.
Ima kono sekai de wakaru koto mitsumete
Yes
Please believe in the kindness of your eyes
Anata no hitomi no yasashisa wo shinjite
Make it home to your land of harmony
Make it home to your land of purity
Make it home