Are you crying?
It's a letter from my friend.
My best friend.
When I was fifteen years old...
we tried to cross the Czech border together.
She was caught and sent back to Prague.
She said she's doing well.
She knows me better than anyone in my family...
A true friend.
Who knows what kind of censorship
this letter had to go through...
before she could send it to me?
"If we ever get a chance to meet again..."
"please come to this place... "
"Cedok Bridge, the Three Frogs."
I want to go back... to Prague...
Margot...
Hey...
Huh?
Please call me by my real name.
Just for tonight, I'd like you to use my real name.
I am Helenka Novakowa.
Just for tonight, I'm not Margot Langer.
The Monster's Love Letter
I sold my Reiser-Berger Pharmaceutical
stock in the nick of time.
Then I bought some Kneuter Research stock...
and I hit the jackpot.
I just had to celebrate after that...
Did you drink?
Yes, a little bit.
I'm appalled.
It was just one glass.
I've said this many times.
When you're an alcoholic...
it doesn't matter how much you drink, it's all the same.
And you've been ditching the alcohol
rehab group I recommended for you.
By the way...
Doc, can you keep this secret?
The thing is, there's a woman I want you to see.
Another one of your lovers?
Well...
She's a really bad alcoholic.
She's waiting right outside.
Could you take a quick look at her?
I can't do that without an appointment.
Have one set up for her.
A quick look would be fine.
I've got a house call to make.
For a very important patient, at that.
I went to Prague, in the Czech Republic.
It was beautiful.
Prague Castle.
The cathedrals, with their marvelous Gothic architecture.
The view of the old commercial district
at night was also stunning.
It was like I was in a fairyland.
And Cedok Bridge...?
Did you go to Ceddk Bridge?
Of course, just as you asked me to.
And...
I found it! The Three Frogs!
Was the woman there?
No...
No one was there.
To be honest...
I didn't find anything by going there.
Tenma, Nina, and even Dieter...
I didn't find anything that indicates where they are.
Take this...
It's a rabbit's foot that brings good luck.
It's for our child you're carrying...
Margot... no, Helenka...
I...
Thank you.
Prague
Yes?
Ah, excuse me...
I've come from Germany, and I'm
trying to find a missing woman.
Do you know her?
Margot Langer...
Ah, I mean Helenka Novakowa.
Helenka...
By the way, Mr. Schuwald...
Your son, Karl, mentioned this to me...
You haven't been eating again, right?
I know that during the fire in the
University of Munich Library...
you experienced something truly terrifying.
And I understand that you haven't overcome that fear yet.
But you still have Karl...
who is such a splendid son.
There's no need to worry anymore.
Just eat properly!
That monster...
As long as that monster exists, I will...
How did that monster know so
much about Margot Langer?
He knew more than my son did.
Margot had a friend in Prague who knew
her better than her own family did.
The woman she exchanged letters with.
Around 1980...
you went searching for the missing Margot...
and you met that woman in Prague.
Yes.
I thought she may have heard something from Margot.
However...
She hadn't heard anything.
We talked about Margot for a little while in her doorway.
At the time...
they were listening...
to our conversation.
Who?
They were quietly listening...
standing behind the woman.
They were twins...
Yes, come in.
Have a seat over here.
You were referred by Mr. Talbach.
You also have drinking problems.
Well, let's just have a casual conversation for now.
Doctor!
What's wrong, Mehres?
I'm in the middle of a counseling session.
Just now, on TV...
Tenma! Dr. Tenma...!
Excuse me for a minute!
I repeat...
The Czech police have just announced...
the capture of the main suspect in the poisoning...
of three murdered doctors from Eisler Memorial
Hospital in Düsseldorf, Germany...
the murders of the journalist Mauler
and the Fortners in Heidelberg...
and the street murder at Heidelberg Castle.
The Japanese doctor, Kenzou Tenma,
who had been hiding in Prague...
was apprehended on the afternoon of the 5th.
We're still waiting for more information
on the details of his arrest...
which will be released during
the police press conference.
Tenma!
You can't come in here!
This is a private office...
so please wait in the other room, Ms. Eva Heinemann!
Kenzou...
Sorry I'm late, everyone.
Hess, you look ten years younger.
Maybe because I've been taking
care of my grandkids too much.
How've you been, Hubert?
I somehow made it to my senior year...
Mr. Kiefer, I heard you've been doing very well lately.
I've been bragging that I know a script writer
who's been invited to Hollywood.
I'm so honored...
Yes, I just happened to catch a producer's eye.
My mind's become very sharp...
and new ideas just keep pouring into my head.
That's great to hear.
Ever since that surgery...
If that brain surgery hadn't been successful...
right now, I'd be...
I wouldn't have been able to take walks
in the park with my grandchildren.
That seat...
He was always drinking tea by himself.
Though there were other cafes where doctors met...
he always came to this one, in the
back of Eisler Memorial Hospital.
When we the patients, would come here...
he would look up from over there...
and wave at us with a smile.
He was a kind doctor.
Yes.
There's no way a kind doctor like
him could do something like this
This is the reason I asked you to come today.
No, even the people who couldn't make it here
today must be feeling the same way...
if they were Dr. Tenma's former patients.
Dr. Schumann, we've got trouble!
Old man Merkel collapsed!
All right, I'll be right there.
I'm in the middle of something right now.
Sorry, but please wait a minute.
Okay.
Dr. Tenma wouldn't have done such a thing!
Calm down and listen, Mom.
Hurry, go to him, honey!
Yeah, but Petra...
There s no "but"!
Dr. Tenma's been arrested for crimes he didn't commit!
If not for him, I wouldn't be here right now.
Are you going to pretend nothing happened,
when your wife's savior is in big trouble?
What about the village?
What?
In this village, I'm the only doctor.
If I leave, what's going to happen
to the people in this village?
Don't make excuses!
You want to go, right?
Hurry and go save Tenma!
When a doctor has patients, he cannot leave them.
Dr. Tenma would do the same.
Doctor, please hurry and see me!
I'm prepping right now, so wait there.
How long are you gonna make us wait?
Don't complain!
She's been going to medical school recently.
She still runs an unauthorized clinic for us at her own risk!
If you stay in the darkness, you'll sink into the darkness...
Shine light upon it.
I'm sure, you can become a doctor.
I'm sure you'll be a good doctor.
Dr. Tenma...
All right, let's begin.
First patient, please come in.
Get a lawyer.
Yes.
But we still don't know where in Germany
Tenma will be transferred.
Pick a lawyer for each state...
The best criminal lawyers out there.
Right.
Only that man...
I feel only that man can do it...
Only he can obliterate the monster.
For now, let's gather more people.
Let's call out to Dr. Tenma's former patients.
Alone, each of us may not have much
influence, but if we all pull together...
All right.
Let's ask Eisler Memorial for their cooperation...
and create a rescue association...
That's impossible.
Eisler Memorial won't help with that kind of thing.
I've been listening to you for a little while now.
What a tearjerker!
But think about it.
How are you guys going to prove Tenma's innocence?
Dr. Becker!
He had a motive, and no alibi at all.
I heard they also found material evidence.
Even if you get together and make a
fuss, or hire a competent lawyer...
it s impossible to prove Tenma's innocence either way.
It's unfortunate, but...
Such an eminent doctor...
It's unfortunate.
I'll ask you again, but...
what kind of relationship do you have with Tenma?
Ms. Eva Heinemann.
I don't know who you are, but...
I'm going to rescue Tenma.
If you're tagging along out of curiosity,
I'd prefer you didn't come.
Eva...
Heinemann...
Heinemann?!
Could if be that you're...
related to Director Heinemann, who was
murdered at Eisler Memorial Hospital?
Dr. Tenma...
is the man who ruined my life.
But you know...
I'm the only one who can save him.
I saw.
Saw what?
St. Jaromir Hospital
Kenzou Tenma, who has been taken
into custody in Prague...
will be deported to Germany within
the next couple of days to stand trial.
He will be transferred to Düsseldorff
where the string of murders began.
After an interrogation...
the police are going to inspect
the crime scene with Dr. Tenma.
No way!
It can't be!
That man...
That doctor...
This is Dr. Tenma.
Suk, he's the man who saved your life.
It's because of his emergency treatment that you're alive.
Dr. Tenma is also being accused
or crimes he did not commit.
He's in the same situation as you.
The man who saved my life.
And he's also in the same situation as me...
You're a detective, aren't you?
If you're a detective...
then you have to calmly dissect the situation.
If you don't want to be betrayed anymore...
then start doubting the person
you want to doubt the least
I have to go...
Somehow, I have to get to Prague Station...
and talk with Dr. Tenma.
We've been looking for you, Suk.
Detective Blazek...
Detective Stransky...
I...
You don't have to run anymore.
Huh?
We've put you through quite a bit of trouble.
You've been cleared of all charges.
A letter was delivered to the station.
This is a copy.
A letter...?
It's a confession with the kinds of details...
regarding the whole case that
only the killer would know.
All the charges against you have been dropped.
Who sent the letter?
Someone by the name of Grimmer.
What did you say?
We've already put a warrant out for
Grimmer as the prime suspect.
W-Wait a minute!
It's okay now, Suk.
Detective Zeman's murder, the
commissioner's poisoning...
and the special task force murders...
have now all been resolved.
Where have you been, Lunge?!
I've been calling your number all day!
Sorry, Chief.
I went out sightseeing for a bit.
Geez! Stop playing dumb!
Playing dumb?
What are you talking about?
Knock it off already!
I bet you've heard the news!
Yes...
About Dr. Tenma's arrest, right?
Congratulations, Lunge.
Huh?
You knew, right?
That Tenma was hiding out in Prague.
Good job Lunge.
This is the result of your thorough investigation.
We contacted the Czech police immediately and
completed the deportation arrangements.
Tenma will be transferred to Düsseldorf
tomorrow afternoon.
Since you're in charge of this case...
I want you to personally supervise his transfer.
Anyway, you did a good job, Lunge.
Congratulations.
Can you assign it to someone else?
Huh?
Prague is a nice place.
What?
Besides, right now...
I'm still on vacation.
Hey, Lunge!
What are you saying?!
Hey!
Please let me see Dr. Tenma!
I've been telling you, you can't see him
Why not?
Didn't this country become a democracy
Tenma is about to be deported back to Germany.
Before that happens, even if only for a little...!
Looks like we wasted our time.
Even though we came all the way to Prague...
Please!
Even just a quick look!
Come out.
This way, come on.
When we interrogate someone...
what kind of person do you think
is the toughest to crack?
Someone whose expression never changes.
regardless of the question.
Someone who doesn't say a word.
That kind of person.
A love letter from a monster to a beauty.
It's like the draft for a novel.
"I've been watching you all this time."
"To eat up every bit of you."
"But instead, everything about you has devoured me."
"I wonder what I look like to you,
who is collapsing into ruin."
"That which you left me, which is collapsing into ruin."
"You left me with such beautiful jewels."
"The twins, who are like eternal life itself."
"The greatest sin..."
"is to take away a person's name."
"Reclaim your name."
"I return your name to you."
"Your name is... Anna."
"I'm filled with sorrow now."
"Filled with sorrow..."
Filled with sorrow..."
It exists...!
The many people who died in that room...
And...
A terrifying monster was born!
Yes
Cherish what you know is true in this world.
Ima kono sekai de wakaru koto mitsumete
Yes
Please believe in the kindness of your eyes
Anata no hitomi no yasashisa wo shinjite
Make it home to your land of harmony
Make it home to your land of purity
Make it home