It's gonna be another hot day today.
Aren't you hot, dressed like that in the summer?
What's that?
Isn't that newspaper three days old?
They said another middle aged couple
was murdered, this time in Verden.
They said a doctor did it, didn't they?
Speaking of which, you said you were
going to Verden, didn't you?
Do you know someone living there or something?
Yeah...
I don't know if I'll meet him there...
...but I have to go.
An Old Soldier and a Little Girl
Giessen Police Station
(Germany)
You were originally with the French foreign legion.
After becoming a mercenary...
...you took part in the Nicaragua war in 1979.
From 1981 to 1984...
...you aided the anti-government guerrillas in Afghanistan.
In 1987...
...you played an important role in
the Mossad's secret campaign...
...to eliminate a radical Islamic faction.
That is quite an extensive combat history...
...Mr. Hugo Bernhardt.
Since the seminar was held by an excellent
mercenary like yourself...
...I assume the graduating students were splendid.
I really wish our young officers would attend your class...
...so they could be retrained.
T-That's not necessary...
Speaking of which...
...did this man perform splendidly as well?
About five months ago...
...he should have come to your training ground.
He is a genius with a scalpel in his hand, but...
...was he as adept with a gun?
I don't like to talk about my students.
I see.
5 Months Ago
Were you taught how to shoot a gun?
No...
So you were self-taught.
I've never fired a gun before.
Not even once?
No.
I know what I'm asking is absurd.
But...
...you are the only one I can turn to.
Either way, you will have to forget everything you know
about guns if you join my training program.
But...
This is the first time someone who has never
shot a gun before has come to me.
It's a jump rope.
Whether you have experience or not...
...we always start with this.
Just like her.
Quit spacing out!
Hurry up and start!
O-Okay!
Faster!
Balance!  Keep your balance!
I can't jump as well as you.
Do you always supervise the training
for the instructor like this?
Okay.
You don't have to stare at me like that.  I'll do it.
I...
...have to do it, anyway...
It's a brambling...
I wonder if she is looking for food for her chicks?
Too tired to eat?
Y-Yeah...
Eating is also part of the training.
Okay.
Is that your daughter...?
No, your granddaughter?
No.
I was the one who killed her mother.
Right in front of her eyes.
It happened in Myanmar.
When I went into a  hut in the jungle...
...I found those two inside.
The mother was holding a gun.
If I had hesitated, I would have been shot.
That is why I brought her back with me.
Ever since she started living with me...
...she has never smiled.
She will probably live the rest of her life...
...hating me.
That is what happens when you hold a gun.
If you don't like it...
...don't hold a gun.
What is this?
It smells nice.
It smells like daphne.
Thanks...
That is enough.
Then...
It is time for you to go running.
Oh, that is right...
After you are done with that, come to
the depression behind the house.
The depression?
The firing range.
The firing range...
Listen carefully.
Shoot twice.
When shooting a gun, always pull the trigger twice.
You chance of killing someone will
rise dramatically by shooting twice.
If you can't do that...
...don't expect to survive.
What is this?
You always make the food around here...
...so I made some Japanese dishes today.
It is called Beef Potato.
I hope you will like it.
They are chopsticks.
I made them by sharpening wood.
I thought it would feel more Japanese if we used them.
That is pretty good.
You are good at using chopsticks.
Again!
Take aim!
What is wrong?
That is a baby brambling.
It must have fallen down from its nest.
You can't!  You have to return it to its nest!
It will die!
It is very hard to raise it away from its nest.
They rarely ever survive.
Let's return it to its nest.
To its mother...
Three seconds!
Everything will be decided in three seconds!
If you mess up or hesitate for even a split second,
the one who will be shot and killed...
...is you!
...what grade did he graduate with?
He got a perfect score on his technique.
He also built a fundamental level of stamina.
Overall his concentration was absolute.
However...
However...?
If he had to kill a person with a
gun, it would be another story.
Oh?
Whether he can kill his first person or not...
...that is where the path splits.
Between whether he can use a gun or not, that is.
I see.
Which do you think he will take?
Well, that does not matter.
So, do you know where he is headed?
If you do, I would very much like to know.
Thank you for the past five months.
Here is the payment for the rest of the training.
Also, please eat Beef Potato.
Thank you very much for everything.
Damn it...
Shit!
You smiled...
Well?
You know where he is headed, right?
I can't tell you that.
Very well.
You can leave now.
This way.