Please help me!
If I don't hurry, my child will die, too...
I... heard them... talking.
They are going to... burn the entire city... tomorrow night...
Turkish town... they are going to burn it down...
Help me!
I have to tell them quickly...
Or else my town...
They will burn my boy!
Wolf's Confession
Where are you going?
Hey, brat!
That rug in the antique shop...
Its existence is meaningless unless someone knows
its value, someone like myself.
I told you not to look at adults like that!
You thief.
Do whatever you want!
Even if I end up making a lot of money...
...I'm not gonna get you anything good to eat!
Listen up!
You will be sorry if you tell anyone!
I'll never team up with a thief.
No matter what.
I'm so hungry...
There, there.  Don't cry.  Don't cry.
Your mom will be home soon.
That baby doesn't have a mom?
Yeah.
Don't hang around here by yourself...
Go home to your mom.
You don't have a mom either?
I'm sorry, I didn't mean that.
That is alright.
I have Tenma.
Tenma?
Don't hold back, eat up!
Though it is nothing special.
So you are waiting for that Tenma person to come back?
You are the same as that child.
Where did his mom go?
She was taken by some bad people.
Bad people?
That place is very dangerous.
Just now, an Asian person was trying to assist me...
...but he was struck by a car right in front of me.
An Asian man...?
Oh, you said that Tenma person was Japanese, didn't you?
But... it can't be.
I have to go!  Where is he?
One of my customers...
That man... man from the extreme right...
After work, I left the room...
But I forgot the scarf, so I went back to get...
That man... was talking on the phone with friends...
I... ran...
I tried to tell the townspeople...
But I... was caught... and locked here...
My boy... still small...
He cannot run if the fire starts!
Who is it?
Professor Göderich asked me to deliver some fruit to you.
Thank you.
I have a message from the professor.
General Wolf will be arriving soon.
That person who was in the picture with my brother?
Yes.
He is the one who has the most knowledge about Johan.
The professor said that he may know Johan even
better than his little sister.
Oh, you cannot die just yet.
His Excellency Wolf will be here shortly.
He will see my meritorious deed in capturing you.
Wolf...?
That is "His Excellency" to you!
Find General Wolf.
He was the firs to realize Johan's talent.
It is like a dream come true to hear
words of praise from General Wolf.
Pardon me.
We have assembled the crew for the
Turkish district burning.
Are there any changes to the plan?
Everything is going accordingly.
I'll have my dinner as I watch the bright red sky.
That is why my fun filled dinner will be
ruined if the timing is even slightly off.
So tell them they will be punished if they can't
carry it out according to the schedule.
Yes, sir.
Johan, won't command you people.
It is impossible... to make Johan sit
at the top of your organization...
He... doesn't have the cheap racial discrimination
or prejudices... like you people...
Johan mocks the entire human race!
Shut up!
You are a rare kind of customer.
Give this customer my usual.
Coming up.
That was amazing.
He is gonna grow up rotten.
Gross!
I can't believe they drink that stuff.
Tenma's jacket...?
Tenma?
Where are you?
Just calm down.
I want to get you out of that room, but...
...I can't do anything right now.
So I'll sneak out of here and notify your
people in town about this.
R-Really?
What street should I go to?
Calvin Street...
Calvin Street.  Got it.
What is your name?
Ayse...
Ayse, don't worry!
Your boy will be okay!
And I'll help get you out of here soon.
Hang on until then.
Okay?
Thank you...
W-What is your... name...?
It is Nina.
I'm looking forward to meeting you.
Nina...
I...
Ever since I arrived in Germany... only
bad things happen to me, but...
For the first time, I meet a nice person...
We are... friends, right...?
Yeah.
Hey, what is your boy's name?
Ayse?
Please stop!
Ayse!
Ayse...
Is that man Tenma?
Yes.
I was the one who captured him.
Where is "His Excellency" Wolf?
He is waiting somewhere else.
We are taking this man with us.
But this was my achievement...
So I thought I would kill him after I showed
him to "His Excellency" myself...
What should we do with this kid?
He said he came looking for that man.
Oh?  You know each other?
I... I don't know him.
That child has nothing to do with this.
Please let him go...
I can't take this filthy child to "His Excellency" Wolf's place.
Dispose of him.
S-Stop!
Oh, he is so noise.
Since he is an annoyance, kill him now.
Okay.
Stop!
T-That was my subordinate...
Dr. Tenma.
Please forgive our rudeness.
You are an important guest of General Wolf.
Ayse...
I have to tell them quickly...
Or else my town...
They will burn my boy!
We are... friends, right...?
That is right, Ayse.
We are friends!
W-What is going on...?
Professor Göderich...
Everyone is... dead!
We will soon arrive at the mansion
where General Wolf is waiting.
Is Nina there, too?
Yes, please be rest assured.
She is an important guest, like yourself.
What about the Turkish woman?
I don't know.
We don't know anything besides what we were told.
We have to go back to town!
Calvin is gonna be burned down right, right?
If we don't tell the townspeople...
...the lady that treated me to dinner and the baby will die!
Unfortunately...
...it is our responsibility to take you to the mansion.
Stop the car!
Tenma!
Can you get to the Turkish district by yourself?
I'll be right behind you.
But right now, I have to go.
But...
Get a hold of yourself!
You are a man, are you not?
If you go, everyone on Calvin Street will be saved!
Hurry up and go!
Okay!
If you can hitch a ride, it will take you about thirty minutes.
I'm sorry for being so rough.
Please start the car.
I'm sorry for doing this to you after you
trusted me enough to return my gun...
...but you didn't seem like you would
stop if I had not done it that way.
That is okay.
After learning that a gun is not merely an accessory to you...
...I'm sure General Wolf will be quite pleased.
Please, this way.
Where is Nina?
She is in this mansion?
Let me see her!
You will first meet with General wolf
and Professor Göderich.
No, show me that she is safe first!
Göderich is dead.
Not only Göderich...
...but all of his subordinates were killed.
What...!
We have disposed of the bodies.
What about Nina?
By the time we brought General Wolf to this mansion...
...she had already disappeared.
You are Dr. Tenma, correct?
W-Who are you?
You probably won't recognize me when you see my face...
Thank you for coming.
I am Wolf.
B-But...
You appear completely different compared
to the picture from ten years ago...
Fear...
It is due to fear.
Can't you go faster, mister?
You have got to be kidding!  I'm already pushing 200KPH!
200KPH?
Your meters are broken!
I'm not gonna make it!
People's names are mysterious things.
The people I know...
...know that my name is Wolf.
However...
...if I join a group of strangers...
...I must tell them that my name is Wolf.
But you know what?
Where is the proof that I am Wolf?
You were the first one to find out
about Johan, weren't you?
Yes, twelve years ago.
Then you sent him to Kinderheim 511 in Germany...
...to become an East German vanguard...
No, you tried to raise him to be a leader.
Yes...
As a man of talent to support a country
on the verge of collapse.
And even now...
...you chose him as a new Hitler...
...and are trying to expand a fascist organization!
Right now, I am merely involved with this
organization as a matter of convenience.
Even though the others are trying
to fashion him into Hitler...
...that is just a foolish plan.
Even with a man like Hitler, it went that far.
It if had been Johan..
Oh, yes.
I was the one who gave him the name "Johan."
We took the two siblings in when we found them
wandering near the Czechoslovakian border.
The two had evaded the heavy security near the border...
...and were on the verge of death due
to malnutrition and exposure.
They fell unconscious soon after we picked them up.
It was the same as when you saved his life...
When he regained consciousness...
...I asked him a question.
"How do you feel right now?"
And he answered me.
"You'll know soon enough."
I don't have any evidence that I am Wolf.
The people I've known have left
this world, one after another.
My wife, my child...
...my parents, my siblings, my relatives...
...my subordinates, and my friends.
They all died, one after another...
Everything was Johan's doing.
The only thing that can verify that I am Wolf...
...is the large sum of money I took with
me when I escaped from East Germany.
Aside from my own belief that I am myself...
...nobody knows who I am.
"You will know soon enough."
This is what he meant when he said it.
Solitude.
Take a look at this.
"I'll be waiting for you at the ruins of the
Hilden & Engles warehouse in Romberg"
Johan was here this morning.
And he killed Göderich and his subordinates.
Now another man who knows me is gone.
Nina probably went there after seeing this message.
I want you to kill him.
What?
For real?
It is true!
We have to hurry and tell the people on Calvin Street!
I can't believe this!
Finally, I'm blessed with good luck!
What?
I'll use the fire to make that rug mine!
I'm so lucky!
You looter!
Y-You idiot!
Don't say it so loudly!
I can't let anyone hear about this!
Let me go!
Not just the people in town.
Think what would happen if the fascists overheard us.
Let me go!
We would never make it!
Especially with those skinheads with the swastika tattoos...!
I said let me go!
Was there a Turkish woman held in this mansion?
That women was found dead on the third floor.
That woman was the only person Johan didn't kill.
It was the work of one of Professor
Göderich's subordinates.
Do you think that man can kill Johan?
I don't know.
However...
...he might still make it in time.
What is this...?