This is the greatest scandal since the
formation of the Czech police.
Much to our regret, the three that were murdered...
all had ties with the former Czechoslovakian
secret police.
However, I would like to believe
that because of this incident...
any corruption within the Prague police
department has been wiped out.
You are all proud members of the Czech police.
I expect that you will act according to your conscience.
Furthermore...
as the new Chief of Police...
I will try hard to regain the trust of the people...
by carrying out a thorough reform.
I will now introduce the five members of the special
investigative task force from headquarters.
I would like all of you to make a concerted effort...
to join them in solving this awful
case as soon as possible!
You're Detective Suk, correct?
Yes, sir!
As the new Chief of Police, I would like to thank you...
for the investigative work you've done on this case.
Th-Thank you, sir.
By the way, what case are you assigned to right now?
The one that Inspector Zeman was assigned to.
It involves the murder of Mr. Petrov, the proprietor
of an unauthorized orphanage.
I see.
Please continue to devote your efforts to that case.
Yes, sir.
Please excuse me.
Oh, and one more thing.
Regarding the tall man who emerged as a
suspect in Inspector Zeman's murder...
Do you know anything with regard to this suspect?
No, I know nothing about that man.
I see.
You may go now.
Excuse me.
Jan Suk.
It's been a year since he was assigned
to the Prague station.
He's been close to Inspector Zeman
ever since he started out...
He uncovered both Detective Patera's
and Detective Janacek's hidden past...
and met with Chief of Police
Hamrik right before his death.
Put a tail on that man!
Yes, sir.
The Afterimage of the Monster
Hi.
I was glad when I called the hotel
you said you were staying at...
and you actually answered the phone.
Did you think you'd be betrayed again?
Well, no...
Orange juice, please.
Mr. Grimmer.
You said you wanted to meet in a crowded place like this...
but is it really okay?
What do you mean?
The new Chief of Police hasn't taken you off the
suspect list for Inspector Zeman's murder.
Also, you're being pursued by the former
Czechoslovakian secret police as well, right?
Oh, I suppose you're actually safer in crowded places...
There is no safe place.
If they want to get me, they can. Any time, any place.
For example...
from that window with the red curtains.
Mr. Grimmer, just who are you?
Just an unsuccessful journalist.
But...
But then, why are you going through all of this?
I guess I might've gotten too involved.
This isn't something to laugh about!
Your life is in danger...
No, it's okay.
I got involved because I wanted to.
Suk is currently at a cafe in Republic Square.
He's meeting with that tall man, as we suspected.
It's Grimmer, without a doubt.
Yes.
Should we let them hang out a little longer?
So this all happened to you while
you were investigating Petrov...
who was conducting brainwashing experiments
on children when he was in East Germany?
Yeah.
And right before his death...
Retrov entrusted you with that
key to a safety deposit box.
Yeah.
He also said something about the
development of a monster.
The development of a monster?
I don't understand what that means...
but it seems there are many people who
want to get their hands on that data.
The former secret police?
As well as that blonde woman.
The children at the orphanage also mentioned her.
The pretty blonde woman who left the house
right after Petrov was assassinated.
Do you have any idea who she is?
I haven't the slightest idea...
Are you okay?
You hid the fact that you're meeting me
like this from your superiors, right?
Is it okay to betray the police?
I'm not really hiding anything.
This is within my discretion as part of an investigation.
After I have thoroughly investigated the matter...
I intend to report it to the higher authorities.
If I do a good job, I can also prove your innocence.
What's wrong?
Don't look to your left too quickly.
The man under the umbrella to
your left, reading a newspaper.
He's strange.
The secret police...
Who knows?
Well then...
Shall we go?
Go?
Go where?
You brought it with you, right?
The key to the safety deposit box that I gave you.
Yes.
You want to know, don't you?
Who this monster is.
Yes.
All right, let's get going.
Though it may be better for us not to know.
You don't look so good.
Just now, I saw that woman...
Is anything wrong?
No.
I must've imagined it.
Suk is on the move.
I'm going to follow him.
I'm Suk, from the Prague Police, who called earlier.
Please wait a moment.
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
This way.
Please come in.
This is where our safety deposit boxes are kept.
Please check the contents of the box in that room.
Research papers and a cassette tape...
I have a tape recorder.
Ready?
I'm going to play it now.
Where is this place?
Kinderheim 511.
A child's voice?
What is your name?
My name is...
Johan.
What is your last name?
Let me ask you again.
My name is...
Otto.
Hans.
My name is...
Thomas.
Which one is your real name?
Once upon a time...
there lived a monster without a name.
The monster wanted a name so
badly that he couldn't stand it.
Is that a story of some kind?
I was waiting... for Anna.
Who is Anna?
I was waiting for Anna, while reading a picture book...
This boy was being interrogated after being drugged.
Who is your father?
I don't know.
What about your mother?
I think she's still alive.
You are a very talented child.
Are you afraid of anything?
What is it that you're most afraid of?
Let me change the question, then.
Have you ever killed anyone?
A lot of people were dead.
It was like Anna and I were the
only ones left in the world.
Where was that?
Then, let's go back to the other question.
What is it that you're most afraid of?
The monster inside of me is getting bigger.
Chomp chomp.
Munch munch.
Gulp.
Chomp chomp.
Munch munch.
Gulp.
Chomp chomp.
Munch munch.
Gulp.
What I am most afraid of...
That is...
I feel sick...
I feel like I'm going to throw up...
Are you okay, Mr. Grimmer?
Yeah...
Just what is this tape?
Is this the monster's identity?
I don't understand it at all.
Even if we don't understand the meaning of this tape...
there are people out there who'd do
anything to get their hands on it.
The former Czechoslovakian secret police...
Whether you listen to only part of the tape or the
entire thing, it doesn't make any difference.
There's no turning back now.
What are you going to do now?
Are you going to putt that tape and the research
papers back in the safety deposit box?
No.
Normally, they should be kept here as evidence, but...
You're going to hang on to them?
Then let's leave here separately.
It's probably me they're targeting anyway.
Oh, that's right.
Give me your cell phone number and your home address.
If we're both safe, let's contact each other.
I guess I made it home safely...
I have a bad feeling...
He seems to be unreliable after all.
A flat on Lenova Street...
Just what is the meaning of this?
That's what we'd like to know.
You know about us, correct?
You're with that special task force
that headquarters sent over.
This is Senior Detective Novacek.
I'm Senior Detective Janda.
And why are you both in my room?
How long have you been meeting with Grimmer?
You can't say you don't know what I'm talking about.
Just now, you met him at a cafe in Republic Square...
then you guys headed to Procházka Bank.
You know the man in this picture, don't you?
Colonel Karel Ranke.
He's a big shot in the underground
Czechoslovakian secret police.
I... I don't know that person!
We checked your bank account.
There seems to have been a large
sum deposited this month.
What was it for?
W-What are you talking about?
I don't know anything about that money
Your mother is currently hospitalized for a serious
illness at Krumlov National Hospital, correct?
I hear that it costs a lot just to pay
for her hospitalization, right?
What are you trying to say?
After your mother separated from your father...
she raised you all by herself.
And apparently, you care a lot about your mother as well.
Just what are you trying to say?!
We would like to search your room.
Do as you wish.
I have nothing to hide!
Do as you wish...
Janda, come here!
What is that...?
They were in your medicine cabinet.
I don't know...
I know nothing about them!
We can't say anything about the chemical content
until we analyze them at the station.
But in the stomachs of the three that were murdered...
the items they found that contained
the muscle relaxant...
were whisky bonbons.
Let's hear your story back at the station.
Very well.
Investigate it thoroughly.
I'm sorry.
But before that, could I at least change first?
Yeah, go ahead.
Calm down!
I didn't do anything wrong.
They'll understand if I explain it.
The smell of gunpowder...?
Suk!
Yes
Cherish what you know is true in this world.
Ima kono sekai de wakaru koto mitsumete
Yes
Please believe in the kindness of your eyes
Anata no hitomi no yasashisa wo shinjite
Make it home to your land of harmony
Make it home to your land of purity
Make it home