I...
brought him back to life.
brought that monster back to life...
This is it!
You found something?
Schuwald's library donation ceremony!
Is Tenma there?
Dieter, wait here!
Don't follow me!
Schuwald!
I want to see Hans Georg Schuwald.
Contact him.
Okay.
Oh, I think he's at the Munich University library...
donating his collection of books today.
We'll go there immediately.
Tenma's target is Schuwald.
Nina!
Lotte! You came!
I'm sorry.
I looked for him everywhere...
but he doesn't seem to be here, so...
Though we've become friends...
it's too bad...
You guys...
are twins, aren't you?
Am I right?
I'm right, aren't I?
What does this picture book mean?
He suddenly collapsed when he saw this.
A picture book...?
Once upon a time...
there lived a monster without a name.
The monster wanted a name so
badly that he couldn't stand it.
So the monster decided to go off on
a journey to find himself a name.
But because the world was so big...
the monster split in two and departed
in their separate ways.
One went east...
and the other went west.
The one that went east found a village.
There was a blacksmith at the village entrance.
"Mr. Blacksmith, please give me your name."
"I can't give you my name."
"If you give me your name..."
"I will jump inside you and make
you stronger in return."
"Really?"
"I'll give you my name if you can make me stronger."
The monster jumped inside the blacksmith.
The monster became Otto the blacksmith.
Otto the blacksmith was the strongest man in the village.
But one day...
"Look at me! Look at me!"
"The monster inside me has grown this big!"
Chomp. Munch. Crunch. Gulp.
The hungry monster ate Otto from the inside out.
He went back to being a monster without a name.
Even though he jumped inside Hans the shoemaker...
Chomp. Munch. Crunch. Gulp.
He went back to being a monster without a name again.
Even though he jumped inside Thomas the hunter...
Chomp. Munch. Crunch. Gulp.
He still went back to being a monster without a name.
The monster went to the castle to find a wonderful name.
Inside the castle, there was a very sick boy.
"I'll make you stronger if you give me your name."
"I'll give you my name if you can cure
my illness and make me stronger."
The monster jumped inside the hoy.
The boy became very healthy.
The king was delighted.
"The prince is well! The prince is well!"
The monster became fond of the boy's name.
He also grew fond of his life inside the castle.
That's why he endured even when he became hungry.
Every day, even when his stomach
became very empty, he endured.
But because he became so hungry...
"Look at me! Look at me!"
"The monster inside me has grown this big!"
The boy ate his father, his servants, and everyone.
Chomp.
Munch.
Crunch.
Gulp.
Because everyone was gone...
the boy left on a journey.
He walked and walked for days.
One day...
the boy met the monster that went west.
"I have a name."
"It's a wonderful name."
And then the monster that went west said...
"I don't need a name."
"I'm happy even if I don't have a name."
"Because we're monsters without names."
The boy ate the monster that went west.
Even though he now had a name...
there was no one left to call him by his name.
Johan.
It is a wonderful name.
A Monster Without a Name
You know this picture book, don't you?
Can you read Czech?
Are you Czech?
I don't know...
You don't know? But...
A long time ago...
I feel like someone read it to me... a long time ago...
Who are you?
Are you really Nina Fortner?
Tell me the truth!
Just who are you?!
I don't know...
You don't know? We're talking about you here!
How can you not know about yourself?!
Answer me!
Tell me what's going on!
Why did I get such a bad feeling
when I read this picture book?
That student, Fahren, who claimed to be
Schuwald's son, committed suicide!
The detective Schuwald hired fell to his death!
Even the prostitute who called herself
Margot Langer was shot and killed!
Why is it that after reading this book, all
the strange things happening recently...
feel like they're merging together to crush me?!
Why do I get the feeling that everything is tied to Johan?
I'm sorry...
I got a little too agitated...
The man who fainted after reading this book...
looks that much like me?
Like twins...
He looks so much like me that we could be twins?
This friend of yours, Johan?
Where is he now?
He's attending a book donation ceremony
at the university library...
Ah, h-hey!
Hey, Nina!
Hey, wait for me!
I said wait!
Today, thanks to the efforts of the head
of the Schuwald financial group...
Mr. Hans Georg Schuwald...
the University of Munich Friedrich Emmanuel
School Library has been bestowed with...
an enormous collection of books.
They are extremely important and precious.
It can be said that this is Germany's most valuable asset.
We have the responsibility to leave this...
vast amount of human knowledge...
to the younger generation!
Next, a word from the head of the
Friedrich Emmanuel School...
Professor Steinbeck!
Damn!
The trigger...
If I pull the trigger...
everything will be over, and yet...
Please move!
Help me, Doctor!
I don't want to die!
Doctor!
Mr. Mauler!
I have to shoot...
I have to shoot!
Now then, it's time for today's guest of honor to make his appearance!
He's not only the essence of the Bayern economy...
Watch carefully.
but he also has great influence in Europe's economic development.
This is how you shoot a gun.
And also, by donating his large collection
of books to the university...
he has done a great culturally
meritorious service to Bayern.
I take pride in being able to introduce this man to you.
Ladies and gentlemen of the audience...
Mr. Hans Georg Schuwald
This is how...
you shoot a gun!
So many people have gathered here. What a success...
Mr. Schuwald is certainly popular...
He really is...
And also, by donating his large collection
of books to the university...
he has done a great culturally
meritorious service to Bayern.
I take pride in being able to introduce this man to you.
Ladies and gentlemen of the audience...
Mr. Hans Georg Schuwald
The one you're after is me, isn't it?
There are many people gathered here...
They came in droves to see you...
I understand now...
What have you done...?
Whoa, don't make any noise!
Just shut up and watch.
Okay?
Everyone, I want you to listen to me...
I want you to stay calm and act rationally.
I can't see...
I don't know how many people are gathered here...
You mustn't all move at once...
That's it.
Just stay put.
Just watch what I'm about to do.
Slowly, in single file...
get away from here.
What is it?!
What happened?!
Over there, too?!
A short circuit?!
Fire!
Get the fire extinguisher!
Hurry!
What's going on?
My job was to shoot Schuwald.
What's with this fire?
I get it now!
You must've changed your mind Johan!
This is better!
This is much better!
Ants... They're all like ants running away from the fire!
Amazing! This is amazing, Johan!
This is marvelous!
Why don't you take a look, too?
The books!
All the books will burn!
They're all running around...
They're trampling one another, as if each
is more important than the rest...
Can you feel it?
The fear in the air?
I have to shoot...
That's impossible for you.
You can't shoot.
I have to... shoot...
You're just a doctor.
You can only save life.
Taking life is my job.
You can't do it.
Yes
Cherish what you know is true in this world.
Ima kono sekai de wakaru koto mitsumete
Yes
Please believe in the kindness of your eyes
Anata no hitomi no yasashisa wo shinjite
Make it home to your land of harmony
Make it home to your land of purity
Make it home