I was divorced three years ago.
Well, to be precise, my wife left me.
After all, I spent most of my
time listening to what was said here,
and not to what my wife said.
My wife said to me,
"You're just a collector who peers into human minds."
Doctor...
you're abnormal.
Perhaps.
The task of peering into the deep abyss
and lurking in the depths of the human mind
puts me at the inherent risk of sinking into the abyss myself.
So, your fourth victim was an
eighteen year old Munich woman, was it not?
When you cut her up, did you become sexually aroused?
Doctor...
Why don't you ask me about my twelfth victim instead?
That would be Ms. Hanna Kempf from the Klopp House,
fifty two years old, correct?
When it was her,
I--
No need.
I'm sure I'll ask you about it at some point,
but right now, I wanted to ask you
about the one before, the eleventh case.
Okay?
Well then, let me ask you this:
did you feel sexual excitement
before killing the victim,
or after?
As previously stated, the victims were limited to girls
Abyss of the Monster
with long hair, between the ages of sixteen and eighteen.
This case definitely should
be categorized as sexual murder.
However, he has also confessed to the twelfth case.
In this case, the victim, Ms. Kempf, was 52 years old,
and there was no evidence of sexual assault.
In addition, by stating that he
committed this murder at the request of a friend,
he has confused the investigation--
Who is it?
Who's there?
It's me, Rudy.
Tenma!
God, you scared me back there.
Sorry.
This was the only way I could come visit.
You know why, don't you?
Yeah, I've heard.
Do you believe that I am a serial killer?
I don't know.
I can't tell from newspaper articles,
stuff on TV, and rumors from
former university classmates alone.
But why did you come to visit me, of all people?
It's not as though we were particularly good friends.
Or rather, you looked down on me.
That is what I thought, every time our eyes met.
That you looked down on me.
Oh, I get it now.
You want me to repay what I
owed you from that time, huh?
Is it money?
No.  That's not it.
I hear you're an authority on criminal psychology.
I have something.
I'd like for you to see.
"Look at me!  Look at me!
The monster in me has grown this big, Dr. Tenma!"
"Help!  The monster within me is about to explode!"
What is this?
I see.
So, this Johan was the one
who killed the hospital director,
then killed each of his former foster parents, one by one,
and disappeared again after leaving this message.
I must find him as soon as possible!
And thereby prove your innocence as soon as possible.
Twenty years ago in the medical
sciences department of a certain university,
there was a man who had to be number one.
However, a Japanese man transferred in,
and the man's position changed completely.
The Japanese man was social
and become popular right away.
Additionally, he received good
marks and easily dislodged the man
from first place in the first semester exams.
The man
became desperate to regain his
position in the second semester exams.
He performed perfectly in all his subjects up to that point,
but the last test
was on general forensic medicine, the
subject in which he was the least capable.
If he failed that test, all of his
efforts up to then would be wasted.
He decided on a last resort.
"Now, I'll be number one."
However...
But the Japanese man didn't tell anyone.
As a result, the man made a great
comeback and regained first place.
So, is there anything you can
figure out from these two messages?
Whether he has the multiple
personality disorder you spoke of, you mean?
You want to say that one
personality is committing these murders
and that a different personality is trying to prevent them.
Certainly, there have been serial homicides
in which notes like these were left at the crime scene.
But, at times,
these notes can be an
"excuse" in order to escape culpability.
Making the distinction between the two
possibilities is where our skills as psychoanalysts come in.
Most people mistakenly believe
that serial killers are introverted,
but that is completely inaccurate.
There are those who are highly
intelligent, sociable, and smooth spoken.
They are compulsive liars, you see.
Is he...
toying with me?
Well, hang on there.  It's unwise to leap to conclusions.
Can you speak about Johan in more detail?
I was actually divorced three years ago.
Well, to be precise, my wife left me.
Thank you, Rudy.
That was an interesting story, Tenma.
I would like to do a complete study on this.
Please contact me in a week.
What do you think of this man?
I can understand him well.
Oh?
On what points?
The...
"monster" that he spoke of.
I see.
So the monster exists.
It does exist indeed...
in you, in him,
and also in myself.
Stop.
That's an armchair theory.
What?
I'm saying that a monster exists in this world.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Don't look at me like that!
I don't like being looked down on!
What are you...
Th-the guards...
Are you afraid?
Huh?
But listen,
there are things in the world that are more terrifying.
I'll tell you something good.
Thank you for your cooperation.
He will definitely come to see you, I hope?
He will.
I'll contact you right away when that happens.
However...
However?
I'd like for him to become one of my
research subjects after you arrest him.
He is an extremely interesting criminal,
that Dr. Tenma.
I'll tell you something good.
Go to Ms. Kempf's mansion.
The basement storage room.
If you go there, you'll understand.
There is proof...
that a monster exists.
Yes?
Hi, Tenma.
Yes, I'd love to meet with you.
Sure, okay.
I'll be waiting, then.
Is this Detective Köhl?
I've promised to meet up with Tenma.
It's at 8 o'clock this evening
in front of the fountain in Oder Park.
Well, then.
I am currently retracing
the route Jurgens took to break
into the house on the day of the crime.
According to his statement,
he hid in this storage room, and spent a few hours there.
Then immediately after Ms. Kempf returned home,
he forced his way into the second floor bedroom
and committed the crime.
There is nothing unusual about this room...
just...
some framed photos.
Many of them...
include Ms. Kempf.
A doll...
I don't see anything out of the ordinary.
There is nothing that would prove the existence
of the monster Jurgens mentioned.
Just as I'd thought, he committed the twelfth murder
to confuse the investigation.
He stated that he committed
the crime at a friend's request.
By calling that friend a monster...
When I was a kid,
my mom would punish me every day.
In the room,
there was a large doll that my mom
really treasured.
A girl doll with long hair.
I would ask the doll to help me as my mom beat me.
But that doll would only smirk at me as it watched.
That storage room was full of my mom's pictures, too.
No matter where I looked,
it was my mom, mom, mom, mom...
She would be watching me all the time.
What is going on here?
It's just like the room he described.
Did Jurgens recreate
the storage room from his childhood here?
This is
Jurgens when he was a child.
Impossible...
He never had any contact with
Ms. Kempf during his childhood.
What is this photograph?
Jurgens' face was added on?
This one too!
This too,
and this one too!
This too!
Ms. Kempf had no children.
This boy...
Who are you?
There is proof...
that a monster exists.
I just did exactly what was written in my friend's letter.
F-friend...?
One day,
I got a white envelope that didn't
have the sender's name or address.
At first, I was irritated
by the peculiar friendly letter,
in which he said he understood me.
Then the letters started coming every week.
He likes letters.
But at some point,
I started looking forward to these letters.
Those letters were fun.
I thought...
that he might actually be a friend.
And one day,
the letter told me to go somewhere.
It told me to go to a storage room in a mansion.
The storage room in Ms. Kempf's mansion?
I wonder how he knew.
I wonder how
he knew about my childhood.
At. Ms. Kempf's mansion, I became disoriented.
What's going on?
Is Ms. Kempf...
my mom?
When I regained my senses, I
was already on the second floor and...
He likes letters.
His friend also sent letters to Ms. Kempf?
This is...
This too!
And this.
"Look at me!
Look at me!
The monster in me has grown this big!"
"Help!
The monster within me is about to explode!"
They are messages that Johan left.
They are the same.
The friend...
Johan...
exists!
He's not here yet?
Eight o'clock came and went a long time ago.
Detective Köhl.
That's...
He's here.
We have an Asian with longish hair.
Sorry for making you take time away from work, Rudy.
I tried to analyze what you said.
I thought they were all lies.
I thought Johan didn't exist anywhere
and that he was an imaginary person you had thought up.
Rudy, please listen to me.
I--
At the moment, I am studying a serial killer named Jurgens,
but there was one murder in which
his methods differed from his usual ones.
Please listen to me instead of talking about him!
Okay folks, that's it for today!
Please come again!
The carnival is finished.
Tell everyone
to secure him at my signal.
Understood.
Listen to every single word of their conversation, got it?
Tenma,
you looked down on me, didn't you?
Ever since you saw me cheating at the university,
you've been looking down on me.
Isn't that right?
Detective Köhl,
this isn't good.
Dr. Galen and Tenma are walking toward the west exit.
They will mingle with the crowd of
people going home after the carnival.
Indeed, I am someone who should be looked down on.
Rudy, now is not the time-
Do you remember?
I had the cheat sheet hidden here.
Like this.
"Run!
You're surrounded by the police."
Don't look.  Let's keep on walking.
Is the doctor being threatened?
W-well, the people around them are so
noisy that we can't pick up their voices...
What?
Wait!
Jurgens said that he killed Ms. Kempf at a friend's request.
Th-this is...
It was in Ms. Kempf's storage room.
Ms. Kempf didn't have any children.
The Johan you spoke of and the friend of Jurgens spoke of
are probably the same person.
They have passed through the west exit.
Shall we go get him?
Wait!
Tenma may have a gun!
The same messages as Johan's
were at Ms. Kempf's mansion.
Johan lived off of Ms. Kempf,
then killed her when he didn't need her anymore.
It may be to erase his past, as you said.
You are innocent.
I'm not in any position to preach at you.
but I'll tell you the result of my analysis.
I don't know how,
but Johan can detect killers.
He can infiltrate their solitude
and manipulate them.
Also, as to why you haven't
found any cases where he murdered
the foster parents he had when he was older...
It's probably because
he is at an age where he no longer needs foster parents.
There are other possible reasons, though.
Johan has finally found and joined
the ideal family.
Still, why does he try to erase his past?
Is there a reason he needs to?
If so, then is he currently with
a family for a particular purpose?
To accomplish something...
Now,
we have arrived at the bus terminal.
Confirm which bus he boards!
Get cars to the terminal!
Prepare for pursuit!
Understood!
I bought the bus ticket for you in advance.
Tenma,
there is the option of giving yourself
up, and then proving your innocence.
I'll help you.
I...
I am not pursuing Johan in order to prove my innocence.
What?
Thank you,
Rudy.
Tenma,
you aren't possibly thinking of...
Oh, right.
I wasn't looking down on you.
It's the truth.
I thought you looked like an interesting guy,
but I didn't get a chance to get to know you.
However, we've finally become friends.
But...
you saw me cheating...
You raised your head and looked toward me...
I was cheating too.
What?
Five buses departed almost all at the same time?
Tenma...