First, it was so many flowers that they wouldn't
even fit in the dressing room.
Next, it was brand name clothes and bags.
And then the biggest jewels I've ever seen in my life.
I had no idea who was sending them to me.
It was you, wasn't it?
I felt something special when I first saw your show.
Special?
My breasts?
Or my ass?
Something you can't see with your eyes.
You should have come to the dressing
room to meet me in person.
Someone like me?
What are you talking about?
For some reason...
you seem like you might actually listen to me.
The Baby's Depression
This is delicious!
I've never had anything so good
Eat as much as you like.
Do you always eat food like this?
Yeah.
But depending on one's dining companions,
the meal can taste either good or bad.
I usually eat alone, so...
Do you usually eat with a group of people?
Yes, I pay many people to come dine with me.
Why would you do something like that?
I wonder why?
Now that I think about it...
no matter how many people
I invite, or how lively it gets...
I always feel like I'm eating alone.
How about now?
I'm having a wonderful time.
I'm so glad!
Would you dine with me like this from now on?
Sure.
But I think I'll get tired of eating food like this all the time.
Things have been strange lately.
What do you mean?
I've never felt like this before.
I built my kingdom here in Frankfurt.
I fought to create a new order.
My dream was to be like General Hitler...
My dream is to become a dancer.
What I'm doing now is a little different, though...
But everyone's eyes are glued to me when I dance.
I feel so good when I dance, and...
I'm scared.
I've never felt like this before.
What are you trying to say?
No, well, uh...
Regarding the three murders that took
place over the last few months...
It must be Johan's will.
Y-Yes...
It's exactly as you say.
I understand the meaning behind the murder of
Fritz Overt from the Bilker Investment Bank...
and the daughter of the general
store owner, Frieder Schelling.
Scandal cover-ups...
We were aware of these two.
However...
The foreign trader, Erich Klemperer.
Do you know this man?
No, I don't.
That was probably unrelated to Johan.
Is that really true?
Do we really know what Johan's doing?
Or are you hiding something from me?
There is nothing to worry about.
More importantly...
have you located Nina?
After leaving the psychiatrist's home in Munich...
it appears she came here to Frankfurt.
Isn't securing Nina our top priority?
I don't believe you're aware of Nina's true nature.
Please don't forget that she's Johan's sister.
Those eyes back then...
On the night of the burning of the Turkish district...
Those eyes, as she pointed the gun at me...
It gives me chills just thinking of them.
Isn't that wonderful?
Are you talking about the program you created?
I was merely assisting.
Everything is proceeding according to my master's...
Everything is going according to
the program he has created.
Are things really proceeding according to the program?
Oh, there it is!
That's my favorite!
This time, it's on me.
Isn't it good?
It's the best ice cream in Frankfurt.
Yes.
I haven't felt this relaxed in a while.
I've been so stressed lately.
Why?
I wonder why?
You don't need to put so many bodyguards around me.
That's what Mr. Čapek has ordered.
You don't have to worry.
Even if I go for a walk...
there aren't many people who would recognize me.
No, there would be more trouble if we
let you do whatever you wanted.
Who's doing as he pleases?
Three people have died to cover up your scandal.
Well, I can kill as many people
as I want and not get caught.
Who do you think gave you your current power?
The four leaders of the organization.
Professor Göderich.
General Wolf.
Mr. Čapek.
And your late father.
You seem to think that you've succeeded him.
However, things aren't that simple.
The question is whether or not you
are worthy of that position.
Are you saying that you're meant to take that position?
I know all the scandals that surround you.
Then you should also know what happens
to those who know about them.
You've got a long way to go before you
can even think about threatening me.
I'd never dream of making you my enemy.
Not a leader of Frankfurt's extreme right wing.
I had fun.
Me, too!
I'm glad I asked you out today.
You can ask me out any time you want.
It's been a while since I enjoyed walking around
town without a bodyguard like this.
Are you going to be okay?
Do you want me to walk you back?
You?
You're saying that you'll protect me?
I'll be fine.
My hotel is right there.
That's amazing!
You live in a hotel?
This isn't much, but...
I don't want it.
Goodbye.
It's my usual habit!
I apologize!
I've always...
bought people with money.
Can I come up?
To your hotel room?
Everyone calls you "The Baby," but...
what's your real name?
My name is...
Yes.
We've located the twin sister.
I just called The Baby, but he isn't answering.
I'm going directly to his room.
Yes.
Goodbye.
Hello?
Yes, it's me.
T-The Baby has...
The Baby has been...
He's been murdered!
Come with me.
Don't be afraid.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Are you okay, Mr. Čapek?
You don't look very well.
Anyway, please forgive my rude question, but...
you weren't the one who killed The Baby, correct?
That's a ridiculous question.
We just need to make sure.
By dawn...
news of The Baby's death will have spread.
With the death of The Baby...
the balance of the organization
will be completely destroyed.
We have no idea how things will turn out now.
We are bodyguards.
We will carry out the jobs given to us.
However, if you were the one who killed him...
then protecting you will be a farce.
Why do you think I ordered you two to protect me...
immediately after I heard about The Baby's death?
Because you felt something was
going to happen to you next?
You have an idea about who killed The Baby?
Do we really know what Johan's doing?
What are you afraid of?
Everything is going according to plan.
Everything is...
proceeding according to the program.
Very well.
We'll move you somewhere safe.
I have a small house in Idstein.
I haven't told anyone about that place.
I'll stay there for the time being.
More importantly, the twin sister!
You said you found out where she is.
Yes.
She's here in Frankfurt.
At a cheap hotel called the Tourette.
Securing that girl will be the best guarantee
of my safety right now.
Then tomorrow morning, we'll...
Right now!
Very well.
I've made a call to have two other guards
protect you at your house in Idstein.
Good.
Last night, The Baby sent his bodyguards
home for some reason...
He acted by himself, and that's what happened.
You have us with you.
Please don't worry.
Good.
You were also saved from the assassination attempt
the other day at the convention center.
You're a very lucky person.
Milan!
Listen to me!
I met a wonderful person!
Nice to meet you.
I'm Peter Čapek.
You showed me something truly wonderful!
Could you tell me more about your readings?
I want to know about your completely new...
You should read these.
Everything is drawn in there.
How beautiful!
Such beautiful children!
These children are the ones who will
become the leaders of tomorrow...
according to your program. Right, Franz Bonaparta?
The car...
Stop the car!
What's the matter?
Your house is just up ahead, over this mountain road.
What did you say earlier?
There will be two other bodyguards?
Yes, at the house.
They should be there already.
Is there a chance those two would
leak the information to others?
Can you guarantee that the information
about me going to my house...
hasn't been leaked?
Yes.
They are both very trustworthy.
We're not going to the house.
Wait a minute.
Then... where are we going?
Whatever the case, we're not going to the house.
But it's pointless to keep driving at night like this.
That's an order.
I understand your life is in danger, but...
for now, let's head to the house.
A lighter?
He wasn't going for his gun?
It's me!
Is anyone... here?
Johan!
Many people drank that red wine...
at the Red Rose Mansion.
It's all right.
See? I'm drinking it, too.
Where are...
the bodyguards that were supposed to be here?
Why?
Why did you kill The Baby?
We were supposed to be on the same side.
You were supposed to help us.
We were supposed to look for your sister and bring her...
Everything is going according to plan.
What about your sister?
We already located her.
If something happens to me...
your sister will...
It won't go the way you want.
Listen, everything is going according to my plan.
What am I?
The monster I thought was inside me...
wasn't inside.
It was outside.
What are you trying to say?
Isn't Franz Bonaparta...
alive?
Yes
Cherish what you know is true in this world.
Ima kono sekai de wakaru koto mitsumete
Yes
Please believe in the kindness of your eyes
Anata no hitomi no yasashisa wo shinjite
Make it home to your land of harmony
Make it home to your land of purity
Make it home