It's me! Is anyone...
here?
Johan!
Many people drank that red wine...
at the Red Rose Mansion.
It's all right.
See? I'm drinking it, too.
Where are the bodyguards that were supposed to be here?
Why?
Why did you kill The Baby?
We were supposed to be on the same side.
You were supposed to help us.
We were supposed to look for your sister and bring her...
Everything is going according to plan.
What about your sister?
We already located her.
If something happens to me, your sister will...
It won't go the way you want.
Listen, everything is going according to my plan.
What am I?
The monster I thought was inside me...
wasn't inside.
It was outside.
What are you trying to say?
Isn't Franz Bonaparta...
alive?
Johan's Footprints
Sorry for coming this late.
Ms. Nina Fortner...
Ms. Fortner?
Ms. Nina Fortner?
Don't move!
Who asked you to come here?
I see.
Just as The Baby said, she's not your average girl.
The Baby...?
Did you come here on orders from The Baby?
No.
The Baby's dead.
He's d...
Peter Čapek was the one who told us to bring you in.
He said he'd be safe...
if we took you hostage.
Čapek...
Take me, then.
I'll go with you to see Peter Čapek.
We're the police.
We're here to search the residence of Milan Kolasch...
who is suspected in the shooting at
the Rodelheim Convention Center.
Begin the search.
Out of the way.
Hey, get out of the way.
Is that Kolasch's room?
Seems like it.
The police will come to search the house soon.
I have to go.
What happened to Milan?
Did Milan really die?
Milan...
Milan died for our sake.
Čapek killed our families...
For our sake...
he tried to take revenge, and got killed.
Revenge...
Revenge!
No!
You must not think that!
But...
But Milan...
Milan...
Milan wouldn't want this.
Revenge leads to revenge...
You'll just go back and forth, again and again.
Milan wouldn't have wanted you to think like that.
Somebody has to stop it.
Milan was trying to stop it.
What did Milan truly want?
To travel with everyone and visit all of our hometowns.
Study hard.
That dream will come true someday.
Thank you for letting me stay, Mr. Mustafa.
Ms. Minh...
Ms. Suleiman...
Thank you for your delicious meals.
Dr. Tenma...
You're not going to...
There's a lot of material regarding
a man named Peter Čapek.
Oh, it looks like...
Milan Kolasch was after Čapek.
Find this man as soon as possible.
I want to question him...
Inspector!
At the Kaiser Hotel, a man known as "The Baby"...
the leader of an extreme right organization...
has been found murdered!
Somebody has to...
I have to...
stop it.
The young man coming in and out
of this hotel with Peter Čapek...
He's the devil's disciple.
Follow that car.
Johan?
Are you here, Johan?
Where were you, Johan?
If I remember correctly, you are... Eva.
Where?
Where is Johan right now?
Mr. Čapek?
I brought Nina.
Peter...
Čapek...
Now, come here.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Hey!
Wait, freeze!
Who is it?
Johan...
or his sister?
Right now, it doesn't really matter.
Johan has kept me alive...
because the one who is going to kill me...
is his sister.
Everything is going according to plan...
Whose plan?
Mine?
Johan's?
Just whose...
Whose plan is it?
Hurry up and kill me.
Johan was here, wasn't he?
Where did he go?
Take me to him.
Where is Johan right now?
It's totally dark.
I'm scared.
I want to get out of here.
If we go outside now...
I wonder if it's still going on...
Killing each other...
If only I hadn't led you...
to the devil...
at the banquet hall...
If I hadn't done that...
Martin...
wouldn't have died.
I understand.
Please wait a moment.
Where is Johan?
I don't know.
I also want to know where he is.
Calm down.
I've been watching this apartment for two weeks.
He never showed up.
Where could he be?
I just said that...
I don't know.
Really...
My ear! My ear!
I'm serious.
Owww! That hurts!
It won't be your ear next time...
Christoph Sievernich.
I know all about you...
Though I'd already heard of your late father, Ernest.
In Frankfurt... no, in Germany...
the Sievernich financial group
is one of the largest powers.
I can't believe that you're the heir to the company.
What is Peter Čapek trying to do by
bringing you and Johan together?
I'm bleeding too much!
Please, let me treat it.
What did I start...
when I led you to that devil?
No, that's not it...
What's not it?
Čapek thinks he's the one who brought us together...
but Johan and I...
were friends a long time ago.
What did you say?
Čapek doesn't know about it.
We were friends in East Berlin over ten years ago.
Over ten years ago...
in East Berlin?
I'm Sievernich's adopted son.
I was sold by an agent on the black market.
The place where Johan and I first met was in East Berlin...
at Kinderheim 511.
511...
We got to know each other there...
and survived.
Only he and I...
survived.
I'm scared.
I'm hungry, too.
I need to pee.
Do you think they're done killing each other?
I wonder if everyone's dead...
Let's go find out.
We'll be fine.
It's gotten real quiet outside.
It'll be all right.
Go and see.
We'll go crazy if we stay in here.
I-I'm going to go see.
If it's fine, come back and let us know, okay?
Okay...
I don't know why, but...
on that day, everyone at Kinderheim 511 went crazy.
Not just the children. The instructors
also started killing each other.
He didn't come back.
He must have run away.
He must have escaped, leaving us here.
No way!
He wanted to survive.
You think so?
If you think I'm lying, go check it out.
He must be eating a warm meal by now.
A warm meal?
I'll go and see.
You won't betray me, right?
Of course not!
He didn't come back, either.
I'm going to hide forever.
Hungry and thirsty...
I drifted in and out of sleep.
Am I going to die like this?
He was standing there.
There's only you and me.
I have a plan.
And that was Johan?
It's a big joke that Čapek thinks it's his plan.
We talked about it thousands of times when we were kids.
About what?
What is his plan?
You want to know?
It is...
You can't do that!
You can't shoot my ear!
A politician's face is his life!
Don't do that!
I'm going to change the world.
Huh? Isn't that right?
With Johan's help, I'm going to make the world mine.
Isn't that right?
What are you going to do about my ear?
Don't spoil my plans!
Don't do that!
Drop the gun!
Kenzou!
Johan told me...
"When my sister arrives, tell her where I am."
"After that, my sister will kill me."
Why don't you kill me?
Have you regained all of your memories?
Yes.
Then why don't you...
kill me?
Your heart is full of hatred, anger and...
sadness, right?
What are we?
You know, right
I heard.
How you twins were created.
Yes
Cherish what you know is true in this world.
Ima kono sekai de wakaru koto mitsumete
Yes
Please believe in the kindness of your eyes
Anata no hitomi no yasashisa wo shinjite
Make it home to your land of harmony
Make it home to your land of purity
Make it home