Come on, let's not waste time here.
Let's just go!
Geez.  Oh, man...
I'm hungry, I'm broke...
If only I had that carpet... Dammit...
Huh?
What is this?
Th-This is...
"Help!  The monster within me is about to explode!"
Within Johan... there are two personalities!
The Fifth Spoonful of Sugar
So, this was what happened:
When you stopped by that warehouse,
the Asian man and the arsonist were already fighting.
and the Asian ran away when he noticed you.
Is this correct, Miss Anna Liebert?
Yes.
Well, the suspect is a man from a fascist group.
And he's admitted his crime by talking about
some fire for a festival for some ethnic group.
Also, we've confirmed your identity,
so you may go for today.
Then, I can go home now?
Yes.
Oh...
and...
the people in that town called the Asian "Dr. Tenma."
Would you happen to know anything about him?
I don't know anything.
What do you think?
Judging by her appearance,
don't you think she was trying to
become a prostitute in this town?
Not about her.
I mean Dr. Tenma.
That's what the people from the Turkish town
called that Asian.
But, after we told them he was
a suspect in a series of homicides.
we began our questioning,
and every single one of them
said that they had no idea who he was.
I acted as your guardian this time.
Mr. Rosso...
Are you alright, Anna?  I was worried!
You just disappeared all of a sudden!
You changed clothes.
Yes,
that's better.
That stuff you were wearing didn't suit you.
You must be hungry!
Eat!
Mr. Rosso, aren't you having anything?
I already ate.
I'll just have some coffee.
Come on, eat!
Okay.
Thank you.
What?
I see you still put five spoonfuls of sugar in your coffee.
Of course.
Coffee is no good if it's not sweet.
You finally smiled.
You looked so depressed, even
though you're here for a job interview.
Is it so funny that I put so much sugar in my coffee?
Uh... Anna...?
Oh...
Anna Liebert.
Uh...
Of course you are hired!
How can I refuse?
With such a pretty girl working here,
my restaurant will get plenty of business.
It's just that...
Just that...?
You should...
smile a bit more.
Don't let your pretty face go to waste.
Thank you!
I'll do my best!
You don't have to be so gung-ho about it.
After all, this is an Italian restaurant
in the middle of nowhere.
Being "busy" here doesn't mean much.
Go around that way.
Okay.
I'll put the food out here.
You take them to the customers.
Put the empty plates on the right side of the bar counter.
The wines are here
and the glasses go on the shelf here.
There is also wine on top of the bar.
The orders should go here.
The wine goes on top of the bar,
the glasses go over there...
This is the water.
Okay.
Hey there.
Welcome!
Man, I'm hungry...
Whaaa?
Pleased to meet you.
I'm Anna.
"Pleased to meet you?"
Hey, you're not going to be working
as a waitress in this restaurant, are you?
Huh?
And what's wrong with this restaurant?
Of course, Anna is going to be our waitress from now on.
Nice to meet you.
Are you serious?
Wow...
Anna, can I get a carbonara?
Anna, I'd like a bolognese.
Anna, could you come over here and give me some water?
Sure, in a second!
An order of carbonara and bolognese here.
All right.
Thanks for waiting.
Thank you.
Here is the vongole and rigatoni,
and the fettuccine too!
Okay!
Hey Rosso,
where did you pick up a cutie like her?
I don't have to pick up anybody!
Anna,
I could take you out to somewhere better than this place.
How about it?  Tonight?
Hey!
If you hurt my valuable waitress,
you won't get away with it!
Oh wow, that cry-baby Rosso is talking like he's got guts!
Here is the thing, Anna.
He started crying when he
was watching a movie at my house.
Sh-
Sh-shut up!
An extra order of squid ink risotto!
Oh, hm...
They are playing "Summertime."
Huh?
They are playing "Summertime" at the classic movie theater.
See?
Isn't that great?
Frankfurt has so many movie theaters.
It was showing on TV the other day.
Man, I cried so much.
Have you seen it?
I see.
The movie takes place in a city in Italy called Venice.
Venice is a city from medieval times,
and is known as a city of water.
It was originally built on a lagoon.
That's why there are
waterways running throughout the city.
I would like to take you there some time.
Have you been there, Mr. Rosso?
Yeah.
And the music in the movie is great.
I'm sure that you have
at least heard the theme song once before.
How does it go?
Let's see...
I've got an idea!
Why don't we go see it now?
Maybe we can still get in.
Oh, yeah...
But...
I see.
You would run late if you went now.
Yeah.
I'm home!
Welcome back.
Oh,
I'll do that.
Don't worry about it.
I'm sorry.  Thanks for letting me off work in the afternoons.
It's alright.
We don't get many customers at this time anyway.
I don't mean to ask questions, but...
Where are you going every day?
Oh, forget about it.
It's none of my business what you do on your break.
I go to... practice shooting.
Shooting?
Yes.
I go to Mr. Venkel's shooting range.
Oh, you go to Venkel's place?
Yep, he's a good guy.
Mr. Rosso, have you ever fired a gun?
Guns?  No way!
I get the shakes from just seeing one.
Here you go.  Enjoy.
Thank you.
I wonder how it turned out this time?
Try it.
What can you taste?
The garlic, the olive oil, and the parsley...
Then you've probably killed the
taste of the other stuff you in there.
Yeah.
Then, that's not real pasta.
This is hard.
It's all about training.
Mr. Rosso, the bathroom is open now.
Goodni -
I can't believe there was a
movie like this when I was young.
Mr. Rosso...
you were always crying while watching movies.
Yeah.
When I was young, I didn't have the time for movies,
even when I wanted to watch them.
I know I ate a lot of good food back then,
but I can't remember the taste of a single thing I ate.
I didn't even know the taste of sugar.
The taste of sugar?
You know about me,
don't you?
I also checked you out,
after you left.
Nina Fortner.
Missing, after her parents were
murdered by unidentified individuals.
What did you want me to do?
Was it a job?
Did you want me to teach you?
I thought about having you... teach me.
How did you figure out who I was?
There was a law professor at my college,
who had been researching you.
The Ristorante Nino homicide,
the Sacco-Milano case,
and the bomb assassination of Mr. Sabatini.
In each of the three murder cases,
you were summoned as a possible suspect,
even though all were committed using different methods.
However, none of the cases were
prosecuted, due to lack of evidence.
But,
the professor had an interesting hypothesis,
in which you were...
undoubtedly a professional hitman.
An extremely top notch one, at that.
How many people do you think I have killed?
To be honest, I don't know either.
It started when I was a kid.
I was a member of the organization before I knew it.
Stealing, extortion... I could do anything.
In the end, I was a killer.
I could eat good food with the rewards.
It wasn't a big deal;
it was my job.
It was the same routine on that day, also...
just like on all the other days.
It was a café in the middle of the day.
I aimed my gun at this person I didn't know,
who might have been the hundredth person I would kill.
That person...
had ordered coffee.
Then, he began to put sugar in his coffee.
One spoonful.
Two spoonfuls.
Three spoonfuls.
Four spoonfuls.
When he put the fifth spoonful of sugar in,
the taste of the coffee I usually
drank spread through my mouth.
That person drank the coffee as if it tasted great.
And then I put my down my gun.
Just like that.
Just like that, and I couldn't kill anyone anymore.
Why didn't you ask me to teach you how to kill
during the six months you were with me?
Because...
Because I realized I shouldn't force you to get involved...
Do you have to go?
Well, then...
Thank you, Mr. Rosso.
Killing people is easy.
Just forget the taste of sugar.