He has returned to Heaven.
All that remains of Richard Brawn is an empty shell.
His soul shall live on forever in eternity.
Let us swear to his soul that we will live on with hope.
Let us open our Bibles to Psalm 23.
This is too much...
What a sad funeral...
He was an outstanding detective...
...yet not one of his colleagues came to his funeral.
He caused a lot of problems by drinking on the job.
Eventually, he fell to his death, totally drunk.
That's what the police said, right?
I heard Richard was supposed to meet with
his daughter the day after he died.
I...
What did I do for him?
Dr. Reichwein...
I just sat there and listened to his story,
then told him he had recovered!
What was I able to do for him?
Dr. Tenma...
If we can find him, we may be able
to find out what really happened.
Dr. Tenma...
Don't you think it's strange, Doctor?
That was no accident, nor was it suicide...
Richard was on the phone talking with his
daughter just a few hours before he died.
They were to meet the next day...
Doctor, you did everything you could for him.
And Richard really did recover.
Please don't blame yourself.
A Decision
Listen to this, Doc...
Ever since I found out about his affair,
he hasn't said a word to me.
Day after day, he just washes the
car, then mows the lawn...
He won't even look at me...
It's better than when he didn't bother coming home...
...but if this continues, I might go crazy.
Are you listening, Doc?
Y-Yeah, please continue.
And when I went to that woman's place...
...what do you think happened, Doc?
Murder?  No, that was simply an accident.
That night Richard Brawn went up to the roof of Building
#12 at the University of Munich by himself...
...downed a bottle of whiskey, and
fell to his death, dead drunk.
The bottle... did you follow up on that?
Yes, and Richard's fingerprints were all over it.
Can I see that bottle?
Well.. sure, but it's broken.
Richard...
Don't you think it's strange?
Richard was on the phone talking with his
daughter just a few hours before he died.
They were to meet the next day...
Yeah, this guy was definitely here that night.
Was he alone?
I don't remember.
So you know he was here, but you don't
remember if he was with anyone?
Well, he only ordered coffee.
Coffee?
It's rare for someone to order coffee here at that hour.
Was this young man with him at that time?
I'm not sure...
Please, try to remember.
I don't know!
A lot of customers are always coming and going.
But it's true that he bought a bottle of whiskey.
It's written on the bill.
Did Richard really buy that?
I don't remember!
The bill just says "Racke, one bottle."
What did you just say?
Racke, one bottle.
Why didn't I notice that when I saw
the label at the police station?
Huh?
Have you been drinking again?
Well, umm...
Just a little.
What did you have?
Whiskey.
I only ever drink whiskey.
Hmph!
You're filling the room with the smell of Racke.
Racke?
Are you kidding?
I'd never drink such vile domestic whiskey!
I only drink genuine Scotch whiskey!
Nothing else!
Richard didn't buy that whiskey.
Johan...
Was it him?
Wait!
Hey, wait!
Hey!
What?
Why did you try to push me?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Don't play innocent!
Huh?
Hey, pops.
You need something from my friend?
Die, bastard!
Who wanted you to do this?
Consider your age.
An old man is better off taking care of his grandkids.
Hey, w-wait!
Huh?
I used to be in the border police.
Why did you try to push me?
I... I don't know!
Don't underestimate a former police officer.
Someone asked me to...
Who asked?
A big guy!
A big guy?
I saw this big guy in the subway.
He gave me some money to push you off the platform.
I bought this for you, Richard.
It's genuine Scotch.
You wanted a drink, right?
It's fine now.
Drink as much as you want.
Richard, leave it to me.
I'll definitely figure it out.
Who...
...Johan is.
Listen, Doc.  I told my husband.
"Your habit of having affairs is like a disease."
"Why don't you see a doctor and get some counseling?"
Doc, are you listening to me?
Huh?
Yes, of course, Mrs. Hesse.
So what do you think?
He's not changing, so I'm only
going to get more depressed.
You're not really depressed.
Huh?
Rather, I'm more concerned about you husband, silently
washing the car and mowing the lawn every day.
You think so, too?
He is strange.
Doc, please, could you see him?
Sure.
Let's see...
How about 5 PM the day after tomorrow?
I'll ask him.
Smack some sense into the big oaf!
Doctor, was she the last patient for today.
Okay, then you can go home, Mehres.
See you later.
Oh, Mehres, you forgot to lock
the back door yesterday, too.
Oh, no!
I almost forgot to do it today, too!
No, I did it again...
Take it easy.
Hello?  Dr. Gillen?
This is Reichwein.
I saw it in the newspaper.
Your advertisement.
"Let's reminisce about our cheating.  Rudi."
Will Dr. Tenma really contact us because of this ad?
Yes, if Tenma reads it, he will.
Only he and I know what it means.
I see.
Doctor, please don't do anything
reckless before he shows up.
I know.
But there is one thing I need to find out.
What's that?
There is a prostitute who impersonated Margot Langer.
Richard told me about her...
There was a young man with Fahren, the boy who
committed suicide, when he went to see that woman.
A handsome young man with blond hair.
Please be careful, Doctor.
I know.
I'll be careful, so I'll be able to figure out everything.
For Richard's sake.
I'll get in touch with you later.
Mehres...
You forgot to close the window today.
Margot Langer?
Don't know her
I think she currently goes by
the name of Sofie something...
Oh, that fat old woman.
Is she your kind of girl?
No, I'm not like that...
There is no need to be shy at your age.
Turn at the second corner, and she's on
the second floor of the old building.
Thanks.
She's not there, though.
Oh?
I haven't seen her lately.
I guess she's gone somewhere nice.
Somewhere nice?
Geez, why on earth is that fat old woman so popular?
I heard an incredibly rich man used
to come by her place until recently.
Where did she go?
Hey, how about me, gramps?
I'll show you a much better time than
that old woman ever would.
Do you know where she went?
I don't know.
Maybe she went somewhere with the new guy.
The new guy/
Yeah, she was all over him.
He's a big guy.
A big guy?
Looked like he was big down there, too.
Doctor, can I leave for today?
Oh, yeah, you work til 5 PM today, huh?
The only other patient for today is the
unfaithful husband, so it's okay.
Don't you have a date, Mehres?
Please, Doctor!
Please don't forget to lock up.
If I show this picture to Sofie, the Margot Langer
impersonator, and if she confirms that...
...the young man who was with Fahren was indeed Johan...
...I'm one step closer to the truth...
Yes?
It's Hesse, my wife made an appointment for me today.
Please come in.
Should I try visiting that woman's place again tonight?
Please to meet you, Dr. Reichwein.
Nice to meet you too, Mr. Hesse.
How do you do?
Please come in.
I've never been to see a counselor before, so...
You don't need to be nervous.
Please relax, and talk about anything you like.
Whatever you say here will stay strictly confidential
between you and me, so please don't worry.
Even to my wife?
Of course.
How have you been recently?
Are you worried about anything?
Worried?
Yes.
My wife found out that I was having an affair.
I see.
So when I'm at home, I don't know what to do.
I mow the lawn, or wash my car.
Every day passes like that.
Do those things make you feel better?
No.
I don't talk to my wife at all.
You mean, even though you want to
talk, you don't know where to start?
Well, I'm not sure.
What about the other woman?
Huh?
The woman you're having an affair with...
I killed her.
Huh?
No, I dreamt that I killed her.
Do you have that kind of dream often?
Often?
No, I haven't had it lately.
I was lonely.
That's why you had an affair.
No, since I met him...
Him?
A handsome young man with blond hair.
Even if I killed lots of people, or
even if this country collapsed...
...everything was like a dream to me.
But since I met him, things have changed.
Everything seems so real, and I'm no longer lonely.
W-Would you like some tea?
No, I'm fine.
I'm a little thirsty.
Could you excuse me for a minute, please?
My secretary went home already.
It seems that she had a date.
She makes really good tea, but I'm
afraid I won't be able to serve it.
Doctor.
W-What is it?
With this kind of career, you must go through a lot.
Getting to know people's dreams...
It's no good if you learn of dreams you shouldn't know.
Especially the fact that I'm a murderer.
A-Anyway, if you and your wife
want to start over together...
...you should start by talking.
Please, I hope you forgot to lock the back door, Mehres!
Y-You...!
Quickly, run!
Dr. Tenma!
I've been watching you!
You're being targeted!
Run!
Hurry!