Reichwein Counseling Center
(Munich)
Have you had any liquor since?
Not a single drop.
That's good.
As long as you stay away from the stuff,
you can turn over a new leaf.
I've been unable to drink since I
started seeing you each week...
I'm scared to death of your angry thunderstorms.
What do you mean, my thunderstorms?
I'm only counseling you.
Actually, I don't have time to drink.
I've got my first big case since
switching to being a detective.
Big case?
Doctor, what do you think of this man?
What do I think?
With your skill at physiognomy, can
you tell me what kind of man he is?
Physiognomy?
Richard!
Do you think I'm a psychic or something?
Well, you are known for being able to tell what
someone is like just by looking at his face.
I'm only good at that because of my
many years of counseling people.
Then with your skill, could you tell me if he's a fraud?
Fraud?
Hmph!  This one's no good.
He's unable to lie.
Even if he tried, he'd be easily exposed.
I see.
How likely is he to commit suicide?
Very unlikely.
He doesn't have the face of one who would commit suicide.
Since you sound so confident, I'm convinced
of your skills at physiognomy.
It's just because of my years of experience at counseling.
So, is something wrong with that man?
Hans Georg Schuwald.
Schuwald?
Doctor, you know of him, right?
Yeah, the billionaire.
The Vampire of Bayern.
Right.  That billionaire hired me.
The man in this photo, Edmund
Fahren, claimed to be his son.
Hmph!  His lies were quickly exposed, right?
No, Schuwald completely believed his story.
It was quite a setup.  It took me a while
to discover that he was a fake.
But I still don't understand something.
How was he so well acquainted with Schuwald's son's
background that Schuwald actually believed him?
Why don't you ask him about that?
The truth is, he has already committed suicide.
The Secret Forest
Just let it go, Martin.
Come on, for old times' sake.
Let me see Edmund Fahren's suicide note.
The handwriting analysis has already been done.
No doubt about it, that was his handwriting.
There is no reason to show it to an outsider.
The first two witnesses, Karl Neumann and Lotte Frank...
They worked with Fahren, right?
They were just friends.
Just friends, huh...?
So, how are you guys doing?  Same as always?
Yeah, we never have enough manpower.
Since taking over your job, I've barely had any free time.
Dull-witted Martin has gotten high and mighty, huh?
Don't ever call me that again.
You are no longer my boss, and I'm
no longer your subordinate.
Hey, come on, Martin...
You don't seem to understand how hard it was back then.
We spent so much time tracking that serial killer, and
just when we were about to make the arrest...
...you shot him in your drunken stupor...
You wouldn't believe how much trouble
it was, cleaning up your mess.
Now, if you will excuse me.
I don't have time to deal with such a simple suicide case.
Oh.
I want to check out the crime scene.
Everything is still intact, right?
Well, since it's not really a crime scene, I've already
given permission to clean the place up.
I think they are moving the victim's belongings today.
Damn it!
Since when did dull-witted Martin get so fast?
Good, I'm in time.
The movers will be coming to pick
everything up soon, though.
Oh, I'll just be a few minutes.
He hung a rope from the pipe, huh?
He wrote his suicide note on this desk.
He was writing a paper on...
"The Birth of Tragedy," "Process and Reality,"
"The Sense of the World."
This is definitely the bookshelf of a philosophy student.
This is the source material for
the essay he was working on.
Hmm?  Oh, this is "The Gallic War."
This book is unrelated to the others, so why is it here?
Spanish?  No, Latin?
I don't have a clue what language this is.
This is a new book, but why is this
the only underlined passage?
Room 204... Ah, here it is.
Hey, we need more boxes!
Load up the books first.
Okay.
Great job, guys.
What should we do with this?
Oh, that one should be here.
All right.
Yes?
I'd like to ask you some questions about your neighbor.
I've already told you people everything I know.
Wait, I'm not a cop.  I'm a private investigator.
It doesn't matter who you are.
I've got a paper due tomorrow, but thanks
to all the commotion next door...
...I haven't been able to concentrate at all!
I understand.
Then, just one question.
Were these two people close to Fahren?
No, I've never seen them here before.
He didn't seem to have many friends.
I see...
That is it, right?
Hang on, just one more question...
What now?
Do you think you can translate this for me?
Just the underlined passage.
What?
You have got to be kidding me!
It will be your fault if I fail my class.
Sorry about that.
"I can't..."
"...deceive..."
"...anymore."
Huh?
What was that?
How should I know?  That's good enough, right?
"I can't..."
"...deceive..."
"...anymore."
Where have I heard this before?
You like this spot too?
Oh, you are... Johan, right?
Come on up here.
You can get a much better view up here.
Okay.
Thanks.
Wow, this is kinda scary.
There is nothing to be afraid of.
Hey, stop it!
Hey, I said stop!  It's dangerous!
Do you come here often?
Y-Yeah.
You can see the lights coming on in
all the houses around this time.
Families come home...
The smell of dinner is in the air.
I envy them.
You envy them?
Yeah, I haven't had anything like that since I was a child.
What was your family like?
Sorry, guess that is a touchy subject.
The thing is, I've been in foster homes since I was little.
If you don't mind, would you tell me about it?
About your past.
Damn!  This is it!
"I can't deceive him anymore."
Fahren's last words.
Wait, those weren't his last words...
He was only translating the line from that book.
That is the story of my life.
Kinda depressing, isn't it?
It's strange...
When I'm talking to you, I feel like I can say anything.
What you said just now, about your rich father...
You are talking about Schuwald, right?
Johan, you are crying... for me?
Hey, we have to do something about this.
I can't help but worry about Schuwald,
since I'm taking care of him.
Ever since Fahren's suicide, he hasn't been eating much.
If this goes on, he might die.
Karl, why don't you tell him you are his real son?
I just wanted to know what kind of person he was.
If I tell him the truth, he would probably
think I'm only after his money.
That is what Schuwald is like.  Everything is
about money to him.
He won't understand how I feel.
But we have to try.
Your own father is wallowing in despair.
I see, so that is what is going on.
Huh?
If that is the case, I've got an idea.
"I can't deceive him anymore..."
Those weren't Fahren's last words.
I found this Latin book in his room.
He simply translated this line from "The Gallic War."
This doesn't seem like a suicide to me.
I don't have proof, but my experience
as a cop tells me that.
Are you listening, Mr. Schuwald?
You don't look well.
That is enough.
Huh?
What are you saying?  This doesn't look good, you know.
If his death wasn't a suicide, that means
your life may be in danger, too.
He... he was my son.
Wait a minute... I already told you.
Neither his background nor his birthplace
has anything to do with you.
He was a fraud.
Indeed, Fahren was a good person, not
the type who could deceive people...
...but he did try to deceive you.
The master needs his rest.
I will have to ask you to leave now.
I'm not finished with this investigation.
And it's not because you are paying me a lot of money.
I can feel it!
There is something more sinister lurking behind everything.
In life...
In life, there are some things that cannot be undone.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
I understand very well.
The investigation will continue.
Okay?
Over here!
Children's Bill of Rights?
Yes, it's something like an international agreement...
...to protect the rights of children who are in need.
I'm working on this topic right now.
Volunteering to take care of these children at
the orphanage has nothing to do with it...
It's just something I enjoy doing.
So, tell us the rest of what you were talking about earlier...
The three times that Schuwald filed for bankruptcy, and...?
Yes, during those three times, he suddenly disappeared...
And when he reappeared, it was as though
he had been totally rejuvenated.
He said something about that during
one of our Friday reading sessions.
Did you ask him where he went during
those times when he disappeared?
Yes.
Then let's take him there.
Everyone has a place where they can go to relax.
For you, it's looking at the homes from
the rooftop of the university.
Mr. Kunz...
The drain in the bathroom seems to be clogged.
Can you take a look at it?
That sink over there.
Lotte, what is wrong with it?
Hey, open up!  Stop fooling around!
What is she up to?
Hey, open up!  Damn it!
Where are you taking Mr. Schuwald?
His eyes are bad, you know!
Open up!  This is kidnapping!
Damn you, kidnappers!
Okay!  Everything went according to plan.
All right, let's go!
Where are you taking me?
Somewhere nice, you'll see.
I know you are not Margot Langer.
I just need some information on the late Mr. Fahren.
He came to see you, right?
Fahren?  Which one are you referring to?
Which one...?
There were two different groups...
...with men claiming to be Schuwald's son.
The one with blond hair, or the one with black?
Black hair?
The one with black hair came with a girl.
Imagine, that a girl would actually
follow him to such a place.
A guy with black hair and a girl?
Don't tell me... these two?
Yeah, those two.
This guy...
...actually claimed to be Schuwald's son?
Is this really the place?
This should be right... It should be around here.
Where have you taken me?
Well, this is...
Orbenberg Forest.
I thought this place would help cheer you up.
Let me out.
Can you see the lake?
Y-Yeah...
The colors of the autumn leaves are beautiful, aren't they?
Y-Yeah, very beautiful...
Where are the wrens?
I can't hear the wrens singing...
I'm so... sorry.
This place is just a construction site now...
Can't you hear it?
Huh?
Close your eyes and listen carefully.
What a beautiful chorus.
Many apples have fallen from the trees onto the ground.
Put out your hand...
Come take a look over here.
What a spectacular sight.
The rays of the setting sun shining
through the autumn leaves...
Their radiance reflecting off the serene lake...
You can see it too, can't you?
I can't believe such a beautiful place actually exists.
I see it!
I can see it!
Hang on!
What did you just say?
Huh?
You said two different groups came, right?
The young man with black hair came with a girl.
Then, Fahren didn't come alone?
Yeah, someone else came with the blond guy.
That Fahren guy you are asking about hardly said a word.
It was his friend that did all the talking.
I wonder which one it is...
I'd believe him if he said he was Schuwald's son.
Who was...
...the other guy?