Key...
Key... and card...
The PIN...
Inside the safety deposit box...
is my experimental data and a tape...
A tape?
It's an interview... of a young boy...
It's the monster that led Kinderheim 511...
down the path of destruction...
The Adventures of Mr. Steiner
Prague Police Station
This way, please.
Inspector Zeman!
I've brought him.
Inspector?
This is the first man to arrive at
yesterday's murder scene...
Oh, Mr. Grimmer, is it?
I'm sorry you had to stay the night at the station.
I dropped my nail clippers, under the desk, so...
When your body's so big,
you bump into a lot of things...
You're pretty big yourself!
Yes.
I bump into a lot of things.
I'm Zeman, the lead investigator in this case.
I'm Grimmer.
Please, have a seat.
I'm sorry, but I was in the middle of clipping
my nails, so I'm going to continue.
Oh, go ahead.
My wife gets on my case...
If I let my nails grow, that is.
She won't let me have any white showing on my nails.
Thanks to that, I feel like I always have ingrown nails...
Yesterday must have been terrible.
Yeah...
I never thought something like that would happen...
I heard you're a freelance journalist.
Did you know anything about his personal history?
Mikhail Ivanovich Petrov...
Real name, Reinhard Biermann.
A German.
After the unification of Germany...
he was accused of civil rights oppression,
slave labor, child abuser and more.
Immediately after the Berlin Wall came down,
he escaped to the Czech Republic.
Germany wanted to prosecute him but...
the authorities in the Czech Republic left him
alone while continuing to monitor him.
Monitor?
That's right.
Along with the disturbing elements of
the old Czechoslovakian secret police.
Secret police?
You remember how violently they oppressed thought and
speech in this country during the Cold War, right?
Also, they were involved with and provided weapons for
extreme leftist terrorist acts throughout the world.
Despite all that...
Because the separation and democratization of the Czech
Republic and Slovakia was carried out rather calmly...
they went underground without being indicted.
It appears that Petrov was in contact with them.
For instance, Petrov could've sold them his information...
See?
They're ingrown again!
Oh, that's right.
Did you happen to see a woman?
A woman?
It appears that Petrov's killer was a young woman...
On top of that, she's apparently really pretty.
The children said they passed a woman
in front of the house, but...
I didn't notice anyone.
I see.
Those children...
What will happen to those orphans Mr. Petrov took in?
We're keeping them at the station
for the time being, but...
starting today, a few of them are going
to be taken in by orphanages.
I see...
I'm sorry you had to get caught up in all of this.
It's okay...
Speaking of which...
what kind of information were you trying to collect?
Oh, well, it's like what you just said.
Just some questions regarding Mr. Petrov, that's all.
Were you able to learn anything from him?
No, I was just about to, and...
Okay perfect!
Now my wife won't get mad at me!
Please, feel free to leave now.
I'm sorry to have kept you here for so long.
It's okay.
As he was dying...
did Mr. Petrov have any last words?
No.
Miroslav... Josef...
Also, where is Tomas?
Here...
Looks like all three of you are here.
Okay, get in this car.
Come on, come on! Hurry up and get in!
All right, next.
Three to the Vinohrady Nursery.
Honza, Antonin, Izzy.
Here...
It's going to be lonely now...
You guys were getting along so well,
but now you're splitting up...
Even though you'll be separated, you'll
still all be under the same sky!
A day will come when you guys
can play soccer together again!
Cheer up, Antonin!
You were the leader, right?
You can still write them letters.
You should become the center of the
group and cheer everyone up!
Okay...
Good, that's it!
Where to, sir?
Oh, the Hotel Kafka...
Actually, the Procházka Bank first, please.
The Procházka Bank is on the way to the hotel.
Sorry, but I don't speak Czech very well...
Can you speak German or English?
The weather's nice today, isn't it?
Why are you stopping?
This isn't...
You can share the ride.
Take me to the Svoboda industrial area.
Hey, hey!
You should at least ask me before
picking up someone else.
Did you see the soccer game on TV yesterday?
Yeah, they didn't do very well.
E-Excuse me...
Why are we going so far away from town?
My hotel is in the city.
Key.
Key!
W-What are you talking about?
You're such a troublemaker.
He's up there!
Stop him!
Are you okay?
I followed you because I thought
you might be in danger.
Any injuries?
Are you okay?
Inspector...
They're probably from the former
secret police I told you about.
Did they demand anything from you?
N-No, nothing...
I can't believe they'd go this far just for nothing.
No, really. Nothing...
Are you sure you aren't hiding anything?
N-No...
You must have some idea.
They really went pretty far.
No, I really don't know...
Then you've already removed it from
the safety deposit box at the bank?
The tape.
The cassette tape.
They're looking for his roots.
They...?
Roots...?
The roots of the monster.
They'll fetch a high price.
Monster...?
We'll know immediately if we listen to the tape.
Where in the Czech Republic the
monster's mother lives, that is...
Oh, hello.
This is Inspector Zeman.
About that supermarket robbery suspect...
Did he give up any of his accomplices?
I see.
Nice work, Detective Suk.
Me?
I still have some errands I need to run.
Let's see I think I can return to
the station in about an hour.
Goodbye.
If you don't stop there he won't be able to talk.
Do you feel like talking now?
Where is the key?
I... I have no idea what you're talking about...
You son of a...!
Now, now, wait.
There's nothing in it for you even
if you hide it Mr. Grimmer.
Where is the key to the safety deposit
box you got from Petrov?
I... I already said, I can't tell you what I don't know.
I see, so you want money
I'll hear you out.
How much would you sell it for?
Even though I'm a third-rate journalist...
I'm not hurting to put food on the table.
Mr. Grimmer...
This is bad.
Look how long your nails are!
Didn't I tell you my wife is very fussy about these things?
When your nails get long...
Oh, it's best if you don't move.
Or else I'll cut the nail too far.
Where?
Where is the key?
Even if you open the safety deposit box at the bank
with the key and get the tape and documents...
you have no use for either of them.
That tape is only meaningful when it
is in the hands of their organization.
For the sake of their goals.
For the sake of resurrecting the East!
The monster's identity is recorded on that tape.
They need that monster.
I heard that the monster...
is capable of unifying them.
The alumni of Kinderheim 511, that is.
They're going to gather the
alumni of Kinderheim 511...
the ones who were raised in old East Germany,
for the health and prosperity of communism.
Nobody is more qualified.
It is said that the monster had all of
Kinderheim 511 under his control...
and then destroyed it.
He is the only one.
The only one who can unify that group of elites!
Now, where is the key?
Group of elites, huh...?
What's so funny?!
What is it that you want?
If you want money, I can understand.
I'm a capitalist.
I love money!
I'm merely trying to earn a lot of
money by selling them the key.
What are you doing this for?
The justice of society?
There's no way you'd go this far for something like that!
Who are you?
You said you were a journalist from the East, but...
most of them were intelligence gatherers...
Most likely, the majority of them were spies.
Where were you sent from?
Trying to be like 007?
You used to torture or something?!
You're really going to die.
Last chance.
Where is the key?
Do you know about... "The Amazing Steiner"?
In the 60's...
it was a cartoon on TV in West Germany...
Even in East Germany...
I was able to secretly watch it.
The main character...
was normally a weak guy.
But when he was in a tight spot...
help would always come.
His secret friend...
But the main character didn't realize it...
That his secret friend...
was in fact himself.
The main character...
when placed in absolute danger...
would transform into "The Amazing Steiner"...
who was scary just to look at...
Before the main character realized it...
All the bad guys...
were beaten to a pulp.
Try to transform.
Hurry up and transform, then!
Dump some water on him.
He'll spill it eventually.
It's only a matter of time.
Who are you...?
A woman came in...
A woman...
came in, and then...
One gunshot...
One man shot to death...
The other two bodies...
had no bullet wounds...
The Amazing Steiner, huh...?
I did it again...
Yes
Cherish what you know is true in this world.
Ima kono sekai de wakaru koto mitsumete
Yes
Please believe in the kindness of your eyes
Anata no hitomi no yasashisa wo shinjite
Make it home to your land of harmony
Make it home to your land of purity
Make it home