Zeus proclaimed...
And the human tribes living on the land...
learned to sow the seeds and cultivate the fields.
Karl, your pronunciation is off again.
I'm sorry.
I'm trying to be careful.
You've gotten better, though.
When you first came here...
I thought, "Such a terrible student
has come to my place."
You're right...
What happened to him?
That Japanese doctor.
I heard he's traveling around the world.
I see.
I sure would like to meet him again someday.
Yes.
The Real Monster
You started working?
That's great!
What are you doing?
Interior decorator.
I see.
I know you have an eye for furniture.
Even though I do interior design,
it's a little different than usual.
I'm a kitchen coordinator.
Funny, isn't it?
I've never really set foot in a kitchen until now.
Then maybe I should ask you to do my kitchen next time.
Sure.
But I get the feeling you have expensive tastes.
Just a little.
You haven't been drinking, have you?
No, not a single drop.
That's great.
Let's take it slow.
Even if you try to rush it, today is going to
pass by and tomorrow will still come.
That's what happiness is.
Right?
Tired of hearing that?
Happiness, huh?
He said that knowing I was waiting for him at the
train station was enough to make him happy...
That man., Martin?
People are so strange.
Sadness keeps fading away...
and only happy memories remain.
People sure have a convenient makeup.
That's why we can keep on living.
Let me introduce you.
This is Mr. Verdeman, the attorney.
He's the one who cleared the suspicions against you...
Mr. Grimmer.
I learned everything I could about you.
You came from Kinderheim 511.
A member of East German intelligence,
you masqueraded as a journalist...
and traveled around the world.
Afterwards, as a freelance reporter...
you continued to investigate human
rights violations in old East Germany.
In that big bag of yours...
I found piles of supporting documents.
However, the one thing that remains a mystery...
is your real name.
Wolfgang Grimmer...
Not just his name.
He left without telling us anything.
Inspector Lunge.
I'm not an inspector anymore, Detective Suk.
I heard you became an instructor at a police academy.
I've begun to talk with my daughter a lot lately.
Only through e-mail, though.
Until now, we've lived without
saying anything to each other.
We lived without knowing anything about each other.
I wonder how many things people can really
tell each other while they're alive...
You probably had a lot of things
you wanted to talk about...
over a good beer.
You're going back to Düsseldorf?
Yes.
The company I have a contract with is there.
I see.
Are you going to be okay?
That place has a lot of bad memories for you...
"Trying to run away is useless."
"What's important is to face the truth and move forward."
Right?
Exactly.
Can you dispose of this for me?
Goodbye.
Yeah.
Take care of yourself.
Tell me immediately if something happens.
Both Dr. Gillen and I are here to help at any time.
And Dieter.
He's here, too.
Give my regards to them.
I will.
Dr. Tenma's hearing continues.
Still unable to grasp the whole story.
Inspector Lunge begins his testimony.
Has this developed into the worst serial
murder case in the history of Europe?
Dr. Tenma completely exonerated.
The authorities express their apologies to Dr. Tenma.
The motive behind the case is still unknown.
What is the identity of the mysterious
young man said to be the real culprit?
Münster Medical School offers Dr.
Tenma a position as professor.
Dr. Tenma continues to decline the position.
Dr. Tenma participates in "Doctors Without Borders."
The articles keep getting smaller.
People have a convenient makeup, huh?
Hey, Dieter.
You've gotten big since the last time I saw you.
You've gotten slimier since the last
time I saw you, Mr. Heckel.
And you're still as snotty as ever!
Sorry, but I'm going to soccer practice, so
I don't have time to hang out with you.
H-Hey!
W-Wait a minute!
Did Tenma come back?
I don't know about this "Doctors Without Borders" thing...
He's just acting cool and not making any money!
And I can never get in touch with him!
What would you do if he came back?
I took a job he asked me to do a little while ago.
After thinking about the expenses and the labor...
the reward he offered wasn't nearly enough!
Tenma asked you to do something for him?
He only asked me to find someone...
but I had a hell of a time!
I even went so far as to steal top
secret material from the police!
Who knows what will happen if they catch me?
Hey!
Give this invoice to Tenma!
Tell him that if he can't pay...
I'll make him work as an underground doctor again!
Southern France
We've been waiting for you.
We haven't seen you in a while.
Sorry, I had to go abroad.
Please share this with everyone.
My, thank you.
What nice weather.
All these leaves are photosynthesizing.
Life.
Countless genes.
Do you know about Mendel?
Yes.
The one who determined the laws of inheritance.
I went to the same college as Mendel.
Brno University.
A town in Moravia in southeastern Czechoslovakia, right?
It's a wonderful place.
I'll definitely go there next time.
Thank you...
for coming here so many times.
For allowing me to have such a wonderful time.
It's nothing.
I feel quite well today.
I feel like I can talk about anything.
No matter how frightening it may be.
You have something you want to ask me, don't you?
You're...
the mother of the twins, aren't you?
Yes.
I loved him.
He was killed by that man.
Killing him was that man's experiment.
I will never forgive him.
Even if I died...
the children that were growing inside of me...
would surely deliver punishment to that man.
Please don't.
Please don't let go of my hand.
Who is the real monster?
Are the children alive?
Yes, they're doing well.
I remember.
Remember what?
I will probably never recall this again.
I have to say this now.
I gave those children names.
Their names are...
Come in.
You're still the tardy offender, I see.
You're ten minutes late.
I'm sorry, Professor Kronecker.
Oh, well. That's all right.
You know why you've been called here today, don't you?
It's regarding your graduation thesis.
Step forward.
Y-Yesr sir.
I know a lot has happened to you.
It must have been hard to catch up on everything
after you took a break from school.
But that doesn't excuse my grades...
Exactly.
Now, about your thesis.
It's first class.
This is the best thesis paper I've ever seen...
out of all the students I've taught.
You did well.
I'm proud of you.
Thank you...
What do you wish to do?
Sir!
To become a lawyer!
I pray that many lives will be saved by your hands.
You may go now.
Thank you!
However.
Tardiness won't be allowed in court.
Fraulein Nina Fortner.
Yes, sir!
Yes, hello?
Oh, Dieter?
What's the deal with your graduation?
Even if you fail, I'm still with you.
Oh, how reassuring.
Maybe I should have you comfort me next time I see you.
It's useless to fake it, because I can tell by your voice.
You did it!
Congratulations!
Thank you.
This is where things start to get tough, though.
Let's celebrate!
Hurry up and come back!
I can't come back right away.
I have to go to work...
and I have a lot of plans with my friends.
What are you talking about?
Tenma is coming back!
I just got a call from him!
But he said he has to leave again
with Doctors Without Borders.
When?
He said he'll be back by tomorrow.
You should hurry up and come back!
Oh, Nina.
About tomorrow...
Sorry! I can't go!
Tenma!
I get to see Tenma!
Oh, hello.
Bayern State Police Hospital
Hello.
You've been asleep since then.
Can you hear me?
I've spoken with your mother.
She loves you very much.
She told me your real name.
You had a name.
Dr. Tenma.
There's one thing I want to ask you, and only you.
Back then...
that monster appeared before me.
Don't!
Don't touch these children!
No!
Don't come near me!
This is an experiment.
We're going to leave one and take the other.
Now, which one will we take?
Please don't let go!
Mommy.
Please...
don't let go of my hand!
This one.
No...
This one!
No!
Did my mother try to save me?
Or did she mistake me for my sister?
Which is it?
Who was the one she didn't want?
I'll be going now.
Yes
Cherish what you know is true in this world.
Ima kono sekai de wakaru koto mitsumete
Yes
Please believe in the kindness of your eyes
Anata no hitomi no yasashisa wo shinjite
Make it home to your land of harmony
Make it home to your land of purity
Make it home