Get out!
Leave me alone.
You can't sleep in here forever.
Wake up!
You are hopeless...
Seriously!
This is not a hotel, you know!
Don't touch me so casually.
Who do you think I am?
Here.
These are your belongings.
Check the content and sign here.
Eva Heinemann.
Don't let me catch you in here again.
I can't believe you passed out drunk
in a back alley like that...
You should be thankful that you are safe.
Do you have a cigarette?
I asked if you had any cigarettes on you...
Smoking is not permitted inside.
Go outside and smoke all you want!
Eva's Confession
Lighter...
Where is my lighter?
My bag!
Where did you put my bag?
That was the only bag you had.
That is a lie!
I had another shoulder bag with me!
Then a thief probably stole it while
you were passed out in the alley.
What are you going to do about it?
I had something really important in there!
Well...
...do you want to fill out a stolen property report?
Although personally, I think it would be a waste of time.
You lost your key?
My whole bag was stolen.
Hurry up and open my room!
W-What is this?
Oh, man.
Someone broke in.
This is bad.
Now I'll have to change the lock.
Oh, and Ms. Heinemann...
I've been asking since yesterday, but about the room bill...
...the advance payment I got ran out a long time ago.
If I don't receive payment for the overdue days, then...
Even my suitcase was broken into...
Are you even listening to me?
I need payment for the overdue
days and a replacement key.
If you want money, I don't have any.
You want me to leave, right?
That was some bad luck.
So that is why you came to me for help?
Even though you were the one who left
saying we would never see each other again?
We haven't seen each other in a while, so
why don't you at least buy me a drink?
Hey, Eva.
Don't tell me you are out of money just
because someone stole your bag.
I've never come across another woman
who spent her money as freely as you.
No amount of money would have ever been enough for you, the way you spent it.
You were out of money anyway, weren't you?
How much will you pay?
I'll sleep with you.
I'm asking how much you'll pay me.
You idiot.
What kind of man would pay for a woman
he has slept with so many times?
Get me a drink.
Go stand out in the street.
Some curious weirdo might buy a drink for you.
Even an alcoholic hag like you.
Well, I'm sure you didn't leave it at my store.
You sure you didn't leave it at the next store you went to?
I don't remember anything after this store.
You said you had something important in there, but...
...if it had any real value, you should forget about it.
It's not something you could get money for.
Not money...
Hey, I've been looking all over for you.
When I went to the pub over there...
...they said you had wandered off this way, so...
Who are you?
Oh, come on.
We had such a good time drinking
together last night, remember?
I drank... with you...?
Here, your bag.
I wanted to give it to you.
Oh?
Does this mean I'll have to reintroduce myself?
I'm Roberto.
So, how about getting some food?
That's horrible.
Your hotel room was vandalized?
But it doesn't seem like you did it.
Of course not.
I didn't even open your bag.
The hotel room key is still in here, too.
But I don't need it anymore.
I'm truly sorry.
If only I had returned your bag sooner, you wouldn't
have been chased out of your room.
It's not your fault.
More importantly, I'm grateful you came to return it.
That is because I'm grateful to that bag.
When you left the pub last night, you forgot your bag.
I thought I would never see you again, but...
...thanks to that bag, we are here, together again.
There must have been something very important in there.
Something like this.
It's all I have left in my possession.
A photo album?
May I take a look?
Go ahead.
That is my father.
A fine man.
If I recall correctly, he was the director of a hospital.
Did I tell you that last night?
Yes, and that you respected him very much.
You said he passed away ten years ago.
You had such a sad expression when
you talked about it last night.
And... oh, yes.
This was your fiancé.
I even told you about him?
Yes.
I believe his name was Tenma?
You still can't forget him?
What did I say last night?
You should forget about him already.
I got a little jealous.
This is the only page that doesn't have any pictures.
Oh, really?
There used to be some.
Some traces remain.
I took them out because I had no need for them.
I see.
Hey.
Would you like to go drinking with me?
Sounds good.
I see.
So you used to run a security firm?
Yes, in southern France, Nice.
But the longtime client I was guarding was killed.
So I shut the company down.
We've both had it rough.
Let's forget about that.
What is important is right now.
We have to enjoy the present.
This song...
It's Al Green.
You like this song, too?
Yeah...
Let's dance.
What's wrong?
Well, I'm not very good at dancing...
Put your hands around my waist.
That's right.
I love this song, but...
...there was another guy who wasn't very good at dancing.
So you always stayed like this.
Yeah...
This is so fun!
How about you?
Want another drink?
No, I've had enough.
You can't hold your liquor, can you?
Then... wanna go to bed?
Oh, that sounds good.
But before that, there is something I have to ask you.
What?
Where are the pictures?
What pictures?
Don't play dumb!
The pictures you took from the album.
Where did you hide them?
Give me the pictures, and I'll tell you something.
You are looking for Tenma, aren't you?
Wha...!
I know you didn't burn those pictures.
Y-You know where Tenma is?
Yeah.
The pictures you are talking about...
They are the ones with that boy in them, right?
His name is Johan.
I saw him.
He has grown up into a pretty boy with blond hair.
I saw him in Düsseldorf about a year ago.
Kenzou...
We're going to start over again.
You...
...have to be with me.
Kenzou...
You are mine.
I will get you back again.
Because you are mine.
Düsseldorf
Spring 1995
So, what are you doing right now?
I've heard a lot of rumors, but...
It's just as those rumors say.
I've been married three times and I have been divorced three times.
Thanks to my father's will and the condolence money...
...I'm living luxuriantly, lacking nothing.
What about you, Dr. Becker?
Oh, me?
It's the same old story for me.
I'm not in with the management, so
no chance of promotion for me.
However, in Tenma's case, he's now
the head of the surgical department.
And rumor has it that he will become the director someday.
Talk about being left behind!
But you know, my life isn't so bad.
Life is not about being promoted.
No way do I want to end up like Tenma,
who has no time for women or fun.
Kenzou...
Dr. Tenma still hasn't gotten married?
Nope.
I've introduced him to tons of women, but...
...he puts work first and isn't really interested in them.
Oh, yes.
So I set him up with someone again.
She's the daughter of the state legislator.
And she is really fine!
If she doesn't get his attention, I'm giving up on him.
So why did you call me, Eva?
As the daughter of the former hospital director, you've
never even glanced in my direction before.
I never would have imagined that you would
ask me to spend some time with you.
I understand.
Even though you say you don't lack anything...
...you are actually pretty lonely, right?
If you will let me, I'll lend you my ear any time you want.
I don't want them to meet.
That state legislator's daughter...
Please don't let her meet Kenzou.
Don't tell me... you still haven't...
Please...
You better make it tonight!
I went through a lot of trouble to set this up just right.
I won't know until I meet her.
This is it!
This must be the clock that Mr. Junkers
from the hospital was talking about!
Excuse me!
About the clock in the window...
Hey, what are you doing?
It's time for your date!
Hey!
That is a beautiful wristwatch.
You are...?
My watch is only an accessory.
I don't bother looking at the time anymore.
I wonder why it feels like time is moving faster and faster?
Um, excuse me, but who are you?
You are Ms. Angelika, the daughter of
State Legislator Berger, correct?
Yes.
You are very beautiful.
Young, too.
Oh, thank you. Umm...
You believe that the world revolves around you...
You think there is nothing in this
world that you can't get, right?
Um, what are you trying to say?
Who are you...?
I have a mole on my inner thigh...
He kisses it.
He always kisses it.
Dr. Kenzou Tenma, that is.
Oh, crap!
Look!
She went home, all because you were shopping
at that place and got here late!
Oh, I see.
I did something bad to her.
Can you apologize to her for me?
H-Hey!
If you give her a call right now, I'm sure she will forgive you.
Hey!
I want to swing by the hospital for a second.
Work again?
Would you cut it out already?
Man...
Kenzou...
...is mine...
You are mine...
Please wait!
Mr. Junkers!
Kenzou...
What's wrong?
Wait, Kenzou!
I want to talk to you!
Mr. Junkers!
Kenzou!
Please, wait!
Kenzou...
My heel...
Kenzou?
I saw him...
...one year ago...
That was Johan, wasn't it?
So she saw Johan, huh?
Guess I'll kill her after all.