Jahreszeit Hotel
(Frankfurt)
The Red Rose Mansion experiment is still going...
The devil got himself a disciple.
The man with glasses...
The survivor from the Red Rose Mansion...
Peter... Čapek...
That man...
is trying to control the devil.
Please follow that car.
He ran!
A Fun Dining Table
Where am I?
Where is this place?
You're awake.
How are you feeling?
Well, uh...
You're very lucky.
You only sprained your leg.
From what I can tell, you didn't hit
your head all that hard, either.
Though I'm not an expert like you.
You know about me?
Dr. Tenma.
A genius brain surgeon.
I read about you in the newspaper.
Who are you?
I'm a local dentist.
The name's Milan Kolasch.
I happened to see you get hit by a car.
The car that hit you sped off in a hurry.
You should stay in bed for now.
No, I'll cause you trouble.
Wobbling around here with that leg of yours...
and catching the attention of the
police would trouble me more.
Around here?
This is the Turkish district in Frankfurt.
Turkish district?
I should say it used to be the Turkish district.
They're tearing down all the buildings around
here for redevelopment or something.
Most of the Turks who were living here...
moved to another location.
But when they were attacked by the extreme right...
they fought back together.
Is Café Bahir gone, too?
Yeah.
It's long gone.
You know this area?
Yes, a little.
Well, if you can get up...
you want to have your meal over there?
It tastes better when you eat with everyone.
We're having Vietnamese food today.
Minh made it.
Pho Ga and Cha Gio Tom.
Minh's Vietnamese dishes are exceptional.
Don't hold back, eat up.
It's delicious!
I love pork, but...
Turkish people don't eat pork.
I'm not too fond of Czech food.
That's because Milan can't cook.
Well, sorry.
Everyone takes turns making food
from their home country.
It's luxurious to be able to taste food from different
countries every day, don't you think?
Dr. Tenma, you're Japanese right?
What does Japanese food taste like?
Japanese food, huh?
Yes, make us some.
Oh, I can't wait.
Let's see...
Katsudon requires pork.
Sushi...
There are probably people who can't eat raw fish.
How about Oyakodon?
Oyakodon -Chicken and egg on rice, also known as parent and child donburi.
Oyakodon?
Yes.
You put chicken on top of rice,
covered in soy sauce and eggs.
Why is that Oyakodon?
The chicken is the parent, and the eggs are the children.
That's why it's called Oyakodon?
Japanese food names sure are amusing!
Chicken and egg together means parent and child!
What's wrong, Tenma?
Nothing.
You don't like the food?
No, it's good.
It's just been so long...
since I had such delicious food...
Since I had such an enjoyable meal...
Good night, Tenma.
Good night.
I wonder how long it'll take...
before I can walk again?
I don't have any time to waste...
Peter...
Čapek?
A gun?
A report on the actions taken by Peter Čapek.
Didn't you think it was strange?
The reason the police were so well-organized...
wasn't because they were trying to catch you.
They were originally on the lookout for me.
I'm going to kill Peter Čapek.
It didn't work.
That's strange.
I used to be able to make good
ones that could fly really far.
Milan is good at making paper airplanes.
They would fly all the way to the roofs over there!
I see.
Milan always said to us...
He always promised us...
Someday, we'll go much farther than those roofs.
We'll go to Turkey, Vietnam, and
even the Czech Republic.
Let's go see everyone's homelands.
Right?
Yeah!
There!
It's no good after all.
Why won't it fly?
That's strange.
I'm going to kill Peter Čapek.
Why?
Why would you do such a thing, Mr. Milan?
That man...
The man named Peter Čapek...
is a devil.
In 1989...
the night before the fall of the Communist
Party in Czechoslovakia...
he escaped into this country.
Čapek lived here in Frankfurt.
He became a teacher, and he started teaching German.
He was a quiet man.
However, somewhere down the road...
the children started to change.
Children who attended his class committed
suicide, one after another.
And then...
they started to show extreme aggression.
And finally, one day...
a riot broke out, and the children tried to kill each other.
I went to an institute where the ringleader
of that incident was being held.
He quietly said to me...
that he wanted to hurry back to the book readings.
Book readings?
The child committed suicide in the institute that night.
He was my son.
Čapek left town during the disturbance.
The next time he appeared in this town...
he was like a different person.
He took control of the underground
organization in Frankfurt...
and had ties with the extreme right.
And then...
he used them to start purging this neighborhood
of Turks and other foreigners.
I don't know what he's trying to accomplish in this town.
However, the pinnacle of his violence...
was the burning of the Turkish district in 1996.
You know about that incident, don't you?
Yeah.
I saw it on the news.
The townspeople formed a vigilance
committee to try to oppose them.
However...
The five leaders of the vigilance committee...
all died strange deaths...
in just three months.
The five people who died were...
Suleiman's son.
Tung's father.
Minh's husband.
Mustafa's son.
And Shemel's father.
They didn't die.
They were killed...
by Peter Čapek.
I don't know why you were watching Čapek.
But let me just say this...
The one who will kill Čapek...
is me.
Hold on.
I think this one is pretty good.
It's useless.
No, I have to try.
Some things are impossible, no matter how hard you try.
We know.
We know we can't go on vacation to Turkey or Vietnam.
I don't care if I go on a trip or not.
I'm happy as long as I can live
with Milan and Tung like this.
Yeah.
Okay, it's done.
This one will fly.
There.
See?
Yay! It's flying!
Wow! Wow!
I doubt it'll fly over to the roof on
the other side like Mr. Milan's.
But it's still flying.
Aren't you glad we didn't give up?
Yeah!
You can't give up...
Where's my gun?
Where did you put the gun that was in my drawer?
My chance to shoot Čapek has come.
I'm going now.
Give me back my gun.
I can't let you do something like that.
I can't give you back your gun.
This is the gun I found in your coat.
I'd like to use the gun I trained with and am
familiar with when I do the real thing.
Give me back my gun.
You have a family now.
You can't do this.
I've been following Čapek's actions for a long time now.
I've never had as good a chance to do Čapek in.
Please.
Don't do this, Mr. Milan.
I thought I told you.
Don't try to get in my way.
Even if you get revenge now...
you can't bring back the dead.
Rather, you should think about the future.
You don't have the right to tell me that.
Mr. Milan...
You and I are the same, Dr. Tenma.
I've done some checking up on you.
If what you claim is true...
you and I are both trying to do the same thing.
He wasn't always like that.
The person I knew...
wasn't a devil like that!
Peter Čapek and I are childhood
friends from the same country.
I brought him into this country!
Do you know what's on the other side of the border?
You're not allowed to go there.
I know you're not allowed to go there.
But do you know?
I heard the other side of the border is a wonderful place.
There's a town that's always bright at night.
Really, Peter?
Who did you hear that from?
Mr. Gregor.
He's an alcoholic.
Besides, I heard that on the other side of the border...
there are things that make people
worthless, like Mr. Gregor.
Things that make people worthless, huh?
I'd like to see that.
Why would you want to see that?
There!
It's riding the wind
You're good, Milan!
It's flying! It's flying
Amazing!
It could go over the border if it keeps flying like that!
Go see what it's like on the other side for us!
We grew up in a town near the border
of Czechoslovakia and Austria.
I was the son of a craftsman.
He was the son of a government official.
However...
strangely, he and I got along well.
In 1989...
when the Czechoslovakian Communist Party collapsed...
I was the one who helped him escape.
The one who brought that devil to this country...
was me.
Prague
I was really worried about you during
the Soviet invasion last year.
A lot of my friends were dragged away.
But here I am, safe and sound.
What about you?
Me?
I'm doing so-so, I guess.
I'm a novice dentist, and I'm earning money for food.
So you're a dentist now, huh?
Well, you did have skillful hands.
I wish I had some of your social skills, too.
It's true that even after the Soviets came in...
the reason why I'm in my current position...
is thanks to my social skills.
I did enjoy myself quite a bit during the "Prague Spring."
I was able to go to the West, too.
We used to talk about that a lot when we were kids.
About what it was like on the other side.
Did you find the answer?
I did.
So?
There was nothing there.
Nothing here, nothing there.
This country is making a mistake.
But they aren't necessarily right on the other sider either.
I see.
You said I had good social skills, but...
the truth is, there was a person
who appreciated my skills.
Since I met him...
I haven't really cared about
the position I hold right now.
He's such a wonderful person.
Just when I came to the conclusion that there was
nothing in this country or on the other side...
he showed me a light hat I never knew existed.
He's someone who brings forth something entirely new.
So, what will that person bring forth?
What?
Let's see...
It could be something frightening.
When I think about it now, back then...
something inside of him must have started to fall apart.
Give me back my gun.
Here, I'm giving you back your gun.
You can't, Mr. Milan.
You mustn't do this.
It's no use trying to stop me.
I'm going to kill him.
You have a family that you're living with now.
And he's the one who killed their families.
Because I brought him into this country...
they were killed.
And...
even my own son.
When this neighborhood was being burned down...
there was a man the Turks still talk about, even today.
There was a Japanese man who tried
his best to treat the injured...
and risked his life trying to put out the fire.
That was you, wasn't it, Dr. Tenma?
I believe you.
I fully understand what you're trying to do.
You and I are the same.
I'm going.
It's time.
If I miss this opportunity, I may
never get the chance again.
Mr. Milan!
Thank you for trying to stop me.
If I was in your position...
I wouldn't be able to stop, either.
What is it?
It's delicious!
Yeah, this really is good!
This Japanese Oyakodon tastes really great!
Is your leg okay?
Do you want any help, Dr. Tenma?
It's okay.
Yours will be done soon, Ms. Minh.
Milan sure is late.
I think he'll be back soon.
It's better to eat it fresh...
so I'll make his later.
In our next story...
At 11 o'clock this morning...
Really?
Then, I look forward to it.
at the Rodelheim Convention Center in Frankfurt...
there was an incident where an
armed man opened fire, but...
the gunman was shot and killed by security
who were on guard at the convention center
There were no other victims, but...
because a large number of important people
from various fields were attending...
the convention center was thrown
into confusion for some time.
Now, the shooter's identity and his motives
are still uncertain at this point.
Here's footage from the incident
as it happened, caught on tape.
Everyone says it's really good!
I hope Milan comes home soon.
Here's footage from the incident
as it happened, caught on tape.
That man...
He's from the Red Rose Mansion!
He's...
You must not hide anything from him.
Yes
Cherish what you know is true in this world.
Ima kono sekai de wakaru koto mitsumete
Yes
Please believe in the kindness of your eyes
Anata no hitomi no yasashisa wo shinjite
Make it home to your land of harmony
Make it home to your land of purity
Make it home