Ruhenheim...
This is it.
Stop it, Ludwig!
What is this dog barking at?
Ruhenheim
That bike is broken again?
Yeah, the chain keeps coming off.
I should have figured it was in the dumpster for a reason.
It doesn't look like trash to me.
Whenever I ride this, everybody says, "Look!
Look at the moving pile of trash!"
That trash is riding some trash...
That's not true.
It's a wonderful 5-speed supercycle.
Here, let's try fixing it again.
Looks like you have a customer.
Oh, that's right. I received a call earlier.
Excuse me, are you the one who reserved a room...?
Yes. My name is Lunge.
Oh, Mr. Lunge.
Welcome.
I'm glad there was a room available on such short notice.
Well, the rooms are always empty.
It is still the off-season.
It feels like it's the off-season all year long.
The only other people staying here
are that elderly couple over there.
Her husband injured his legs...
...so it seems that they have difficulties traveling.
I'll take your bag.
Please do, Wim.
He's in room 302.
How is the view from that room?
Well, it has the best view in the building.
I'll put your bag here.
It doesn't look like trash to me, either.
I thought it looked like an excellent bike.
Inspector Lunge of the BKA!
Why are you at a branch office all the
way out in a country town like this?
I was wondering how much backup
you could request out here.
Request? Backup?
Well, if we contact state headquarters, we can get
a lot of reinforcements in as little as an hour.
But I don't think anything big like that would
happen in a country town like this.
You should check everyone who
comes into town starting now.
Before anything terrible happens.
Great! Keep going!
Nice run!
Let's go faster!
Change gear!
Ouch...
What's up, trash?
That trash is still moving?
This trash is painful to look at!
Stop!
Stop it!
Stupid trash!
You're just trash!
Are you okay?
By yourself?
Are you traveling by yourself?
Yes.
Here for work?
No, private business.
Oh, my.
Aren't you lonely by yourself?
No, I'm used to jt.
Do you have a family?
Yes, I have one.
My daughter even has a son now.
Oh, a grandson!
Grandsons are great.
They care about us.
Look! I was writing a postcard to my grandson just now.
Letters are nice.
In letters, you can write things you can't say face to face.
Why don't you try writing one as well?
A letter to my grandson...
But I don't even know what to write...
Anything will do.
If I could draw...
Excuse me.
Can I stay here for the night?
Yes, of course.
Oh, that's great!
I was enjoying a relaxing picnic...
but I got lost.
Now that I've finally arrived in town...
it's already late.
Well, I really appreciate this.
Looks like nobody's getting off at this town.
A gunshot?
I didn't hear any gunshots.
No, I swear I heard it.
No one in this town has a gun.
If anyone did, it'd be that drunk out back.
If he shot it out from the back of the house.
it'd sound much louder.
Besides, that drunk couldn't hit anything, even if he tried.
Damn it! I lost again!
I lost again because you jinxed me!
Damn!
Shut up!
It's not my fault!
Why don't you just stop trying to win the lottery already?
Ludwig!
I can't find my Ludwig anywhere!
You heard that gunshot just now, didn't you?
What if my Ludwig was...!
What if my baby was...!
Please calm down, Mrs. Hillman.
There weren't any gunshots.
Please calm down.
Is something wrong?
Well, this woman's dog has gone missing.
Oh, my.
That's always a worry.
Well, let's call the police.
I already reported it to the police!
But you can't count on that man!
Even though he's an officer, he's totally unreliable!
How could you rely on an officer who hates dogs?
Would you like me to go look for him?
Are you sure, Mr. Neumaier?
Yeah.
I was going to wander around town anyway.
Yes, I know Mrs. Hillman's dog quite well.
You're talking about that stupid
mutt that never shuts up, right?
He's missing.
Have you seen him?
No, I haven't.
I see. Thank you.
Oh, one more thing.
Have you seen any unfamiliar or suspicious
characters around town lately?
Yes, I have.
You.
A dog?
I thought you were going to stay here.
I'm sorry.
I'm staying at the Versteck Hotel.
Man, he takes all of my customers.
Which means nobody is staying at this hotel?
Nobody at all.
Thanks to him, I lead a quiet life.
That's why I'd know right away
if that noisy dog was around.
Have you heard him bark today?
No, I haven't.
But maybe...
You heard what sounded like a gunshot, didn't you?
Maybe some degenerate got fed up and shot him.
Oh, hello. Umm...
It's Lunge, Mr. Neumaier.
Oh, Mr. Lunge.
Where are you headed?
I'm looking for the dog.
Oh, I see.
Did you find any clues?
No.
Then let's keep looking.
Alcohol!
Get me some alcohol!
No, Dad! You can't have any more!
Hurry up and buy me some alcohol!
I don't have any money!
I know you got some money working at the hotel!
Maybe I can buy a bottle...
Wim.
It's okay.
You earned that money.
Looks like you had another rough day.
Now, come on. Let's go back to my hotel.
This is delicious!
Not many people eat with such enthusiasm.
Really?
But good food is delicious!
You don't have to get all worked up over a sausage.
This is how I look when I eat something delicious!
This is a nice town.
It's quiet and has good food.
You think so?
I want to hurry up and get out of this boring town.
I hope a wonderful person will show up one
day and take me away from this place.
Has a wonderful person stopped by lately?
Not at all.
I'm getting sick of seeing the same old faces every day!
By the way, about the dog...
Oh, I've taken that dog for a walk before.
A walk?
When Mrs. Hillman had a cold, I helped
her out by walking the dog.
When I gave it one of our Eisbein bones
from the deli, it wouldn't let it go!
And then he wouldn't stop pulling!
How far did you guys go?
Inspector Lunge!
A terrible thing happened, just like you said.
A dog.
A dog has gone missing.
Did you hear any gunshots?
Oh, that wasn't a gunshot.
A car broke down on the highway.
You must've heard the engine backfiring.
You won't hear any gunshots in this town.
Bye.
You don't want to scare me, if you
know what's good for you.
There you are.
Ludwig.
You've caused so much trouble.
So you remembered you buried that bone here, huh?
Well hello, Mr. Lunge.
Looks like we've arrived at the same
place through different clues.
What are you doing in this town?
What are you doing here?
You're a detective, aren't you?
I can tell.
You just have that kind of air about you.
I'm on vacation.
Those eyes don't say you're on vacation.
I was in Prague until recently.
There, I heard information about a
man involved in a certain incident.
A tall man carrying a large bag.
He had a social, friendly smile.
The color of his hair.
You match the description of the
man in my data, Mr. Neumaier.
No... Mr. Grimmer.
Why are you here in this town?
It seems that we really did arrive at the
same place through different clues.
Am I wrong?
Do you think we can stop it?
The terrible massacre that is going
to happen in this town...
Hey, you're checking the lottery numbers again?
You're not going to say anything to your husband
who's about to spend all day sweating?
You talk like you make a lot of money.
What?!
Our life will be a total disaster if we
don't win the lottery or something.
If you've got a problem with that, go make more money!
Honey!
Shut up! What do you want?!
Honey...!
What do you want, I said!
I won...
You won what?
I... I won the lottery...!
Give it back!
Where did you put my bike?
Please give it back!
Shut up!
We don't know about any bikes, right?
We did throw away some trash, though.
You threw it away?
Yeah, we threw it into the vampire's
mansion on the western hill.
Vampire...?
If you want it back, go get it yourself.
You better watch out, though.
Stupid trash!
H-Honey...
Nobody came by, right?
N-No...
Don't forget to put the chain on.
Hey.
Y-Yes?
You sure you didn't get the numbers wrong?
I... I checked them over and over again.
W-We really did win.
Twenty million marks...
W-What should we do, dear...?
I went to the next town over.
D-Dear! These are...!
Just in case.
It's not safe to have such a large sum
of money without any protection.
But if nobody finds out about it, we won't need these.
Y-Yes, well...
What's wrong?
Nobody knows the numbers you
picked for the lottery, right?
W-Well, the truth is...
W-When I bought that ticket...
The usual.
Here you go.
It sure is hard to win, isn't it, Mrs. Hennich?
Oh, hello, Mr. Konrad.
Your husband was throwing a fit about
how addicted you are to the lottery.
Well, feel free to use my birthday if you wish.
March 2, 1945.
It works pretty well.
I've won big twice at the track.
Yes, yes. Thank you for your concern.
D-Don't tell me you used Konrad's birthday...
l-lf he reads the newspaper and sees the numbers...
B-But he doesn't know that you actually
used those numbers, does he?
I don't know!
Maybe the rumors have spread across town already.
N-Now that you mention it...
W-What?
When I stopped by the general store to
buy some cigarettes on the way home...
the girl from the sausage store was looking at me.
I knew it!
It happened to me, too!
When I went to take out the trash just now...
the drunk in back of our house...
was staring at me!
Who knows what will happen if he hears
about us having so much money!
Calm down!
But...!
Listen! We have to protect ourselves now!
The vampire's mansion...
l-lt's dead!
Someone's here!
From the look of things...
He doesn't seem to have been here recently.
They're all unfinished.
Does it mean that he stopped drawing them?
Or that he couldn't continue to draw anymore?
Hey, if it isn't Wim.
Mr. Neumaier?
Mr. Lunge?
What are you doing here?
W-Well...
M-My bike...
Some of my friends said they threw my bike in here, so...
Oh, it looks like your friends played a trick on you.
If you're looking for your bike, I saw it in the thicket
near the entrance to the mountain path.
Anyway...
It looks like that cat was shot with a submachine gun.
So, they're already...
Yes, they're already nearby.
Look.
A drawing of twins?
Yes.
This one, as well.
And another one.
And another...
They're about ten years old here.
When I was in charge of Tenma's case...
those twins were about ten years old.
All of these seem to have been drawn around that time.
Just how many pictures did he draw?
No matter how many he drew...
he was never satisfied.
Man, there are so many vines this year.
I'm worried about how many cowberries
we'll be able to harvest this year.
Well, you're an unfamiliar face.
Yes
Cherish what you know is true in this world.
Ima kono sekai de wakaru koto mitsumete
Yes
Please believe in the kindness of your eyes
Anata no hitomi no yasashisa wo shinjite
Make it home to your land of harmony
Make it home to your land of purity
Make it home