This jam is truly delicious!
Thank you very much.
It's the local homemade cowberry jam.
Oh, homemade?
I'm told to show this to any customer who enjoys the jam.
He's the one who made this jam.
Oh, so he's the one who made this?
His name is Konrad.
There's a place on the hill to the south where
you can pick a lot of cowberries.
Eventually, he ended up owning the whole area.
And no one complained about it...
since his jam is so delicious.
Yes, he is a very enjoyable man to be around.
He is one of the few people I call a friend.
It was his idea to show his photograph, as well.
I guess it's his way of asking people
to support his cowberry jam.
Then we must come here again for this jam.
You're right.
I'm sure he'll be happy to hear that.
Are they really going to invade this peaceful town?
A Peaceful Home
Invade?
There are other methods than that.
There was a case where a single
gun destroyed an entire town.
It was in 1958, in Zweifelstadt.
A series of murders occurred in Niedersachsen.
When the people began to suspect their
neighbors of being the serial killer...
the townspeople became paranoid
about even dull, everyday activities.
In a state of mass hysteria...
one of the townspeople used a gun
he purchased for "protection"...
and shot his neighbor.
No one could stop it after that.
The town was set on fire...
and everything within reach became a weapon.
The residents killed each other...
and no one survived.
That can't be...
Is that going to happen to this town?
We have to stop something like that before it starts.
No.
It may have already begun.
Hey, give me your money!
I know you have some!
Hurry up and give it to me!
No, that money is for...!
It's to buy alcohol for your drunk dad, right?
Drinking too much is bad for his health!
We're helping him out!
Hey, let's go eat at the usual place!
Yeah, I'm in.
Hey, boy.
You hate them, don't you?
Don't you hate them so much that you want to kill them?
Where are you going, honey?
I'm going to talk to Konrad.
Talk to him?
When we went to the coffee shop just now...
didn't you notice how the owner, Ralph,
and all the customers were looking at us?
That's because they don't see us together that often.
No, you don't know...
what they'll do if they learn we won
20 million marks in the lottery.
B-But...
I'm saying that if we're going to be this paranoid...
it'll be better if we just talk to him!
Well, it's true that Mr. Konrad might
know that I won the lottery.
But even so, what are you going to do?
I don't care if we pay him off.
We'll keep him quiet that way.
But what if Konrad is greedy...
and he keeps demanding money from us?
W-When that happens...
What are you going to do then?
I...
I don't know!
Isn't this the place where he comes to pick his cowberries?
Honey...
Mr. Konrad isn't a bad person, right?
Yeah...
He isn't the type of person...
who would ruin the happiness we've finally found, right?
Hey, honey...
What's wrong?
H-Honey!
D-Don't tell me, you...!
l-lt wasn't me!
W-What have you done?
I told you, it wasn't me!
Then who would do such a thing?
H-How should I know!?
I haven't used the gun since I bought it!
Man, shut up...
That dog pisses me off...
Man, this is irritating...
You seem to be in a very good mood today.
Did something good happen?
He finally showed up!
Who showed up?
The wonderful man who will take
me away from this town!
A drink...
I need a drink...
Shit!
The entire town...
is laughing at me...
Shit! This is stupid!
I need a drink...
What you want...
is this, isn't it?
Your son has already taken one.
A gunshot...
And the dog stopped barking...
That was interesting!
It was cute!
Mr. Lipsky.
You're Franz Bonaparta's son, aren't you?
Please tell me where your father is.
I'm in a hurry.
If I don't hurry...
something terrible will happen.
You know where your father is, don't you, Mr. Lipsky?
You modeled that doll after Nina, didn't you?
Nina was the one who told me that you'd be here.
Nina did?
Please...
leave the curtains open.
Sure.
How long have I been here like this?
Don't worry about it.
You should rest some more.
Thank you.
I can tell, somehow...
that you've been looking after me all this time.
Don't worry.
I'm fine now.
I won't think of killing myself.
Dr. Reichwein and Dieter should be here soon.
What about you?
I have to go.
Where?
You gathered a lot of material and were
studying it here, weren't you?
Did you learn anything?
I'm okay, so please tell me.
I asked some of Prague's former secret police members...
and some of General Wolf's men...
to obtain as much information as they could.
About Franz Bonaparta.
Yes.
He's a man who's full of mysteries...
but I'm starting to piece together his profile.
A Czechoslovakian born in Germany.
It seems the name "Franz Bonaparta" is fake.
After World War II...
even though numerous Czechs born in Germany...
were chased from their homeland of Bohemia...
his family remained in the country.
Under the communist rule in Czechoslovakia...
it's unclear what kind of role
he played in the government.
I discovered that he married a Czech woman...
and even had a son with her.
It appears that his son was actually one of the students...
at his book reading seminars...
that began in the mid 1960s.
"Bonaparta's son is in Prague."
I think Peter Čapek's last words...
were pointing to his son.
Although it was an old photograph...
I was able to obtain a copy of it...
showing all the children who attended
the book readings in the 1960s.
It seems that this child on the far left is...
"Not a superior child."
He was kicked out of the book readings...
because he wasn't a "superior child."
You know about this?
He became an "unwanted child" to Bonaparta.
I'm pretty sure he's the man I know in Prague.
Does he know where his father...
Does he know where Bonaparta is?
I don't know.
But he's our only clue.
We have to hurry, or something terrible will happen.
Something terrible?
I can tell...
what Johan is trying to do.
What is he trying to do?
The perfect suicide.
True solitude.
His only expression of love.
If we don't hurry...
many innocent people will die.
Your bookshelf...
It's full of picture books written
by Bonaparta under pen names.
I've read most of them, as well.
After reading several of these, I've
come to realize something.
All the characters in his works have
German names for some reason.
Klaus Poppe's "The God of Peace."
This one, too.
However, the problem is with this pen name, Klaus Poppe.
The name Franz Bonaparta...
and all his other pen names were Czech...
but only this pen name was German.
Could it be that...
Klaus Poppe is the real name of your
German-born Czechoslovakian father?
There was a detective using the same reasoning...
who also discovered my father's real name.
A detective?
He said he was Inspector Lunge from the BKA.
Lunge?
He was here?
He left weeks ago...
He left?
He also made another deduction.
No, with Inspector Lunge...
it was more like he became the person
rather than using deduction.
"I am Klaus Poppe."
"I have no place to return to."
"In order to regain tranquility in my heart..."
"I must return to my heart's homeland."
German-born Czechoslovakians
were chased out of Bohemia...
and lost their homeland when Germany lost the war.
What part of Germany was his family from?
I don't know the details.
However, my father told me once when I was a child.
Our hometown was in southern Germany,
surrounded by mountains.
I didn't want that thing anymore...
so I gave it to Inspector Lunge.
It was a postcard I received about three or four years ago.
The sender didn't put his name.
It had a hand-drawn scene looking down
on a town from a mountain...
signed by K. P.
K. P.
Klaus Poppe...
That's all I know.
Southern Germany...
A town surrounded by mountains...
Will my father...
Will my father be killed?
I don't know.
However, that won't be the end of it.
What about Nina?
Is she safe?
I want to make a happy ending for this puppet show.
Please protect Nina.
I will.
What, exactly, is about to happen?
He's...
Johan is trying to recreate it...
The massacre that occurred at the Red Rose Mansion...
The slaughter at Kinderheim 511...
Please.
No matter what happens...
come back alive, Tenma.
You saved me.
That's why you must...
It's...
starting to rain.
Alcohol...
Give me some alcohol...
Shit!
How was it?
Did the police find Mr. Konrad's body?
No.
They still have him listed as missing,
and they're looking for him.
I knew we shouldn't have hidden his body in the woods!
If we had notified the police right away, then...
What's the use of saying that now?
You thought I was the one who shot him, too!
Man, this is what we get for winning the lottery
But still, you didn't need to buy these.
The train won't come, no matter how long you wait.
I heard the rails are flooded because of the rain!
Road traffic has also stopped because the river is flooding.
Guess we're like a deserted island.
This is the worst possible situation...
Klaus Poppe, right?
Do you know him?
Jakub Farobek...
Emit Sebe...
I think they and Poppe are all the same person.
He changed his art style and content for each...
but if you become an obsessive
like me, you can tell these things.
Though I don't know why he used
so many different pen names.
I find the art interesting.
But I just can't bring myself to like this person's works.
There are tons of picture books with
depressing content in the world.
But his works are different from those, too.
How are they different?
I guess you could say that they are full of malice.
Now then...
This is a picture book written by
an author named Helmuth Voss.
It was published in 1989.
It's hard to come by since a very limited number
were printed, but from what I can tell...
this author and Klaus Poppe are the same person.
How do you know that?
I told you.
You can tell these things when you become like me.
No matter how much he changes his art style,
it always peeks through somewhere.
The content has completely changed.
A thief escapes to a town in the mountains.
The thief has a scheme to make
some money in that town...
but forgets how to steal after interacting
with the townspeople.
And then...
he lives quietly, working for the people of the town.
The title is "A Peaceful Home."
Those bad feelings you get from his
past works were completely gone.
However, his art style became much worse.
Strange, isn't it?
When his content became better,
he couldn't draw anymore.
It feels like he lost his goal or something...
"A Peaceful Home"...
A town in the mountains...
Our hometown was in southern Germany,
surrounded by mountains.
A map...
Do you have a map of southern Germany?
What are you looking for?
A town in the mountains in southern Germany...
I found it!
Ruhenheim.
Ruhenheim
(A Peaceful Home)
Man, it's pouring out here.
Oh, did you find Konrad?
No, I have no idea where he is.
My colleagues are still searching.
But it's difficult in this rain.
The rails and roads have been closed
because the rivers are flooding.
As his friend, I know you must be worried about him.
Man, what is going on?
What happened to this peaceful town?
Starting with Mr. Konrad's disappearance...
Mrs. Hillman's dog was also shot.
Poor Mrs. Hillman is bedridden.
Mr. Kemner was attacked last night
right after leaving the pub.
I heard he was seriously injured.
We still don't know who attacked him.
If Mr. Kemner passes away...
it will be the first murder since this town was founded.
Even though we have a situation here, no reinforcements
are coming because of the rain!
What are we supposed to do with so few men?!
It must be outsiders! Outsiders!
There were no crimes in this town before!
It must be the work of outsiders!
We're outsiders as well.
No, you guys are...
It sure is pouring out there.
I can't even go outside in this rain with this wheelchair.
All right...
I'm going to get my partner and make one more round.
Be careful.
Your husband's shoes...
They are rather dirty.
It's as if he was walking in the rain.
I'm using the phone.
It's just that drunk...
It's not like he's going to do anything.
What's wrong?
Are you out of gas?
Or do you have an oil leak?
I could call a mechanic for you.
Another gunshot...
The lines are down.
Looks like we can no longer stop it.
Yes
Cherish what you know is true in this world.
Ima kono sekai de wakaru koto mitsumete
Yes
Please believe in the kindness of your eyes
Anata no hitomi no yasashisa wo shinjite
Make it home to your land of harmony
Make it home to your land of purity
Make it home